<resources>
    "<string name='apr2013_que_1'>Which of the following statements explains how price, demand and supply respond to
a shortage?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_que_2'>If the price of a product rises from £3 to £4 and demand falls from 100 to 80 units,
then using the average price elasticity of demand method the price elasticity of
demand is:</string>"
    <string name='apr2013_que_3'>If Goods X and Y are substitutes, an increase in the price of Good X causes the:</string>
    "<string name='apr2013_que_4'>A student studying a one year Masters degree in Actuarial Science has course fees of
£12,000 and could otherwise have had a job paying an after tax income of £20,000.
The cost of her accommodation is £7,000 whether she studies or works and the food
bill is £3,000 whether she studies or works. The opportunity cost of studying for the
Masters degree is:</string>"
    <string name='apr2013_que_5'>Which of the following is a measure of total consumer surplus?</string>
    <string name='apr2013_que_6'>Second degree price differentiation refers to the situation where:</string>
    "<string name='apr2013_que_7'>Which of the following is NOT implied by the principle of diminishing marginal
utility of income:</string>"
    <string name='apr2013_que_8'>For a monopoly, price exceeds marginal revenue because:</string>
    <string name='apr2013_que_9'>Which of the following is an example of economies of scope?</string>
    "<string name='apr2013_que_10'>Which of the following is NOT a motive for advertising by an existing firm in an
industry?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_que_11'>Which of the following is NOT a feature of the short run average variable cost curve
according to the law of diminishing returns?</string>"
    <string name='apr2013_que_12'>Which of the following are the three injections into the circular flow of income:</string>
    <string name='apr2013_que_13'>Which of the following statements is FALSE?</string>
    "<string name='apr2013_que_14'>During the winter season, a hotel has fixed costs of £4,000 per week, total variable
costs of £5,000 per week and prospective total revenue of £4,500 per week. In such
circumstances a profit maximising hotel will:</string>"
    <string name='apr2013_que_15'>Which of the following is NOT an example of the market drivers of globalisation?</string>
    "<string name='apr2013_que_16'>Which of the following will result in an improvement in the domestic country’s terms
of trade?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_que_17'>Which of the following will result in a decrease in aggregate demand for an economy
with international trade, other things being equal?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_que_18'>In the Keynesian 45° line diagram showing the equilibrium level of GDP in a country,
the marginal propensity to consume domestically produced goods is:</string>"
    <string name='apr2013_que_19'>The unemployment rate is given by:</string>
    "<string name='apr2013_que_20'>Which of the following is NOT a supply side economic policy aimed at promoting
economic growth?</string>"
    <string name='apr2013_que_21'>Which of the following will increase the demand to hold money?</string>
    <string name='apr2013_que_22'>According to the accelerator theory the level of investment depends on the:</string>
    "<string name='apr2013_que_23'>Which ONE of the following would be observed following a contractionary open
market operation by the central bank?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_que_24'>Which ONE of the following is NOT part of the calculation for the Gross National
Income?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_que_25'>If a central bank decides to reduce the money supply to fight inflation, then if the
country has a floating exchange rate this will assist in the process because the
exchange rate of the domestic currency will tend to:</string>"
    <string name='apr2013_que_26'>The Phillips curve shows:</string>


</resources>