<resources>
    <string name='apr2017_que_1'>The problem of scarcity in economics:</string>
    "<string name='apr2017_que_2'>If the government chooses to use resources to build a hospital instead of a school, this
illustrates the concept of:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_que_3'>When the owner of a patented product allows another firm to produce it for a fee, the
arrangement is referred to as a:</string>"
    <string name='apr2017_que_4'>In relation to insurance, moral hazard describes the fact that:</string>
    "<string name='apr2017_que_5'>A firm’s decision to reduce its expenditure on advertising is most likely to have the
following impact on its demand curve:</string>"
    <string name='apr2017_que_6'>Which of the following is an example of economies of scope?</string>
    <string name='apr2017_que_7'>Increasing long run average costs are associated with:</string>
    <string name='apr2017_que_8'>In which situation will a firm cease production in the short run?</string>
    "<string name='apr2017_que_9'>Which one of the following characteristics does NOT apply to a firm in an industry
characterised by perfect competition?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_que_10'>A monopoly firm faces a linear demand schedule and has positive but constant
marginal costs which are currently below its marginal revenue. If the firm wishes to
maximise profits then it should:</string>"
    <string name='apr2017_que_11'>A perfectly contestable market is a market where the:</string>
    "<string name='apr2017_que_12'>Which of the following is NOT usually given as a reason why firms form strategic
alliances?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_que_13' formatted="false">The terms of trade index is initially set at 100. If the average price of exports has
risen by 50% since the base year and the average price of imports has risen by 20%
since the base year, what is the current figure for the terms of trade index to the
nearest whole number?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_que_14'>Which of the following types of unemployment would exist even in a well
functioning free market economy?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_que_15'>The aggregate demand curve slopes downwards because at higher price levels the real
money supply:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_que_16'>Which of the following is least likely to lead to an increase in long run economic
growth?</string>"
    <string name='apr2017_que_17'>Unanticipated inflation:</string>
    "<string name='apr2017_que_18'>If the total output of goods and services increases and the price index falls then the
nominal Gross Domestic Product (GDP):</string>"
    <string name='apr2017_que_19'>If a country has a current account deficit then:</string>
    "<string name='apr2017_que_20'>Devaluation of a country’s currency will lead to the greatest improvement in the
current account of a country’s balance of payments when the demand for:</string>"
    <string name='apr2017_que_21'>All other things being equal, which one of the following statements is always TRUE?</string>
    "<string name='apr2017_que_22'>A government’s attempts to increase the monetary base (narrow money supply)
through open market operations are likely to cause short term interest rates to:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_que_23'>Consider an economy where the demand for real money balances is interest inelastic
and the demand for investment is interest elastic. A change in the money supply will
result in a relatively:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_que_24' formatted="false">The nominal rate of interest is 2% and the rate of inflation is negative at −3%. Which
one of the following is TRUE?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_que_25'>The introduction of a restrictive monetary policy in an open economy operating with a
flexible exchange rate would most likely lead to:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_que_26'>A central bank’s use of the “Taylor Rule” attempts to take which of the following two
macroeconomic objectives into account?</string>"


</resources>