<resources>
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_1'>A A rise in the price of cars
ENDSTOPB A fall in the price of public transport
ENDSTOPC A fall in car insurance premiums
ENDSTOPD A rise in consumers’ incomes.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_2'>A The use of the price mechanism to solve the question of what to produce
ENDSTOPB A minimal role for government
ENDSTOPC State ownership of the most important industries and private ownership of the
other industries
ENDSTOPD Freedom of entry and exit into various industries.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_3'>A 1/4 of a unit of Good Y.
ENDSTOPB 4 units of Good Y.
ENDSTOPC 10 units of Good Y.
ENDSTOPD 20 units of Good Y.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_4'>A A fall in consumers’ incomes
ENDSTOPB A rise in the price of Good X
ENDSTOPC A fall in the price of a substitute Good Y
ENDSTOPD A rise in the price of a complementary Good Y.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_5'>A An increase in labour productivity in the production of Good X
ENDSTOPB A fall in price of inputs used to produce Good X
ENDSTOPC An increase in real wages for workers producing Good X
ENDSTOPD A government subsidy on the production of Good X.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_6'>A 208 units.
ENDSTOPB 216 units.
ENDSTOPC 75 units.
ENDSTOPD 50 units.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_7'>A one unit of Good X and four units of Good Y.
ENDSTOPB two units of Good X and three units of Good Y.
ENDSTOPC three units of Good X and two units of Good Y.
ENDSTOPD four units of Good X and one unit of Good Y.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_8'>A consumer has reached a point of equilibrium with respect to the consumption
of Good X.
ENDSTOPB consumer is consuming too much of Good X and should decrease their
consumption to obtain positive marginal utility.
ENDSTOPC consumer can increase their total utility by reducing consumption of Good X.
ENDSTOPD total utility from consuming Good X must be zero.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_9'>A average variable cost.
ENDSTOPB average fixed cost.
ENDSTOPC marginal cost.
ENDSTOPD average total cost.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_10'>A In the long run, firms make only normal profits.
ENDSTOPB Price is equal to marginal cost.
ENDSTOPC Price is equal to average revenue.
ENDSTOPD An individual firm can raise its price without losing all its customers.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_11'>A Under monopolistic competition, in the long run, all firms make only normal
profits.
ENDSTOPB Firms under monopolistic competition produce homogeneous products.
ENDSTOPC Under oligopoly, firms make decisions without considering the possible
reactions of their competitors.
ENDSTOPD Under monopoly, a profit maximising firm with positive marginal costs
always produces where the demand is price inelastic.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_12'>A Firm A – High; Firm ENDSTOPB – Low
B Firm A – High; Firm B – High
ENDSTOPC Firm A – Low; Firm B – Low
ENDSTOPD Firm A – Low; Firm B – High.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_13'>A price in Market 2.
ENDSTOPB price in Market 1.
ENDSTOPC marginal revenue in Market 2.
ENDSTOPD average cost in Market 2.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_14'>A The investment multiplier has a value of 5.
ENDSTOPB At the equilibrium level of income, consumption will be £470 million.
ENDSTOPC The economy is in equilibrium if output is £500 million.
ENDSTOPD None of the above.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_15'>A An increase in the income tax rate
ENDSTOPB A decrease in government expenditure
ENDSTOPC A decrease in the value of exports
ENDSTOPD A decrease in the rate of interest.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_16'>A £2,000,000
ENDSTOPB £800,000
ENDSTOPC £600,000
ENDSTOPD £300,000.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_17'>A The simple closed economy multiplier, ignoring taxes, is 2.
ENDSTOPB The simple closed economy multiplier, including taxes, is 5.
ENDSTOPC An increase in government expenditure of £10 million will increase the
national income by £25 million.
ENDSTOPD An increase in government expenditure of £10 million will increase the
national income by £10 million.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_18'>A 395, 400.
ENDSTOPB 395, 390.
ENDSTOPC 455, 460.
ENDSTOPD 455, 450.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_19'>A £45,000.
ENDSTOPB £30,150.
ENDSTOPC £29,850.
ENDSTOPD £20,000.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_20'>A Investment income from abroad
ENDSTOPB Investment expenditure
ENDSTOPC Export revenue
ENDSTOPD Government expenditure on employing teachers.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_21'>A £40 million.
ENDSTOPB £60 million.
ENDSTOPC £80 million.
ENDSTOPD £100 million.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_22'>A 0.8
ENDSTOPB Greater than 0.8
ENDSTOPC 0.2
ENDSTOPD Less than 0.2</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_23'>A £500 billion
ENDSTOPB £550 billion
ENDSTOPC £600 billion
ENDSTOPD £700 billion.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_24'>A 1%.
ENDSTOPB 1.25%.
ENDSTOPC 9%.
ENDSTOPD 13%.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_25'>A A reduction in unemployment benefit
ENDSTOPB Better dissemination of information about job vacancies
ENDSTOPC An extension of job retraining programmes
ENDSTOPD A reduction in the minimum wage.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2022_choices_26'>A negative relationship between inflation and economic growth.
ENDSTOPB positive relationship between inflation and economic growth.
ENDSTOPC negative relationship between inflation and unemployment.
ENDSTOPD positive relationship between inflation and unemployment.</string>"



</resources>