<resources>
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_1'>A exists only in economies which rely on the market mechanism.
ENDSTOPB could be eliminated if prices are forced to fall.
ENDSTOPC means that there are shortages of some goods.
ENDSTOPD exists because there are insufficient resources to satisfy human wants.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_2'>A a market system.
ENDSTOPB macroeconomics.
ENDSTOPC competition.
ENDSTOPD opportunity cost.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_3'>A franchise.
ENDSTOPB joint venture.
ENDSTOPC licensing agreement.
ENDSTOPD merger.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_4'>A people who know that they are a particularly high risk are more inclined to
take out insurance.
ENDSTOPB a policyholder may act in a way which makes the insured event more likely to
occur.
ENDSTOPC people who know that they are a particularly high risk are less inclined to take
out insurance.
ENDSTOPD an insurance company will face false insurance claims.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_5'>A The curve will shift to the left and become less elastic.
ENDSTOPB The curve will shift to the right and become less elastic.
ENDSTOPC The curve will shift to the left and become more elastic.
ENDSTOPD The curve will shift to the right and become more elastic.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_6'>A A firm doubles its inputs of capital and labour and its output more than
doubles.
ENDSTOPB A firm doubles the number of products it produces and also doubles its
research budget.
ENDSTOPC A firm produces a new product and in so doing lowers the average cost of
producing its existing products.
ENDSTOPD A firm produces a new product and in so doing lowers the price it charges on
its existing products.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_7'>A constant returns to scale.
ENDSTOPB decreasing returns to scale.
ENDSTOPC increasing returns to scale.
ENDSTOPD the law of diminishing returns.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_8'>A Total revenue is less than total costs.
ENDSTOPB Total revenue is less than total fixed costs.
ENDSTOPC Average revenue is less than average fixed cost.
ENDSTOPD Average revenue is less than average variable cost.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_9'>A The firm can make only normal profits in the long run.
ENDSTOPB There are no barriers to entry into the market.
ENDSTOPC The firm can make only normal profits in the short run.
ENDSTOPD Marginal revenue is equal to average revenue.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_10'>A lower its price and increase output.
ENDSTOPB raise its price and increase output.
ENDSTOPC lower its price and decrease output.
ENDSTOPD raise its price and decrease output.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_11'>A costs of entry and exit are zero and potential entrants can enter the market
quickly.
ENDSTOPB existing companies charge identical prices.
ENDSTOPC the barriers to entry are substantial but the existing firms compete so hard that
industry profits are kept to the normal level over both the short and long run.
ENDSTOPD existing firms compete on price and quality so as to maximise industry
supernormal profits in the long run.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_12'>A entry into new markets
ENDSTOPB risk sharing
ENDSTOPC capital pooling
ENDSTOPD to reduce overall managerial remuneration</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_13'>A 83
ENDSTOPB 125
ENDSTOPC 250
ENDSTOPD 80</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_14'>A classical
ENDSTOPB frictional
ENDSTOPC technological
ENDSTOPD structural</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_15'>A decreases and national income is lower.
ENDSTOPB decreases and national income is higher.
ENDSTOPC increases and national income is lower.
ENDSTOPD increases and national income is higher.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_16'>A An increase in the money supply.
ENDSTOPB An increase in capital investment expenditure.
ENDSTOPC An increase in education expenditure.
ENDSTOPD An increase in research and development expenditure.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_17'>A increases the opportunity cost of holding money and redistributes wealth from
fixed rate borrowers to lenders.
ENDSTOPB increases the opportunity cost of holding money and redistributes wealth from
fixed rate lenders to borrowers.
ENDSTOPC reduces the opportunity cost of holding money and redistributes wealth from
fixed rate borrowers to lenders.
ENDSTOPD reduces the opportunity cost of holding money and redistributes wealth from
fixed rate lenders to borrowers.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_18'>A may rise or fall and real GDP will fall.
ENDSTOPB will stay the same and real GDP will rise.
ENDSTOPC will rise and real GDP will rise.
ENDSTOPD may rise or fall and real GDP will rise.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_19'>A Gross Domestic Product is greater than Gross National Income.
ENDSTOPB Gross Domestic Product is less than Gross National Income.
ENDSTOPC Gross Domestic Product is the same as Gross National Income.
ENDSTOPD we cannot say whether Gross Domestic Product differs from Gross National
Income.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_20'>A imports is price elastic and the demand for exports is price inelastic.
ENDSTOPB imports is price inelastic and the demand for exports is price elastic.
ENDSTOPC both imports and exports is price inelastic.
ENDSTOPD both imports and exports is price elastic.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_21'>A An appreciation of a country’s exchange rate will increase its import
expenditure and decrease its export revenues.
ENDSTOPB An appreciation of a country’s exchange rate will increase its import volumes
and decrease its export volumes.
ENDSTOPC A depreciation of a country’s exchange rate will decrease its import volumes
and decrease its export volumes.
ENDSTOPD A depreciation of a country’s exchange rate will decrease its import
expenditure and increase its export revenues.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_22'>A fall and reduce money demand.
ENDSTOPB fall and raise money demand.
ENDSTOPC rise and reduce money demand.
ENDSTOPD rise and raise money demand.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_23'>A small change in the rate of interest and the level of investment.
ENDSTOPB large change in the rate of interest and the level of investment.
ENDSTOPC small change in the rate of interest and a relatively large change in the level of
investment.
ENDSTOPD large change in the rate of interest and a relatively small change in the level of
investment.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_24'>A The real rate of interest is greater than the nominal rate of interest.
ENDSTOPB The real rate of interest is negative.
ENDSTOPC The rate of inflation is greater than the real rate of interest.
ENDSTOPD The real rate of interest is −1%.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_25'>A higher domestic interest rates and an exchange rate appreciation.
ENDSTOPB higher domestic interest rates and an exchange rate depreciation.
ENDSTOPC lower domestic interest rates and an exchange rate appreciation.
ENDSTOPD lower domestic interest rates and an exchange rate depreciation.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2017_choices_26'>A inflation and the exchange rate
ENDSTOPB economic growth and unemployment
ENDSTOPC inflation and economic growth
ENDSTOPD unemployment and the exchange rate</string>"


</resources>