<resources>
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_1'>A Price elasticity of demand is minus one and price falls.
ENDSTOPB Demand is price elastic and price falls.
ENDSTOPC Demand is price inelastic and price falls.
ENDSTOPD Demand is price inelastic and price rises.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_2'>A 1.33 units of Good X.
ENDSTOPB 2 units of Good X.
ENDSTOPC 8 units of Good X.
ENDSTOPD 10 units of Good X.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_3'>A An increase in labour productivity in industry X.
ENDSTOPB A fall in the price of raw materials used to produce Good X.
ENDSTOPC An increase in wages in industry X.
ENDSTOPD A government subsidy on the production of Good X.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_4'>A A rise in the price charged to consumers of more than £7.50.
ENDSTOPB A rise in the price charged to consumers of £7.50.
ENDSTOPC A rise in the price charged to consumers of between £5 and £7.50.
ENDSTOPD A rise in the price charged to consumers of less than £5.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_5'>A 125 units.
ENDSTOPB 95 units.
ENDSTOPC 80 units.
ENDSTOPD 70 units.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_6'>A (i) only
ENDSTOPB (i) and (ii) only
ENDSTOPC (i) and (iii) only
ENDSTOPD (i), (ii) and (iii)</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_7'>A The long run average total cost curve passes through the minimum point of all
the short run average total cost curves.
ENDSTOPB The minimum efficient scale is the point at which long run average costs must
begin to fall.
ENDSTOPC In the long run a firm cannot alter its fixed costs of production.
ENDSTOPD If a firm doubles all its inputs and its output rises by 50 per cent then this is
indicative of diseconomies of scale.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_8'>A greater than one.
ENDSTOPB equal to zero.
ENDSTOPC between zero and one.
ENDSTOPD one.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_9'>A Under perfect competition, in the long run all firms make only normal profits.
ENDSTOPB Firms under monopolistic competition produce homogeneous products.
ENDSTOPC Under oligopoly, firms make decisions taking into account the possible
reactions of their competitors.
ENDSTOPD A profit maximising monopoly will equate its marginal costs to its marginal
revenue.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_10'>A Equilibrium price will be equal to marginal cost.
ENDSTOPB There are no barriers to entry.
ENDSTOPC The average revenue curve is greater than the marginal revenue curve.
ENDSTOPD Only normal profits are made in the long run.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_11'>A increase price and reduce output.
ENDSTOPB reduce price and reduce output.
ENDSTOPC increase price and increase output.
ENDSTOPD close down.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_12'>A rightward shift of the supply curve for Good X.
ENDSTOPB leftward shift of the supply curve for Good X.
ENDSTOPC rightward shift of the demand curve for Good X.
ENDSTOPD leftward shift of the demand curve for Good X.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_13'>A 20
ENDSTOPB 30
ENDSTOPC 40
ENDSTOPD 50</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_14'>A gross fixed capital formation.
ENDSTOPB capital depreciation.
ENDSTOPC consumption expenditure.
ENDSTOPD net income from abroad.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_15'>A The multiplier has a value of greater than 4.
ENDSTOPB At the equilibrium level of income, consumption expenditure is £260 million.
ENDSTOPC The economy is in equilibrium if output is £300 million.
ENDSTOPD None of the above.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_16'>A rise as the short-term interest rate falls.
ENDSTOPB rise as the short-term interest rate rises.
ENDSTOPC fall as the short-term interest rate rises.
ENDSTOPD fall as the short-term interest rate falls.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_17'>A (i) increase, (ii) decrease
ENDSTOPB (i) increase, (ii) increase
ENDSTOPC (i) decrease, (ii) increase
ENDSTOPD (i) decrease, (ii) decrease</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_18'>A £150 million
ENDSTOPB £130 million
ENDSTOPC £120 million
ENDSTOPD £110 million</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_19'>A Decrease interest rates and increase income tax rates.
ENDSTOPB Increase interest rates and decrease income tax rates.
ENDSTOPC Decrease interest rates and decrease income tax rates.
ENDSTOPD Increase interest rates and increase income tax rates.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_20'>A the government spends more money.
ENDSTOPB the government buys Treasury bills from the public.
ENDSTOPC a citizen buys a newly issued corporate bond.
ENDSTOPD a firm obtains an overdraft from a bank.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_21'>A Exports become less expensive when measured in the foreign currency.
ENDSTOPB Imports become cheaper when measured in the domestic currency.
ENDSTOPC Export volumes will increase.
ENDSTOPD Import volumes will decrease.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_22'>A Increased government expenditure on domestically produced goods.
ENDSTOPB Increasing the money supply.
ENDSTOPC Reducing the general level of interest rates to increase the supply of loans.
ENDSTOPD A privatisation programme.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_23'>A An increase in the marginal propensity to save.
ENDSTOPB An increase in government expenditure.
ENDSTOPC An increase in the marginal propensity to consume.
ENDSTOPD An increase in income tax rates.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_24'>A Interest rates must have risen.
ENDSTOPB The velocity of circulation must have fallen.
ENDSTOPC The price level must have risen by the same proportion as the increase in the
money supply.
ENDSTOPD Taxes must have risen.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_25'>A unemployment benefit.
ENDSTOPB government expenditure.
ENDSTOPC information on job availability.
ENDSTOPD the money supply.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_choices_26'>A increase and the domestic money supply will fall.
ENDSTOPB increase and the domestic money supply will rise.
ENDSTOPC decrease and the domestic money supply will rise.
ENDSTOPD decrease and the domestic money supply will fall.</string>"




</resources>