<resources>
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_1'>A Price rises, quantity demanded falls and quantity supplied rises.
ENDSTOPB Price rises, quantity demanded falls and quantity supplied falls.
ENDSTOPC Price falls, quantity demanded rises and quantity supplied falls.
ENDSTOPD Price rises, quantity demanded rises and quantity supplied rises.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_2'>A will fall and the equilibrium quantity may rise or fall.
ENDSTOPB will fall and the equilibrium quantity will rise.
ENDSTOPC may rise or fall or remain the same and the equilibrium quantity will fall.
ENDSTOPD may rise or fall or remain the same and the equilibrium quantity will rise.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_3'>A -12
ENDSTOPB -0.5
ENDSTOPC -2
ENDSTOPD -4</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_4'>A average physical product falls.
ENDSTOPB average physical product rises.
ENDSTOPC marginal physical product falls.
ENDSTOPD marginal physical product rises.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_5'>A Advertising is intended to shift the demand curve for a firm’s product upwards
to the right.
ENDSTOPB Advertising is intended to make the demand for a firm’s product more price
elastic.
ENDSTOPC A potential feature of a successful advertising campaign is that it increases a
firm’s total revenue by more than it increases the firm’s total costs.
ENDSTOPD Advertising can enable a firm to gain economies of scale.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_6'>A and exit from it are both costless.
ENDSTOPB is costly, but exit from it is costless.
ENDSTOPC is costless, but exit from it is costly.
ENDSTOPD and exit from it are both costly.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_7'>A E(U(X - a)) = U(a – P)
ENDSTOPB E(U(a - X)) = U(P – a)
ENDSTOPC E(U(a - X)) = U(a – P)
ENDSTOPD E(U(X - a)) = U(P – a)</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_8'>A If more labour is added to a given amount of capital, the marginal product of
labour remains unchanged.
ENDSTOPB If the ratio of labour to capital doubles, the output of the firm also doubles.
ENDSTOPC If both the input of capital and labour doubles, output remains constant.
ENDSTOPD If the input of capital and labour doubles, the ratio of output to inputs is
unchanged.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_9'>A reduce price and increase output.
ENDSTOPB reduce price and reduce output.
ENDSTOPC increase price and increase output.
ENDSTOPD increase price and reduce output.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_10'>A average total cost curve.
ENDSTOPB average variable cost curve.
ENDSTOPC marginal cost curve above the lowest point of the average total cost curve.
ENDSTOPD marginal cost curve above the lowest point of the average variable cost curve.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_11'>A Some degree of monopoly power ensures that in the long run firms can make
supernormal profits.
ENDSTOPB There is freedom of entry and exit into the industry in the long run.
ENDSTOPC Firms in the industry produce differentiated products.
ENDSTOPD Firms in the industry charge prices above their marginal costs of production.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_12'>A Under perfect competition, in the long run only some firms can make excess
profits.
ENDSTOPB Under oligopoly all firms make decisions without taking into account the
possible reactions of their competitors.
ENDSTOPC For a monopolist facing a linear demand curve, average revenue is always less
than marginal revenue.
ENDSTOPD Firms under monopolistic competition charge a price above their marginal
revenue.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_13'>A not run the extra flight as it will expect to lose £4,500 from its profits.
ENDSTOPB not run the extra flight as its expected profit of £1,500 is insufficient to cover
its fixed costs.
ENDSTOPC run the extra flight as it will add £1,500 to its profits.
ENDSTOPD not run the extra flight as the expected revenue of £4,500 is less than its fixed
costs.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_14'>A the income method
ENDSTOPB the expenditure method
ENDSTOPC the product method
ENDSTOPD the investment method</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_15'>A £250 million.
ENDSTOPB £260 million.
ENDSTOPC £270 million.
ENDSTOPD £280 million.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_16'>A £70 million
ENDSTOPB £143 million
ENDSTOPC £170 million
ENDSTOPD £333 million</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_17'>A a fall in the rate of interest
ENDSTOPB a rise in the real Gross Domestic Product
ENDSTOPC the rise in the frequency with which people are paid
ENDSTOPD a higher expectation that stock prices will fall</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_18'>A £200 million
ENDSTOPB £312.5 million
ENDSTOPC £1,000 million
ENDSTOPD £800 million</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_19'>A add net income from abroad and add capital depreciation.
ENDSTOPB add net income from abroad and deduct capital depreciation.
ENDSTOPC deduct net income from abroad and add capital depreciation.
ENDSTOPD deduct net income from abroad and deduct capital depreciation.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_20'>A a depreciation of the domestic currency as the short term domestic interest rate
falls.
ENDSTOPB a depreciation of the domestic currency as the short term domestic interest rate
rises.
ENDSTOPC an appreciation of the domestic currency as the short term domestic interest
rate rises.
ENDSTOPD an appreciation of the domestic currency as the short term domestic interest
rate falls.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_21'>A decreasing social security benefits
ENDSTOPB decreasing the money supply
ENDSTOPC increasing corporate and personal taxation
ENDSTOPD increasing government expenditure aimed at exploiting the multiplier effect</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_22'>A surplus of £25 billion.
ENDSTOPB deficit of £75 billion.
ENDSTOPC surplus of £75 billion.
ENDSTOPD deficit of £25 billion.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_23'>A the GDP per capita must rise.
ENDSTOPB the GDP per capita must fall.
ENDSTOPC the GDP per capita remains constant.
ENDSTOPD there is insufficient information to determine what has happened to GDP per
capita.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_24'>A a decrease in trade union powers
ENDSTOPB a depreciation of the domestic currency\'s exchange rate
ENDSTOPC a rise in labour productivity
ENDSTOPD a fall in the profit margins applied by firms</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_25'>A absolute advantage.
ENDSTOPB comparative advantage.
ENDSTOPC different factor endowments.
ENDSTOPD all of the above.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_choices_26'>A The demand for money is positively related to the interest rate.
ENDSTOPB The demand for money is negatively related to wealth.
ENDSTOPC The demand for money is negatively related to the general price level.
ENDSTOPD The demand for money is positively related to real income.</string>"




</resources>