<resources>
    <string name='apr2018_que_1'>Which of the following statements below is always TRUE?</string>
    <string name='apr2018_que_2'>Which one of the following will shift the supply curve for Good X to the left?</string>
    "<string name='apr2018_que_3'>Good X is an inferior good. A fall in consumer income when the supply curve for
Good X is positively sloped will cause which one of the following?</string>"
    <string name='apr2018_que_4'>In relation to insurance, the term moral hazard suggests:</string>
    "<string name='apr2018_que_5'>Assuming that the marginal and average cost curves are unchanged then, following a
shift in the demand curve to the right, firms in a perfectly competitive industry will:</string>"
    <string name='apr2018_que_6'>The profit maximising output for a monopoly is at the point where the:</string>
    <string name='apr2018_que_7'>Which one of the following is NOT a barrier to entry into a monopoly market?</string>
    "<string name='apr2018_que_8'>A firm is selling 1,000 units of output at a price of £20, with a marginal cost of £5 and
average variable cost of £8 at that level of output. What is the supernormal profit that
the monopoly firm is making?</string>"
    <string name='apr2018_que_9'>Which one of the following statements about market structures is FALSE?</string>
    <string name='apr2018_que_10'>Under the Cournot model of duopoly, a firm:</string>
    "<string name='apr2018_que_11'>Which one of the following is NOT one of the four phases associated with the product
life cycle theory?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_que_12'>Which one of the following definitions is most compatible with the Basel III definition
of capital adequacy?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_que_13'>Which of the following will result in a deterioration in the domestic country’s terms of
trade?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_que_14'>Which one of the following is most likely to be the best method of reducing long term
structural unemployment?</string>"
    <string name='apr2018_que_15'>If a country has a current account surplus then:</string>
    "<string name='apr2018_que_16'>A country with a population of 20 million has 15 million in employment and 1 million
unemployed. What is the unemployment rate?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_que_17'>Which of the following could explain why a country’s aggregate demand curve might
shift outwards to the right?</string>"
    <string name='apr2018_que_18'>The business cycle is defined as:</string>
    "<string name='apr2018_que_19'>If the rate of inflation is higher than the anticipated rate used for negotiating interest
rates and wages:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_que_20'>Other things being equal, an increase in the level of real output in an economy will
result in:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_que_21'>An unexpected fall in the price level which causes a temporary rise in the real wage
rate may:</string>"
    <string name='apr2018_que_22'>The accelerator theory implies that:</string>
    "<string name='apr2018_que_23'>As a result of a change in economic policy, interest rates and consumption rise but
investment falls. The new policy is most likely to have been:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_que_24'>The introduction of an expansionary monetary policy in an open economy operating
with a flexible exchange rate would most likely lead to:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_que_25'>Which of the following is a supply side economic policy aimed at promoting
economic growth?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_que_26'>Which one of the following will NOT happen following a devaluation of the domestic
currency on the foreign exchange market?</string>"




</resources>