<resources>
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_1'>A Price rises, quantity demanded falls and quantity supplied rises.
ENDSTOPB Price rises, quantity demanded falls and quantity supplied falls.
ENDSTOPC Price rises, quantity demanded rises and quantity supplied falls.
ENDSTOPD Price rises, quantity demanded rises and quantity supplied rises.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_2'>A −0.60
ENDSTOPB −0.78
ENDSTOPC −1
ENDSTOPD −0.05</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_3'>A demand curve for Good X to shift to the left, and the demand curve for Good
Y to shift to the left.
ENDSTOPB demand curve for Good X to shift to the left, and the demand curve for Good
Y to shift to the right.
ENDSTOPC quantity demanded of Good X to fall, and the demand curve for Good Y to
shift to the right.
ENDSTOPD quantity demanded of Good X to fall, and the demand curve for Good Y to
shift to the left.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_4'>A £12,000.
ENDSTOPB £20,000.
ENDSTOPC £32,000.
ENDSTOPD £42,000.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_5'>A Marginal utility minus the price of the good.
ENDSTOPB The total utility consumers get from the consumption of the good.
ENDSTOPC The total utility consumers get from consumption of the good less the total
expenditure on the good.
ENDSTOPD Marginal utility times the price of the good.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_6'>A a firm charges customers different prices according to how much they
purchase.
ENDSTOPB consumers are grouped into independent markets and a separate price is
charged in each market.
ENDSTOPC a firm charges each customer the maximum price he/she is prepared to pay.
ENDSTOPD different firms charge different prices for the same product.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_7'>A Total utility increases at a decreasing rate as income increases.
ENDSTOPB Marginal utility increases at a decreasing rate as income increases.
ENDSTOPC Marginal utility decreases at an increasing rate as income falls.
ENDSTOPD Total utility decreases at an increasing rate as income increases.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_8'>A the firm has to charge a price higher than the marginal cost of producing the
last unit.
ENDSTOPB any decision by the monopolist to sell an additional unit of output does not
affect product price.
ENDSTOPC the firm has to reduce the price on all units sold in order to sell an additional
unit.
ENDSTOPD of the law of diminishing returns.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_9'>A A firm doubles its inputs of capital and labour and its output more than
doubles.
ENDSTOPB A firm doubles the number of products it produces and also doubles its
research budget.
ENDSTOPC A firm produces a new product and in so doing lowers the average cost of
producing its existing products.
ENDSTOPD A firm produces a new product and in so doing lowers the price it charges on
its existing products.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_10'>A To make the demand for the product more price elastic.
ENDSTOPB To shift the demand for the firm’s product to the right.
ENDSTOPC To increase barriers to entry.
ENDSTOPD To increase sales and so help the firm exploit economies of scale.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_11'>A The average variable cost curve is U-shaped.
ENDSTOPB The average variable cost curve cuts the marginal cost curve at the minimum
of the marginal cost curve.
ENDSTOPC The average variable cost curve is an increasing proportion of average total
costs as output rises.
ENDSTOPD The average variable cost curve lies below the average fixed costs of
production.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_12'>A Investment, government expenditure and exports
ENDSTOPB Consumption, government expenditure and investment
ENDSTOPC Consumption, investment and exports
ENDSTOPD Investment, government expenditure and imports</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_13'>A For a firm under perfect competition in the short run, marginal revenue will be
equal to the average revenue.
ENDSTOPB In an oligopoly industry, firms make decisions taking into account the possible
reactions of their competitors.
ENDSTOPC For a monopolist facing a linear demand curve, average revenue is always less
than marginal revenue.
ENDSTOPD A profit maximising monopoly firm with positive marginal costs of production
charges a price in the region of the demand curve where demand is price
elastic.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_14'>A close down during the winter season since it would make a loss of £4,500
during the winter season.
ENDSTOPB close down during the winter season since its revenue is insufficient to cover
its fixed costs.
ENDSTOPC stay open during the winter season as it will add £500 per week to its profits.
ENDSTOPD stay open during the winter season as the expected revenue of £4,500 is
greater than its fixed costs.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_15'>A Establishment of world brands
ENDSTOPB Increasing travel, creating global consumers
ENDSTOPC Per capita income converging among industrialised nations
ENDSTOPD Reduction of tariff barriers</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_16'>A A rise in the average price of imports relative to the average price of exports.
ENDSTOPB A fall in the quantity of imports relative to the quantity of exports.
ENDSTOPC A rise in the quantity of exports while imports remain the same.
ENDSTOPD A rise in the average price of exports relative to the average price of imports.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_17'>A A rise in imports
ENDSTOPB A fall in savings
ENDSTOPC A fall in interest rates
ENDSTOPD A fall in economic and business uncertainty</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_18'>A the intercept of the line representing the part of income spent on goods
produced in the country.
ENDSTOPB the proportion of any rise in GDP withdrawn from the circular flow of income.
ENDSTOPC the slope of the aggregate expenditure line.
ENDSTOPD the slope of the line representing the part of income spent on goods produced
in the country.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_19'>A the number of unemployed divided by the population expressed as a
percentage.
ENDSTOPB the number of unemployed divided by the total labour force expressed as a
percentage.
ENDSTOPC the number of unemployed divided by the number of employed expressed as a
percentage.
ENDSTOPD the number of unemployed divided by all in the population of working age
expressed as a percentage.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_20'>A Cuts in social security benefits designed to encourage more workers to take
work
ENDSTOPB Measures designed to reduce trade union powers
ENDSTOPC Deregulation
ENDSTOPD Tariffs designed to increase production of domestic goods</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_21'>A A fall in the national income
ENDSTOPB A rise in the rate of interest
ENDSTOPC A rise in the expectation of a stock market crash
ENDSTOPD An increase in the frequency with which people are paid, for example, a
switch from monthly to weekly payments</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_22'>A level of national income.
ENDSTOPB rate of change of national income.
ENDSTOPC rate of change of the level of investment
ENDSTOPD level of the interest rate</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_23'>A A fall in the money supply, a fall in the short term rate of interest and a fall in
the price of treasury bills
ENDSTOPB A fall in the money supply, a fall in the short term rate of interest and a rise in
the price of treasury bills
ENDSTOPC A fall in the money supply, a rise in the short term rate of interest and a fall in
the price of treasury bills
ENDSTOPD A fall in the money supply, a rise in the short term rate of interest and a rise in
the price of treasury bills</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_24'>A Net income from abroad
ENDSTOPB Gross capital formation
ENDSTOPC Capital depreciation
ENDSTOPD Imports of goods and services</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_25'>A appreciate and reduce the price of exports.
ENDSTOPB appreciate and reduce the price of imports.
ENDSTOPC depreciate and reduce the price of exports.
ENDSTOPD depreciate and reduce the price of imports.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2013_choices_26'>A the influence of fiscal policy on the level of inflation and unemployment.
ENDSTOPB the influence of monetary policy on the level of inflation and unemployment.
ENDSTOPC an inverse relationship between inflation and unemployment.
ENDSTOPD a positive relationship between inflation and unemployment.</string>"

</resources>