<resources>
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_1'>A exists only in economies that are at full employment.
ENDSTOPB can be eliminated if prices are allowed to rise or fall so as to keep supply equal
to demand.
ENDSTOPC means that there are shortages of some goods due to demand being greater
than supply.
ENDSTOPD exists because there are insufficient resources to satisfy human wants.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_2'>A The effect on price is indeterminate but quantity will fall.
ENDSTOPB The effect on price is indeterminate but quantity will rise.
ENDSTOPC The effect on quantity is indeterminate but price will fall.
ENDSTOPD The effect on quantity is indeterminate but price will rise.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_3'>A long-run total cost rises as output rises.
ENDSTOPB long-run average total cost falls as output rises.
ENDSTOPC short-run average total cost falls as output rises.
ENDSTOPD short-run average total cost rises as output rises.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_4'>A The firm will equate its marginal costs to its average revenue.
ENDSTOPB The firm will equate its marginal costs to its marginal revenue.
ENDSTOPC The firm will have an average revenue that exceeds its average variable costs
of production.
ENDSTOPD The firm will make only normal profits.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_5'>A each firm will NOT take account of its rival’s reactions when making its
pricing decision.
ENDSTOPB the price set by one firm will NOT influence the price set by the other firm.
ENDSTOPC in avoiding the worst possible outcome, each of the firms will fail to reach the
best possible outcome.
ENDSTOPD in avoiding the worst possible outcome, each of the firms will succeed in
reaching the best possible outcome.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_6'>A the consumers of the good at the expense of the producers.
ENDSTOPB the producers of the good at the expense of the consumers.
ENDSTOPC both the consumers and producers.
ENDSTOPD neither the producers nor the consumers.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_7'>A less than £5 and decrease the price by less than £5.
ENDSTOPB less than £5 and decrease the price by more than £5.
ENDSTOPC £5 exactly and decrease the price by £5 exactly.
ENDSTOPD £5 exactly and decrease the price by less than £5.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_8'>A 1/3
ENDSTOPB 2
ENDSTOPC 3
ENDSTOPD 5.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_9'>A The quantity consumers would like to buy annually.
ENDSTOPB The quantity consumers are willing and able to buy at each level of income
over the next year.
ENDSTOPC The quantity consumers are willing and able to buy annually at each price.
ENDSTOPD The quantity consumers are willing and able to buy over the next year.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_10'>A no tendency for the market price of Good X to change.
ENDSTOPB an excess demand for Good X.
ENDSTOPC an excess supply of Good X.
ENDSTOPD an upward pressure on the price of Good X.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_11'>A The average total cost of the eleventh unit is greater than the average total cost
of the tenth unit.
ENDSTOPB The total fixed costs for eleven units are £177.
ENDSTOPC The average fixed cost for eleven units is greater than the marginal cost for the
eleventh unit.
ENDSTOPD The average variable cost of production for the eleventh unit is less than the
marginal cost of production for the eleventh unit.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_12'>A Strategy 1
ENDSTOPB Strategy 2
ENDSTOPC Strategy 3
ENDSTOPD Strategy 4.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_13'>A not run the extra flight because it will expect profits to decrease (or losses
increase) by £250.
ENDSTOPB not run the extra flight because its expected profit of £250 is insufficient to
cover its fixed costs.
ENDSTOPC run the extra flight because that will increase profits (or reduce losses) by
£250.
ENDSTOPD run the extra flight because the expected revenue of £4,750 is more than its
fixed costs.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_14'>A shift to the right and the overall consumption of Good X to fall.
ENDSTOPB become flatter and the overall consumption of Good X to rise.
ENDSTOPC shift to the right and the overall consumption of Good X to rise.
ENDSTOPD become steeper and the overall consumption of Good X to fall.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_15'>A A decrease in interest rates
ENDSTOPB An appreciation of the domestic currency
ENDSTOPC A rise in government expenditure
ENDSTOPD An increase in business confidence.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_16'>A If nominal Gross Domestic Product (GDP) rises by 3%, then the real GDP
must have risen.
ENDSTOPB The nominal GDP must change by a bigger percentage than the real GDP if
there is positive rise in the GDP deflator.
ENDSTOPC An increase in real income will lead to a fall in the demand for real money
balances.
ENDSTOPD Real interest rates can be negative even if both the nominal interest rate and
expected inflation rate are positive.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_17'>A a rise in aggregate demand and a rise in unemployment.
ENDSTOPB a rise in aggregate demand and a fall in unemployment.
ENDSTOPC a fall in aggregate demand and a rise in unemployment.
ENDSTOPD an indeterminate effect on aggregate demand and unemployment.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_18'>A Reducing social security benefits
ENDSTOPB Increasing the money supply
ENDSTOPC Reducing corporate and personal taxation
ENDSTOPD Increased government expenditure on education and training.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_19'>A £200 million
ENDSTOPB £600 million
ENDSTOPC £1,000 million
ENDSTOPD None of the above.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_20'>A An increase in trade union powers
ENDSTOPB An appreciation of the domestic currency’s exchange rate
ENDSTOPC A rise in labour productivity
ENDSTOPD A decrease in the profit margins applied by firms.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_21'>A lower short-term interest rates because the aggregate demand curve shifts to
the left.
ENDSTOPB raise short-term interest rates because the aggregate demand shifts to the left.
ENDSTOPC lower short-term interest rates because the aggregate demand curve shifts to
the right.
ENDSTOPD raise short-term interest rates because the aggregate demand curve shifts to the
right.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_22'>A fall, and real output will rise.
ENDSTOPB fall, and real output will fall.
ENDSTOPC rise, and real output will rise.
ENDSTOPD rise, and real output will fall.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_23'>A (i) increase, (ii) decrease
ENDSTOPB (i) increase, (ii) increase
ENDSTOPC (i) decrease, (ii) increase
ENDSTOPD (i) decrease, (ii) decrease.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_24'>A National income will tend to increase.
ENDSTOPB National income will tend to decrease.
ENDSTOPC Unemployment and production will tend to fall.
ENDSTOPD The general level of prices will tend to fall.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_25'>A velocity of circulation increases.
ENDSTOPB real national income decreases.
ENDSTOPC velocity of circulation is constant and the real national income increases.
ENDSTOPD velocity of circulation and the real national income are constant.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2023_choices_26'>A fall in inflation and fall in unemployment.
ENDSTOPB rise in inflation and fall in unemployment.
ENDSTOPC fall in inflation and rise in unemployment.
ENDSTOPD rise in inflation and rise in unemployment.</string>"


</resources>