<resources>"<string name='apr2005_choices_1'>A a movement along the demand curve such that quantity demanded declines
ENDSTOPB a movement along the demand curve such that quantity demanded increases
ENDSTOPC a shift to the right of the demand curve
ENDSTOPD a shift to the left of the demand curve</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_2'>A consumers wish to purchase more of the product at the market price than is
offered for sale
ENDSTOPB the quantity actually traded at the market price is determined by the supply
curve
ENDSTOPC the quantity actually traded at the market price is determined by the demand
curve
ENDSTOPD the market price is below the equilibrium price</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_3'>A the good becomes less expensive relative to all other products
ENDSTOPB the change in price causes a decline in purchasing power
ENDSTOPC the good becomes more expensive relative to all other products
ENDSTOPD the change in price causes an increase in purchasing power</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_4'>A the best risks are more likely to buy insurance
ENDSTOPB the best risks are less likely to buy insurance
ENDSTOPC those already insured will alter their behaviour
ENDSTOPD those not already insured will become more risk averse</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_5'>A income increases and the good is inferior
ENDSTOPB its price rises and demand is elastic
ENDSTOPC its price rises and demand is inelastic
ENDSTOPD income falls and the good is normal</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_6'>A It increases initially, then eventually decreases.
ENDSTOPB It is increasing.
ENDSTOPC It is decreasing.
ENDSTOPD It decreases initially, then eventually increases.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_7'>A There is freedom of entry and exit to the industry.
ENDSTOPB There are many firms supplying the market.
ENDSTOPC Firms can change their actions without influencing the behaviour of other
firms.
ENDSTOPD Each firm faces a horizontal demand curve.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_8'>A increase output and reduce price
ENDSTOPB reduce price and output
ENDSTOPC increase price and output
ENDSTOPD reduce output and increase price</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_9'>A each firm will not take account of its rival s reactions when making its
decision
ENDSTOPB the price set by one firm will not influence the price of the other firm
ENDSTOPC in avoiding the worst possible outcome the firms will fail to reach the best
possible outcome
ENDSTOPD in avoiding the worst possible outcome the firms will succeed in reaching the
best possible outcome</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_10'>A marginal cost equals price and price is above minimum average total cost
ENDSTOPB marginal cost equals average revenue
ENDSTOPC marginal cost equals marginal revenue
ENDSTOPD total revenue is maximised</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_11'>A average cost curve is discontinuous
ENDSTOPB marginal cost curve is discontinuous
ENDSTOPC marginal revenue curve is discontinuous
ENDSTOPD average revenue curve is discontinuous</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_12'>A When more labour is added to a given amount of capital, the marginal product
of labour remains unchanged.
ENDSTOPB When the ratio of labour to capital doubles, the output of the firm also
doubles.
ENDSTOPC When the input of both capital and labour doubles, output remains constant.
ENDSTOPD When the input of capital and labour doubles, output doubles.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_13'>A 30 units
ENDSTOPB 40 units
ENDSTOPC 50 units
ENDSTOPD 70 units</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_14'>A increase the wage rate
ENDSTOPB decrease the wage rate
ENDSTOPC increase the quantity of labour it hires
ENDSTOPD decrease the quantity of labour it hires</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_15'>A 0.33
ENDSTOPB 3
ENDSTOPC 30
ENDSTOPD 300</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_16'>A increasing absolute risk aversion
ENDSTOPB declining absolute risk aversion
ENDSTOPC constant absolute risk aversion
ENDSTOPD none of the above</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_17'>A supply of 6 units
ENDSTOPB demand of 6 units
ENDSTOPC supply of 12 units
ENDSTOPD demand of 12 units</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_18'>A 0.6
ENDSTOPB 1.4
ENDSTOPC 0.8
ENDSTOPD 1.7</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_19'>A the lower is the marginal propensity to consume and the lower is the marginal
propensity to import
ENDSTOPB the lower is the marginal propensity to consume and the higher is the marginal
propensity to import
ENDSTOPC the higher is the marginal propensity to consume and the lower is the marginal
propensity to import
ENDSTOPD the higher is the marginal propensity to consume and the higher is the
marginal propensity to import</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_20'>A A medium of exchange.
ENDSTOPB A store of value.
ENDSTOPC A unit of account.
ENDSTOPD A measure of liquidity.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_21'>A call in loans and reduce reserves
ENDSTOPB call in loans and increase reserves
ENDSTOPC make additional loans and reduce reserves
ENDSTOPD make additional loans and increase reserves</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_22'>A £3 billion
ENDSTOPB £4.5 billion
ENDSTOPC £300 billion
ENDSTOPD £450 billion</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_23'>A increases in a recession and falls in a boom
ENDSTOPB arises when the unemployed lack the skills needed by newly created jobs
ENDSTOPC arises when those seeking work give up hope of finding a job
ENDSTOPD occurs as the result of a transition from one job to another</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_24'>A domestic inflation rates are unavoidably linked across national boundaries
ENDSTOPB domestic inflation in one country can lead to inflation in another even if the
exchange rate moves to preserve purchasing power parity
ENDSTOPC domestic inflation is dictated outside the bounds that would have constrained
prices in a fixed rate regime
ENDSTOPD none of the above</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_25' formatted="false">A 4.0
ENDSTOPB 3.0
ENDSTOPC 1.2
ENDSTOPD 0.8</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_choices_26'>A deficit of £5 billion
ENDSTOPB surplus of £5 billion
ENDSTOPC deficit of £35 billion
ENDSTOPD surplus of £35 billion</string>"
</resources>