<resources>
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_1'>A natural resources, labour and money.
ENDSTOPB labour, money and factories.
ENDSTOPC natural resources, capital and factories.
ENDSTOPD natural resources, labour and capital.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_2'>A all resources will eventually be exhausted.
ENDSTOPB there are unlimited resources, we just have an allocation problem.
ENDSTOPC there are unlimited wants and limited resources.
ENDSTOPD all of the above.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_3'>A 150 units.
ENDSTOPB 125 units.
ENDSTOPC 75 units.
ENDSTOPD 50 units.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_4'>A a surplus of Good X and price will rise.
ENDSTOPB a shortage of Good X and price will fall.
ENDSTOPC a surplus of Good X and price will fall.
ENDSTOPD a shortage of Good X and price will rise.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_5'>A vertical.
ENDSTOPB horizontal.
ENDSTOPC upward sloping.
ENDSTOPD downward sloping.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_6'>A rise at an increasing rate as consumption of Good X increases.
ENDSTOPB rise at a decreasing rate as consumption of Good X increases.
ENDSTOPC fall at an increasing rate as consumption of Good X increases.
ENDSTOPD fall at a decreasing rate as consumption of Good X increases.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_7'>A having insurance makes an individual less careful.
ENDSTOPB having insurance makes an individual more careful.
ENDSTOPC the people taking out the insurance are those who have the highest risk.
ENDSTOPD the people taking out the insurance are those who have the highest risk
aversion.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_8'>A different consumer’s tastes but not different quality products.
ENDSTOPB same quality products.
ENDSTOPC different quality products reflecting different production costs.
ENDSTOPD different varieties offered at the same price.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_9'>A The short run average cost declines.
ENDSTOPB If inputs are doubled then output less than doubles.
ENDSTOPC An increase in the variable factor of production holding the fixed factor of
production constant leads to a higher increase in output.
ENDSTOPD The long run average cost curve declines.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_10'>A Marginal physical product is equal to total physical product divided by
average product.
ENDSTOPB Average physical product is always greater than marginal physical product.
ENDSTOPC Marginal physical product can never become negative.
ENDSTOPD Average physical product can never become negative.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_11'>A Reduce its output.
ENDSTOPB Raise its output.
ENDSTOPC Raise its price.
ENDSTOPD Reduce its price.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_12'>A the firm has to charge a price higher than the marginal cost of producing the
last unit.
ENDSTOPB any decision by the monopolist to sell an additional unit of output does not
affect price.
ENDSTOPC the firm has to reduce price on all units sold in order to sell an additional unit.
ENDSTOPD of the law of diminishing returns.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_13'>A equally by buyers and sellers.
ENDSTOPB more heavily by buyers.
ENDSTOPC more heavily by sellers.
ENDSTOPD by neither buyers nor sellers.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_14'>A lower the price and raise output.
ENDSTOPB maintain the existing price and output.
ENDSTOPC lower the price but maintain existing output.
ENDSTOPD maintain the existing price and raise output.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_15'>A average physical product falls.
ENDSTOPB average physical product rises.
ENDSTOPC marginal physical product falls.
ENDSTOPD marginal physical product rises.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_16'>A The effect on price is indeterminate but quantity will fall.
ENDSTOPB The effect on price is indeterminate but quantity will rise.
ENDSTOPC The effect on quantity is indeterminate but price will fall.
ENDSTOPD The effect on quantity is indeterminate but price will rise.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_17'>A Country Y has a comparative advantage in the production of Good A.
ENDSTOPB Country X has an absolute advantage in the production of Good B.
ENDSTOPC Country X has an absolute advantage in the production of Good A.
ENDSTOPD Country Y has a comparative advantage in the production of Good B.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_18'>A increases in a recession and falls in a boom.
ENDSTOPB arises when the unemployed lack the skills needed by newly created jobs.
ENDSTOPC arises when those seeking work give up hope of finding a job.
ENDSTOPD occurs as the result of a transition from one job to another.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_19'>A An increase in short run aggregate supply.
ENDSTOPB A decrease in short run aggregate supply.
ENDSTOPC An increase in aggregate demand.
ENDSTOPD A decrease in aggregate demand.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_20'>A The demand for money is negatively related to the interest rate.
ENDSTOPB The demand for money is positively related to the level of national income.
ENDSTOPC The demand for money is negatively related to the price level.
ENDSTOPD The demand for money can be divided into speculative, precautionary and
transactions motives.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_21'>A Increased government expenditure on domestically produced goods.
ENDSTOPB Increased money supply.
ENDSTOPC Reduced corporate and personal taxation.
ENDSTOPD A privatisation programme.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_22'>A an increase in aggregate demand and a reduction in real output.
ENDSTOPB an increase in aggregate demand and an increase in real output.
ENDSTOPC a reduction in aggregate demand and a reduction in real output.
ENDSTOPD a reduction in aggregate demand and an increase in real output.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_23'>A decrease and the domestic money supply will rise.
ENDSTOPB decrease and the domestic money supply will fall.
ENDSTOPC increase and the domestic money supply will rise.
ENDSTOPD increase and the domestic money supply will fall.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_24'>A 8%
ENDSTOPB 11.1%
ENDSTOPC 12.5%
ENDSTOPD 44%</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_25'>A An increase in the money supply.
ENDSTOPB An increase in capital investment expenditure.
ENDSTOPC An increase in education expenditure.
ENDSTOPD An increase in research and development expenditure.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2012_choices_26'>A lenders will gain at the expense of borrowers and employers will gain at the
expense of workers.
ENDSTOPB borrowers will gain at the expense of lenders and employers will gain at the
expense of workers.
ENDSTOPC borrowers will gain at the expense of lenders and workers will gain at the
expense of employers.
ENDSTOPD lenders will gain at the expense of borrowers and workers will gain at the
expense of employers.</string>"

</resources>