<resources>
    "<string name='apr2015_que_1' formatted="false">A company makes economic profits of 10%. The risk premium for the company’s
line of business is 5%. If the banks offer a rate of interest on savings accounts of 3%,
the opportunity cost to the owners of the company is:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_que_2'>Good X is an inferior good. A rise in consumer income when the supply curve for
Good X is positively sloped will cause which one of the following?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_que_3'>What is the combined effect of a decrease in the cost of production and a rise in
consumer income on the equilibrium price and quantity of a normal good?</string>"
    <string name='apr2015_que_4'>Under perfect competition:</string>
    "<string name='apr2015_que_5'>If the income elasticity of demand for Good X is 2, a rise in all consumers’ disposable
incomes from £50 million to £52 million will increase the quantity demanded of Good
X by:</string>"
    <string name='apr2015_que_6'>An example of a conglomerate takeover is a supermarket:</string>
    "<string name='apr2015_que_7'>If, due to pollution concerns, consumers switch from travelling to work by car to
travelling by public transport, the resulting unemployment in the car industry is:</string>"
    <string name='apr2015_que_8'>Which of the following statements regarding the productivity of labour is correct?</string>
    <string name='apr2015_que_9'>The short run supply curve for a firm in a perfectly competitive industry is its:</string>
    <string name='apr2015_que_10'>Which one of the following statements about market structure is TRUE?</string>
    "<string name='apr2015_que_11'>Which of the following is NOT a prediction of the theory of monopolistic
competition?</string>"
    <string name='apr2015_que_12'>A necessary condition for a firm being able to engage in price discrimination is that:</string>
    <string name='apr2015_que_13'>In the circular flow of income model:</string>
    <string name='apr2015_que_14'>If a country has a positive balance of net income from abroad then:</string>
    "<string name='apr2015_que_15'>To obtain a measure of Net National Income from Gross Domestic Product it is
necessary to:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_que_16'>If private savings exceed private investment by £300 million and government
expenditure on goods and services exceeds government tax revenue by £200 million
then net exports will be:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_que_17'>You are given the following information for an economy:
Consumer Expenditure £80 million
Investment Expenditure £20 million
Government Expenditure £40 million
Exports £20 million
Imports £30 million
Net Income from abroad £10 million
What is the value of this economy’s Gross Domestic Product?</string>"
    <string name='apr2015_que_18'>Which one of the following is NOT likely to lead to cost push inflation?</string>
    "<string name='apr2015_que_19'>If a country experiences high domestic inflation compared to its trading partners with
a fixed exchange rate then the effect of the inflation will be to:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_que_20'>Which of the following would constitute a supply side economic policy for reducing
unemployment?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_que_21'>Consider an economy where the demand for real money balances is interest elastic
and the demand for investment is interest inelastic. A change in the money supply
will result in a relatively:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_que_22'>The overall money multiplier effect might be smaller than the full bank deposits
multiplier because:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_que_23'>The following data on an economy is provided for 2005 and 2013: According to the equation of exchange, what would be the value of the price level in
2013 assuming that the velocity of circulation remains unchanged?</string>"
    <string name='apr2015_que_24'>In the model of the circular flow of income if injections are greater than withdrawals:</string>
    "<string name='apr2015_que_25'>The introduction of a restrictive monetary policy in an open economy operating with a
flexible exchange rate would most likely lead to:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_que_26'>The “Taylor Rule” attempts to take which of the following two macroeconomic
objectives into account?</string>"


</resources>