<resources>
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_1'>A Primary Production
ENDSTOPB Secondary Production
ENDSTOPC Tertiary Production
ENDSTOPD Manufacturing Production</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_2'>A 8 units of Good X.
ENDSTOPB 10 units of Good X.
ENDSTOPC 2 units of Good X.
ENDSTOPD 1.25 units of Good X.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_3'>A its price decreases.
ENDSTOPB the price of a substitute rises.
ENDSTOPC the price of a complement rises.
ENDSTOPD consumers’ incomes fall.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_4'>A The quantity that producers would like to sell annually.
ENDSTOPB The quantity that producers are willing and able to sell at each income over the
next year.
ENDSTOPC The quantity that producers are willing and able to produce over the next year.
ENDSTOPD The quantity that producers are willing and able to sell at each price annually.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_5'>A an excess supply of Good X.
ENDSTOPB an excess demand for Good X.
ENDSTOPC no tendency for the market price of Good X to change.
ENDSTOPD an upward pressure on the price of Good X.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_6'>A The average cost for 11 units is greater than that for 10 units.
ENDSTOPB The total fixed costs for 11 units are £165.
ENDSTOPC The average fixed cost for 11 units is the same as the marginal cost of the 11th
unit.
ENDSTOPD The average fixed cost for 11 units is less than the marginal cost of the 11th
unit.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_7'>A no change in price and a surplus.
ENDSTOPB no change in price and a shortage.
ENDSTOPC a fall in price and a fall in the quantity sold.
ENDSTOPD a fall in price and a rise in the quantity sold.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_8'>A marginal cost of production.
ENDSTOPB marginal benefit to consumers.
ENDSTOPC average revenue of the monopolist.
ENDSTOPD average cost of the monopolist.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_9'>A positive.
ENDSTOPB above its average physical product.
ENDSTOPC negative.
ENDSTOPD falling.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_10'>A A firm charges customers different prices according to how much they
purchase.
ENDSTOPB Consumers are grouped into independent markets and a separate price is
charged in each market.
ENDSTOPC A firm charges each customer the maximum price he/she is prepared to pay.
ENDSTOPD Different firms charge different prices for the same product.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_11'>A Strategy 1
ENDSTOPB Strategy 2
ENDSTOPC Strategy 3
ENDSTOPD Strategy 4</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_12'>A not run the extra flight as it will expect to lose £4,500 from its profits.
ENDSTOPB not run the extra flight as its expected profit of £500 is insufficient to cover its
fixed costs.
ENDSTOPC run the extra flight as it will add £500 to its profits or reduce losses by £500.
ENDSTOPD run the extra flight as the expected revenue of £5,500 is more than its fixed
costs.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_13'>A Demand for Good X is price elastic.
ENDSTOPB A cut in the price of Good X will increase revenue for a firm producing
Good X.
ENDSTOPC Good X is a luxury good.
ENDSTOPD Good X is an inferior good.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_14'>A £200 million
ENDSTOPB £312.5 million
ENDSTOPC £1,000 million
ENDSTOPD £800 million</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_15'>A A decrease in trade union powers.
ENDSTOPB An appreciation of the domestic currency\'s exchange rate.
ENDSTOPC A fall in labour productivity.
ENDSTOPD A decrease in the profit margins applied by firms.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_16'>A lower short term interest rates because the aggregate demand curve shifts to
the left.
ENDSTOPB raise short term interest rates because the aggregate demand curve shifts to the
left.
ENDSTOPC lower short term interest rates because the aggregate demand curve shifts to
the right.
ENDSTOPD raise short term interest rates because the aggregate demand curve shifts to the
right.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_17'>A fall and real output will rise.
ENDSTOPB fall and real output will fall.
ENDSTOPC rise and real output will rise.
ENDSTOPD rise and real output will fall.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_18'>A The US dollar appreciates and the Chinese renminbi depreciates.
ENDSTOPB The US dollar depreciates and the Chinese renminbi depreciates.
ENDSTOPC The US dollar appreciates and the Chinese renminbi appreciates.
ENDSTOPD The US dollar depreciates and the Chinese renminbi appreciates.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_19'>A (i) increase, (ii) decrease
ENDSTOPB (i) increase, (ii) increase
ENDSTOPC (i) decrease, (ii) increase
ENDSTOPD (i) decrease, (ii) decrease</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_20'>A national income falls.
ENDSTOPB national income rises.
ENDSTOPC governments decrease the personal income tax rate.
ENDSTOPD government expenditure increases.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_21'>A frictional unemployment and structural unemployment.
ENDSTOPB regional unemployment and seasonal unemployment.
ENDSTOPC structural unemployment and regional unemployment.
ENDSTOPD frictional unemployment and seasonal unemployment.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_22'>A an expansionary fiscal policy.
ENDSTOPB an expansionary monetary policy.
ENDSTOPC a contractionary fiscal policy.
ENDSTOPD a contractionary monetary policy.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_23'>A velocity of circulation decreases.
ENDSTOPB real national income increases.
ENDSTOPC velocity of circulation and nominal national income are constant.
ENDSTOPD velocity of circulation and the real national income are constant.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_24'>A reduce the domestic price of the imported good.
ENDSTOPB increase domestic consumption of the imported good.
ENDSTOPC increase domestic production of the imported good.
ENDSTOPD increase the quantity imported of the good.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_25'>A buy the euro in the foreign exchange market and increase its foreign exchange
reserves.
ENDSTOPB buy the euro in the foreign exchange market and decrease its foreign exchange
reserves.
ENDSTOPC sell the euro in the foreign exchange market and increase its foreign exchange
reserves.
ENDSTOPD sell the euro in the foreign exchange market and decrease its foreign exchange
reserves.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_choices_26'>A A fall in the price of its imports combined with a rise in the price of its
exports.
ENDSTOPB A fall in the price of its imports combined with a fall in the price of its exports.
ENDSTOPC A rise in the price of its imports combined with a rise in the price of its
exports.
ENDSTOPD A rise in the price of its imports combined with a fall in the price of its
exports.</string>"


</resources>