<resources>
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_1'>A 5%.
ENDSTOPB 7%.
ENDSTOPC 8%.
ENDSTOPD 10%.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_2'>A The demand for Good X to fall and the price of Good X to fall.
ENDSTOPB The demand for Good X to fall and the price of Good X to rise.
ENDSTOPC The demand for Good X to rise and the price of Good X to fall.
ENDSTOPD The demand for Good X to rise and the price of Good X to rise.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_3'>A The effect on price is indeterminate but quantity will fall.
ENDSTOPB The effect on price is indeterminate but quantity will rise.
ENDSTOPC The effect on quantity is indeterminate but price will rise.
ENDSTOPD The effect on quantity is indeterminate but price will fall.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_4'>A short run excess profits are competed away by firms leaving the industry.
ENDSTOPB short run excess profits are competed away by new firms entering the industry.
ENDSTOPC short run excess profits lead to price rises.
ENDSTOPD short run excess profits are caused by barriers to entry and exit.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_5'>A 2%.
ENDSTOPB 4%.
ENDSTOPC 6%.
ENDSTOPD 8%.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_6'>A buying a large farm.
ENDSTOPB buying another supermarket.
ENDSTOPC setting up a number of new smaller outlets.
ENDSTOPD buying a car rental business.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_7'>A frictional unemployment.
ENDSTOPB seasonal unemployment.
ENDSTOPC structural unemployment.
ENDSTOPD technical unemployment.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_8'>A Average physical product is maximised when average physical product equals
marginal physical product.
ENDSTOPB Average physical product is maximised when marginal physical product is
maximised.
ENDSTOPC Marginal physical product increases when average physical product is above
marginal physical product.
ENDSTOPD Average physical product increases when marginal physical product is below
average physical product.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_9'>A average cost curve.
ENDSTOPB average variable cost curve.
ENDSTOPC marginal cost curve above the lowest point of the average variable cost curve.
ENDSTOPD marginal cost curve above the lowest point of the average total cost curve.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_10'>A Perfect competition is distinguished from all other market structures because
of the assumption of no barriers to entry/exit from the industry.
ENDSTOPB Firms under monopolistic competition face horizontal demand curves for their
products.
ENDSTOPC A monopoly will find that its average revenue is always greater than its
average costs.
ENDSTOPD Under perfect competition, in the long run, each firm will find that its
marginal cost is equal to its average cost of production.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_11'>A When the monopolistically competitive industry achieves a long-run
equilibrium, price is greater than marginal cost.
ENDSTOPB Monopolistically competitive firms offer differentiated products and face a
downward sloping demand curve.
ENDSTOPC Under monopolistic competition, the price charged to the consumer is equal to
the average revenue of the firm.
ENDSTOPD Monopolistically competitive firms can earn supernormal profits in the long
run.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_12'>A it faces a perfectly elastic demand curve.
ENDSTOPB consumers of its product are willing and able to resell their purchase.
ENDSTOPC it faces a downward sloping demand curve.
ENDSTOPD it is a price taker.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_13'>A savings, taxes and investment are withdrawals.
ENDSTOPB savings, imports and taxes are withdrawals.
ENDSTOPC investment, government expenditure and imports are injections.
ENDSTOPD investment, exports and consumption are injections.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_14'>A Gross Domestic Product is greater than Gross National Income.
ENDSTOPB Gross Domestic Product is less than Gross National Income.
ENDSTOPC Gross Domestic Product is the same as Gross National Income.
ENDSTOPD We cannot say whether Gross Domestic Product differs from Gross National
Income from this information.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_15'>A add net income from abroad and deduct transfer payments.
ENDSTOPB deduct net income from abroad and add capital depreciation.
ENDSTOPC add net income from abroad.
ENDSTOPD add net income from abroad and deduct capital depreciation.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_16'>A zero.
ENDSTOPB £100 million.
ENDSTOPC £100 million.
ENDSTOPD £500 million.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_17'>A £130 million
ENDSTOPB £140 million
ENDSTOPC £150 million
ENDSTOPD £160 million</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_18'>A An increase in trade union powers.
ENDSTOPB An appreciation of the domestic currency’s exchange rate.
ENDSTOPC An increased budget deficit which causes interest rates to rise.
ENDSTOPD An increase in the profit margins applied by firms.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_19'>A decrease the country’s imports.
ENDSTOPB increase the country’s exports.
ENDSTOPC shift the country’s currency supply curve in the foreign exchange market to the
right requiring central bank purchases of the domestic currency to maintain the
fixed exchange rate.
ENDSTOPD shift the demand curve for the country’s foreign exchange to the right
requiring central bank purchases of the domestic currency to maintain the
fixed exchange rate.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_20'>A increasing social security benefits
ENDSTOPB increasing the money supply
ENDSTOPC reducing corporate and personal taxation
ENDSTOPD increasing government expenditure aimed at exploiting the multiplier effect</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_21'>A small change in the rate of interest and the level of investment.
ENDSTOPB large change in the rate of interest and the level of investment.
ENDSTOPC small change in the rate of interest and a relatively large change in the level of
investment.
ENDSTOPD large change in the rate of interest and a relatively small change in the level of
investment.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_22'>A governments are pursuing an expansionary monetary policy.
ENDSTOPB high rates of interest are discouraging borrowing.
ENDSTOPC banks are not holding excess cash reserves.
ENDSTOPD all proceeds of loans are re-deposited with banks.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_23'>A 50
ENDSTOPB 15
ENDSTOPC 10
ENDSTOPD none of the above</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_24'>A national income will tend to increase.
ENDSTOPB national income will tend to decrease.
ENDSTOPC unemployment and production will tend to fall.
ENDSTOPD the general level of prices will tend to fall.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_25'>A higher domestic interest rates and an exchange rate appreciation.
ENDSTOPB higher domestic interest rates and an exchange rate depreciation.
ENDSTOPC lower domestic interest rates and an exchange rate appreciation.
ENDSTOPD lower domestic interest rates and an exchange rate depreciation.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2015_choices_26'>A inflation and the exchange rate
ENDSTOPB economic growth and unemployment
ENDSTOPC inflation and economic growth
ENDSTOPD unemployment and the exchange rate</string>"

</resources>