<resources>"<string name='apr2005_que_1'>If Goods X and Y are substitutes, a reduction in the price of Good X will have the
following effect on the demand for Good Y:</string>"
    <string name='apr2005_que_2'>When there is a surplus of a good or service:</string>
    "<string name='apr2005_que_3'>The substitution effect of a price decrease causes an individual to purchase more units
of a normal good because:</string>"
    <string name='apr2005_que_4'>The problem of adverse selection means that, as insurance premiums rise:</string>
    <string name='apr2005_que_5'>Revenues from the sale of a good will increase if:</string>
    <string name='apr2005_que_6'>When marginal product is decreasing, which of the following is true of marginal cost?</string>
    <string name='apr2005_que_7'>Which of the following is NOT a feature of monopolistic competition?</string>
    "<string name='apr2005_que_8'>A profit maximising monopolist is currently operating at a level of output where
marginal revenue is £20 and marginal cost is £12. In order to increase profits the
monopolist should:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_que_9'>The prisoner s dilemma, applied to a situation involving two oligopolists, illustrates
that:</string>"
    <string name='apr2005_que_10'>A perfectly competitive firm is not maximising profit if:</string>
    "<string name='apr2005_que_11'>According to the kinked demand curve theory of oligopoly, at the quantity
corresponding to the kink the firm s:</string>"
    <string name='apr2005_que_12'>Which of the following reveals constant returns to scale?</string>
    "<string name='apr2005_que_13'>A firm with fixed costs of £100 per week and a constant average variable cost of £3
per unit of output has the following information about its weekly sales: Which level of output gives the highest profit?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_que_14'>Assume a profit-maximising firm hires labour in a competitive labour market. If the
marginal revenue product of labour is greater than the wage, the firm should:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_que_15'>With 50 units of labour a firm can produce 1,800 units of output. With 60 units of
labour the firm can produce 2,100 units of output. The marginal product of labour is:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_que_16'>Consider the certainty equivalent of a fair gamble. If the absolute value of the
certainty equivalent decreases with increasing wealth, the investor is said to exhibit:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_que_17'>Assume the demand equation for a good is Qd = 20 P and the supply equation is
Qs = 6 + 1.5P. If the price is set equal to 2.4 above the equilibrium level then there
will be an excess:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_que_18'>If a household s disposable income increases from £10,000 to £15,000 and its
consumption expenditure increases from £8,000 to £11,000 then the marginal
propensity to consume is:</string>"
    <string name='apr2005_que_19'>The multiplier is higher:</string>
    <string name='apr2005_que_20'>Which one of the following is NOT a function of money?</string>
    "<string name='apr2005_que_21'>Whenever a commercial bank s desired reserve ratio exceeds its actual reserve ratio
the bank will:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_que_22'>Suppose that in 2003 the nominal gross domestic product of Country A was £450
billion and the price index was 150. If the price index was 100 in 1996 what is the
real gross domestic product of Country A in 2003 measured in terms of 1996 prices?</string>"
    <string name='apr2005_que_23'>Structural unemployment is unemployment that:</string>
    <string name='apr2005_que_24'>Under floating exchange rates:</string>
    "<string name='apr2005_que_25'>Consider an economy in which the average price level is 1.8, real GDP is £260 billion
and the nominal money supply is £117 billion. The velocity of circulation is:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2005_que_26'>In Country A the level of government expenditure is £275 billion, tax revenue is £310
billion, aggregate investment is £180 billion and aggregate savings is £150 billion.
The level of net exports in Country A is:</string>"
</resources>