<resources>
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_1'>A the marginal tax rate is negative.
ENDSTOPB the marginal tax rate is equal to the average tax rate.
ENDSTOPC the marginal tax rate is greater than the average tax rate.
ENDSTOPD the marginal tax rate is zero.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_2'>A the quantity of both goods produced is equal.
ENDSTOPB it is possible to produce more of only one good.
ENDSTOPC it is possible to produce more of one good only by sacrificing some production
of the other good.
ENDSTOPD it is possible to produce more of both goods.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_3'>A A change in consumer tastes may lead to a shift in a demand curve.
ENDSTOPB A rise in the price of other goods may lead to a shift in a demand curve.
ENDSTOPC A change in the resources required to produce a good may lead to a shift in a
demand curve.
ENDSTOPD A fall in the price of other goods may lead to a shift in a demand curve.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_4'>A Q = 150 – 3P
ENDSTOPB Q = 350 – 3P
ENDSTOPC Q = 250 – 3P
ENDSTOPD Q = 200 – 3P</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_5'>A 5
ENDSTOPB 2
ENDSTOPC 3.33
ENDSTOPD 0.33</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_6'>A An inferior good is one for which income elasticity of demand is perfectly
inelastic, so that quantity demanded falls as income increases.
ENDSTOPB An inferior good is one for which income elasticity of demand is positive, so
that quantity demanded increases as income increases.
ENDSTOPC An inferior good is one for which income elasticity of demand is negative, so
that quantity demanded falls as income increases.
ENDSTOPD An inferior good is one for which income elasticity of demand is zero, so that
quantity demanded is invariant to income changes.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_7'>A marginal costs will be unaffected.
ENDSTOPB marginal costs will rise by more than the decrease in fixed costs.
ENDSTOPC marginal costs will fall by more than the decrease in fixed costs.
ENDSTOPD marginal costs will fall by the same amount as the decrease in fixed costs.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_8'>A the demand for its product is zero.
ENDSTOPB the demand for its product is elastic.
ENDSTOPC the demand for its product is inelastic.
ENDSTOPD the demand for its product is no more than 1.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_9'>A the amount of capital employed is rising.
ENDSTOPB the amount of capital is the same as the price per unit.
ENDSTOPC the amount of capital employed is optimal.
ENDSTOPD the amount of capital employed starts decreasing at an increasing rate.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_10'>A decreasing returns to scale
ENDSTOPB constant returns to scale
ENDSTOPC increasing returns to scale
ENDSTOPD the law of increasing marginal returns</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_11'>A average costs exceed average revenue.
ENDSTOPB it can no longer cover its fixed costs.
ENDSTOPC it can no longer cover its variable costs.
ENDSTOPD expanding output narrows the gap between marginal revenue and marginal
cost.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_12'>A Greater than 100 but less than 200
ENDSTOPB Greater than 200 but less than 300
ENDSTOPC Greater than 300 but less than 400
ENDSTOPD Greater than 400 but less than 500</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_13'>A Profit is maximised where MC = MR.
ENDSTOPB The firm faces a downward sloping demand curve for normal goods.ENDSTOPC = MR.
B The firm faces a downward sloping demand curve for normal goods.
C The firm can set price or quantity, but not both.
ENDSTOPD Supernormal profits are experienced in the long run.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_14'>A by sector
ENDSTOPB by economic category
ENDSTOPC by listed firm
ENDSTOPD by department</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_15'>A Public Sector Borrowing Requirement of £440m.
ENDSTOPB Public Sector Borrowing Requirement of £370m.
ENDSTOPC Public Sector Debt Repayment of £440m.
ENDSTOPD Public Sector Debt Repayment of £510m.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_16'>A inflationary motive
ENDSTOPB precautionary motive
ENDSTOPC transactions motive
ENDSTOPD asset motive</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_17'>A Taxes, investment and consumption are leakages.
ENDSTOPB Imports, exports and savings are injections.
ENDSTOPC Exports, investment and savings are injections.
ENDSTOPD Savings, imports and taxation are leakages.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_18'>A £80m
ENDSTOPB £20m
ENDSTOPC –£60m
ENDSTOPD £100m</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_19'>A 0.4
ENDSTOPB 0.6
ENDSTOPC 1.4
ENDSTOPD 1.6</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_20'>A 0.25
ENDSTOPB 0.02
ENDSTOPC 0.2
ENDSTOPD 0.1</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_21'>A infinitely elastic at the long run equilibrium level of output.
ENDSTOPB inelastic at the long run equilibrium level of output.
ENDSTOPC infinitely elastic at some point below the long run equilibrium level of output.
ENDSTOPD upward sloping with decreasing elasticity.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_22'>A taxation
ENDSTOPB printing money
ENDSTOPC sale of public assets
ENDSTOPD borrowing</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_23'>A 2
ENDSTOPB 1
ENDSTOPC 8
ENDSTOPD 4</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_24'>A It lowers prices through increased competition.
ENDSTOPB It allows the world’s resources to be used in a more economically efficient
way.
ENDSTOPC It increases the range of goods and services available to consumers.
ENDSTOPD It spreads the benefits of economic growth more evenly across countries.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_25'>A import elasticity is less than 1.
ENDSTOPB sum of the import and export elasticities is less negative than –1.
ENDSTOPC sum of the import and export elasticities is more negative than –1.
ENDSTOPD export elasticity is less negative than –1.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2008_choices_26'>A a moving average of monthly prices.
ENDSTOPB the percentage growth in prices between the month in question and one year
ago.
ENDSTOPC prices over a few days in the middle of the previous month.
ENDSTOPD the expected growth in prices between the first day of the current month and
the first day of the next month.</string>"

</resources>