<resources>
    <string name='apr2014_que_1'>Which of the following would the production of banking services be classified as?</string>
    "<string name='apr2014_que_2'>If an economy moves from producing 10 units of Good X and 5 units of Good Y to
producing 8 units of Good X and 6 units of Good Y, the opportunity cost of the 6th
unit of Good Y is:</string>"
    <string name='apr2014_que_3'>The demand curve for Good X, which is a normal good, will shift to the right if:</string>
    <string name='apr2014_que_4'>Which of the following best describes an annual supply curve?</string>
    "<string name='apr2014_que_5'>If a maximum price for Good X is fixed above the market equilibrium price there will
be:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_que_6'>A firm’s total costs are £150 when 10 units are produced and the marginal cost of the
10th unit is £40. The marginal cost of the 11th unit is £15. Which of the following is
TRUE?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_que_7'>A maximum price is set for Good X at £30 which happens to coincide with the free
market price. A downward shift in the supply of Good X keeping the maximum price
fixed at £30 will lead to:</string>"
    <string name='apr2014_que_8'>A welfare loss occurs in a monopoly industry because the price is greater than the:</string>
    "<string name='apr2014_que_9'>The total output and the average physical product of the variable factor of production
both always increase as long as the marginal physical product of the variable factor is:</string>"
    <string name='apr2014_que_10'>Second degree price discrimination refers to a situation where:</string>
    "<string name='apr2014_que_11'>The profit payoffs to Firm X from combining the various strategies of X (1,2,3,4) and
the presumed response of the other firm (S,P,Q,R) in a duopoly industry is given
below: Which one of the following represents the maximin strategy of Firm X?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_que_12'>Global Airways, which is a profit maximising firm, has to decide whether or not to
run an extra daily flight between London and Edinburgh. The total daily fixed costs
of the airline are £4,000, the total variable costs of the extra flight are £5,000 and the
expected revenue from the extra flight is £5,500. In such circumstances Global
Airways will:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_que_13'>If the own price elasticity of demand for Good X is −0.8 and the income elasticity of
Good X is −0.3, which of the following is correct?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_que_14'>In a simple closed economy, consumption is given by the relationship
C = 0.75 Y
where C is consumption expenditure and Y is Gross Domestic Product.
If government expenditure is £150 million and investment is £50 million, what will be
the equilibrium value of the Gross Domestic Product of the economy?</string>"
    <string name='apr2014_que_15'>Which one of the following is likely to lead to cost push inflation?</string>
    <string name='apr2014_que_16'>Other things remaining the same, the effect of an increase in the budget deficit is to:</string>
    "<string name='apr2014_que_17'>Assume that the actual rate of unemployment is above the natural rate of
unemployment because the expected rate of inflation is above the actual rate of
inflation. If the expected rate of inflation falls to equal the actual rate of inflation then
real wage growth will:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_que_18'>The US has been running a large current account deficit, and China has a large current
account surplus. If their exchange rates were both flexible, how would such
imbalances be eliminated?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_que_19'>Which of the following are the correct responses for the missing words (i) and (ii) in
the following statement?
Automatic stabilisers act to ___(i) ___ government expenditures and
___(ii)___ government revenues during an expansionary period.</string>"
    <string name='apr2014_que_20'>The budget deficit tends to decrease when:</string>
    <string name='apr2014_que_21'>The equilibrium level of unemployment in an economy is the sum of:</string>
    "<string name='apr2014_que_22'>As a result of an economic policy change, interest rates and consumption rise but
investment falls. The new policy was:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_que_23'>According to the equation of exchange an increase in the money supply is most likely
to lead to inflation if the:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_que_24'>For a small open economy the imposition of a tariff on its imports of a good will
normally:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_que_25'>To prevent the value of the euro from depreciating against the US dollar, the
European Central Bank might:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2014_que_26'>Which one of the following will result in an improvement in a country’s terms of
trade?</string>"



</resources>