<resources><string name='apr2006_que_1'>If demand increases and supply decreases then the:</string>
    "<string name='apr2006_que_2'>Flour is an essential input in the production of bread. An increase in the price of flour
would have an impact on the demand and supply of bread by:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_que_3'>In the diagram below points X and Y represent the equilibrium price and quantity
traded of a good in two successive time periods. Which of the following is NOT a possible explanation?</string>"
    <string name='apr2006_que_4'>A price floor set above the market equilibrium price is likely to cause:</string>
    <string name='apr2006_que_5'>If cross elasticity of demand is negative between Goods X and Y then:</string>
    <string name='apr2006_que_6'>Total Revenue from the sale of a Good will decrease if:</string>
    "<string name='apr2006_que_7'>Which of the following would result from the removal of a specific tax of £5 per unit
on sales of Good X which has a price elasticity of demand of 2?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_que_8'>According to the law of diminishing marginal utility the total satisfaction that a
consumer receives from consuming Good X will:</string>"
    <string name='apr2006_que_9'>In relation to insurance the term moral hazard:</string>
    <string name='apr2006_que_10'>A profit maximising firm will produce output where:</string>
    "<string name='apr2006_que_11'>Assume two countries with the same level of technology and resources do not
presently trade. In country X one unit of labour and one unit of capital can produce
5 bicycles or 2 cars. In country Y one unit of labour and one unit of capital can
produce 6 bicycles or 4 cars. Which of the following statements is FALSE?</string>"
    <string name='apr2006_que_12'>Which of the following is NOT a characteristic of perfect competition?</string>
    "<string name='apr2006_que_13'>As a result of an improvement in productivity a profit maximising monopolist is
currently operating at a level of output where marginal revenue is greater than
marginal cost. The monopolist should:</string>"
    <string name='apr2006_que_14'>In the short run a rise in the fixed costs of production for a monopolist causes:</string>
    <string name='apr2006_que_15'>The kinked demand curve model of oligopoly:</string>
    "<string name='apr2006_que_16'>In a country with a rising population nominal Gross Domestic Product (GDP)
increases at a rate of 3% per annum while the GDP deflator increases at 2% per
annum. Which of the following MUST be true?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_que_17'>To obtain a measure of Net National Product from Gross National Product it is
necessary to:</string>"
    <string name='apr2006_que_18'>An explanation of risk aversion is that:</string>
    <string name='apr2006_que_19'>Which of the following is a potential source of demand-pull inflation?</string>
    <string name='apr2006_que_20'>Which of the following is NOT associated with Keynesian economics?</string>
    "<string name='apr2006_que_21'>If a household s disposable income increases from £15,000 to £20,000 and its
consumption expenditure increases from £10,000 to £12,000 then the marginal
propensity to consume is:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_que_22'>Following an increase in the price of fuel there is a 20% increase in the price of air
travel tickets which results in a 10% decrease in total revenue. How would you
describe the demand for air travel?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_que_23'>If the money supply decreases due to a contractionary open market operation by the
central bank then the price of treasury bills will:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_que_24'>According to Keynesian analysis the adoption of an expansionary fiscal policy will
result in:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_que_25'>A country with a population of 25 million has 20 million in employment and 1 million
unemployed. What is the unemployment rate?</string>"
    <string name='apr2006_que_26'>A country is running a current account deficit. In relation to the rest of the world it is:</string>
</resources>