<resources>
    "<string name='apr2021_que_1'>If an 8% rise in the price of Good X results in a 4% fall in the quantity demanded of
Good Y, then the cross elasticity of demand for Good Y is approximately:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_que_2'>A production possibility frontier illustrates the limits on output of finished goods, as
imposed by a limited supply of productive inputs. On the axes of the production
possibility frontier, we place the:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_que_3'>For a profit maximising firm, fixed costs are £20, and the firm’s normal profit is £10.
The marginal costs of production are shown in the table below. The firm faces a
horizontal demand curve when the price is £50. How much supernormal profit does
the firm make?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_que_4'>A firm’s decision to reduce its expenditure on advertising is most likely to have the
following impact on its demand curve:</string>"
    <string name='apr2021_que_5'>In an industry characterised by perfect competition:</string>
    "<string name='apr2021_que_6'>Water is generally cheaper than diamonds when consumers are in equilibrium because
the:</string>"
    <string name='apr2021_que_7'>Which of the following features is NOT a typical characteristic of oligopoly?</string>
    "<string name='apr2021_que_8'>A monopoly firm faces a linear demand schedule, has positive but constant marginal
costs and is currently producing where its marginal cost is below its marginal revenue.
If the firm wishes to maximise profits then it should:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_que_9'>In the Cournot model of duopoly, when the two firms are at the equilibrium level of
output:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_que_10'>Two firms operate in a duopoly but do not collude. Given the profit pay-off matrix of
output options to firms A and B below, what is the dominant strategy for the firms? Note: Profit pay-offs are (Profit A, Profit B) and ‘high’ and ‘low’ refer to the output
decision.</string>"
    <string name='apr2021_que_11'>Which one of the following reveals decreasing returns to scale?</string>
    "<string name='apr2021_que_12'>Good X has a price elasticity of demand of –1. Which of the following statements is
TRUE, following the removal of a £10 per unit sales tax on Good X?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_que_13'>Other things being equal, a fall in a monopolist’s fixed costs of production, which
does not lead to new entrants, causes:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_que_14'>Which one of the following is NOT a ‘crowding out’ effect resulting from a fiscal
expansion?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_que_15'>If the money supply decreases due to a contractionary open market operation by the
central bank, then the price of Treasury bills will:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_que_16'>If the rate of income tax is cut from 30% to 25% while the marginal propensity to
import falls from 20% to 15%, the effect on the open economy fiscal multiplier will
be:</string>"
    <string name='apr2021_que_17'>The Phillips curve shows:</string>
    <string name='apr2021_que_18'>An increase in the money supply will have a stronger impact on real output the more:</string>
    "<string name='apr2021_que_19'>If both government spending and the money supply are increased, and the economy
has a high degree of unemployment, then:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_que_20'>The ‘crowding out’ effect associated with an increase in government borrowing could
be reduced or eliminated by an accommodating increase in:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_que_21'>Which of the following costs of inflation occurs because of the possibility of
unanticipated extra-high inflation?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_que_22'>A short-run fall in real Gross Domestic Product (GDP) would result from an increase
in all of the following with the exception of:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_que_23'>An unexpected increase in the price level, which causes a temporary reduction in the
real wage rate, may:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_que_24'>The nominal rate of interest is 7% and the expected rate of inflation is 4%. Which one
of the following is TRUE?</string>"
    <string name='apr2021_que_25'>Which of the following statements about the demand for money is FALSE?</string>
    "<string name='apr2021_que_26'>Other things being equal, if there is an unexpected fall in money supply, there is no
change in the expected rate of inflation and the unemployment rate is above the
natural rate of unemployment, then the long-run Phillips curve would suggest that the
inflation rate will eventually:</string>"


</resources>