<resources>
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_1'>A a choice between the production of consumer goods and the sacrifice of alternatives.
ENDSTOPB the establishment of freedom of entry and exit.
ENDSTOPC the establishment of a system of market prices.
ENDSTOPD a decision to be made on the degree to which capital will be used in the production process rather than labour.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_2'>A provide a means of allocating resources.
ENDSTOPB ensure that all consumer wants are satisfied.
ENDSTOPC enable the government to control prices.
ENDSTOPD ensure that all the goods that society needs are produced.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_3'>A the price of the good rises and demand for the good is price elastic.
ENDSTOPB the price of the good rises and demand for the good is price inelastic.
ENDSTOPC consumer income falls and the good is an inferior good.
ENDSTOPD consumer income rises and the good is a normal good.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_4'>A The effect on price is indeterminate but quantity will fall.
ENDSTOPB The effect on price is indeterminate but quantity will rise.
ENDSTOPC The effect on quantity is indeterminate but price will fall.
ENDSTOPD The effect on quantity is indeterminate but price will rise.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_5'>A quantity is 20 and price is 150.
ENDSTOPB quantity is 30 and price is 100.
ENDSTOPC quantity is 35 and price is 75.
ENDSTOPD quantity is 40 and price is 50.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_6'>A The curve will shift to the left and become less elastic.
ENDSTOPB The curve will shift to the right and become less elastic.
ENDSTOPC The curve will shift to the left and become more elastic.
ENDSTOPD The curve will shift to the right and become more elastic.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_7'>A short run average total cost falls as output rises.
ENDSTOPB long run average total cost falls as output rises.
ENDSTOPC long run average total cost rises as output rises.
ENDSTOPD short run average total cost rises as output rises.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_8'>A A firm doubles its inputs, both capital and labour, and as a result its output more than doubles.
ENDSTOPB A firm doubles the number of products it produces and also doubles its research budget.
ENDSTOPC A firm produces a new product and in so doing lowers the average cost of producing its existing products.
ENDSTOPD A firm produces a new product and in so doing lowers the price it charges on its existing products.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_9'>A its marginal revenue is greater than its marginal cost of production.
ENDSTOPB its marginal revenue is greater than its average fixed cost.
ENDSTOPC it can charge a price greater than its average fixed cost.
ENDSTOPD it can charge a price greater than its average variable cost.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_10'>A increase as its output increases.
ENDSTOPB decrease as its output increases.
ENDSTOPC remain constant as its output increases.
ENDSTOPD always be greater than its average variable costs of production.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_11'>A Marginal cost will increase by more than fixed cost.
ENDSTOPB Marginal cost will increase by the same amount as fixed cost.
ENDSTOPC Marginal cost will increase but by less than fixed cost.
ENDSTOPD Marginal cost will remain unchanged.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_12'>A The firm can make losses in the short run.
ENDSTOPB There are barriers to entry into the market.
ENDSTOPC The firm can make only normal profits in the long run.
ENDSTOPD Marginal revenue is equal to average revenue.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_13'>A the lowest point on its average total cost curve.
ENDSTOPB a point where average total cost is rising.
ENDSTOPC a point where average total cost is falling.
ENDSTOPD a point where average total cost is equal to marginal cost.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_14'>A the marginal cost curve cuts the marginal revenue curve.
ENDSTOPB the marginal cost curve cuts the demand curve.
ENDSTOPC the average cost curve cuts the marginal revenue curve.
ENDSTOPD the average cost curve cuts the demand curve.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_15'>A A rise in the average price of imports relative to the average price of exports.
ENDSTOPB A fall in the quantity of imports relative to the quantity of exports.
ENDSTOPC A rise in the quantity of exports while imports remain the same.
ENDSTOPD A rise in the average price of exports relative to the average price of imports.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_16'>A Classical (real-wage).
ENDSTOPB Frictional.
ENDSTOPC Technological.
ENDSTOPD Structural.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_17'>A reduce output and increase employment.
ENDSTOPB reduce both output and employment.
ENDSTOPC increase output and reduce employment.
ENDSTOPD increase both output and employment.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_18'>A an increase in shareholders’ dividends causes them to increase their expenditure.
ENDSTOPB the central bank will have to increase the supply of money, which will lead to an increase in the amount purchased.
ENDSTOPC the government will have to reduce taxes, which will lead to an increase in the amount purchased.
ENDSTOPD the real income of people earning a fixed quantity of money increases causing them to expand their purchases.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_19'>A the annual cycle of output.
ENDSTOPB the long run trend path of output after removing short run variations.
ENDSTOPC the periodic fluctuations of output around the long run trend.
ENDSTOPD none of the above.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_20'>A A fall in wages.
ENDSTOPB An increase in imported commodity prices.
ENDSTOPC An increase in consumer expenditure.
ENDSTOPD An increase in direct taxes.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_21'>A speculative motive for holding money.
ENDSTOPB transactions motive for holding money.
ENDSTOPC precautionary motive for holding money.
ENDSTOPD asset motive for holding money.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_22'>A liquidity relative to its assets.
ENDSTOPB liquidity relative to its capital.
ENDSTOPC assets relative to its capital.
ENDSTOPD capital relative to its assets.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_23'>A higher the level of prices, the lower will be the rate of unemployment.
ENDSTOPB higher the rate of inflation, the lower will be the rate of unemployment.
ENDSTOPC lower the level of prices, the lower will be the rate of unemployment.
ENDSTOPD higher the rate of inflation, the higher will be the rate of unemployment.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_24'>A investment is increased when interest rates fall.
ENDSTOPB an increase in national income can lead to a more than proportionate increase in the level of investment.
ENDSTOPC an increase in investment can lead to a more than proportionate increase in national income.
ENDSTOPD the rate of change of investment affects the rate of change of output.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_25'>A Time lags
ENDSTOPB Uncertainty
ENDSTOPC Crowding out
ENDSTOPD The accelerator.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2020_choices_26'>A raise government expenditure and reduce tax revenue.
ENDSTOPB raise government expenditure and raise tax revenue.
ENDSTOPC reduce government expenditure and raise tax revenue.
ENDSTOPD reduce government expenditure and reduce tax revenue.</string>"





</resources>