<resources>
    <string name='apr2020_que_1'>The solution to the economic problem of deciding which goods to produce requires:</string>
    <string name='apr2020_que_2'>In a free market economy, the basic function of the price mechanism is to:</string>
    <string name='apr2020_que_3'>The total revenue from the sale of a good will fall if:</string>
    <string name='apr2020_que_4'>What is the combined effect of an increase in the cost of production and a rise in consumer income on the equilibrium price and quantity of an inferior good?</string>
    "<string name='apr2020_que_5'>A consumer’s demand curve for Good X is represented by the equation:
Qdx = 50 – 0.2Px
where Qdx is the quantity of Good X demanded and Px is the price of Good X.
A producer’s supply curve for Good X is represented by the equation:
Qsx = 10 + 0.6Px
where Qsx is the quantity of Good X supplied and Px is the price of Good X. Demand and supply are in equilibrium when:</string>"
    <string name='apr2020_que_6'>A firm’s decision to reduce its expenditure on advertising is most likely to have the following impact on its demand curve:</string>
    <string name='apr2020_que_7'>Diseconomies of scale means:</string>
    <string name='apr2020_que_8'>Which of the following is an example of economies of scope?</string>
    <string name='apr2020_que_9'>In the short run, a loss making firm that seeks to maximise profits will continue to produce if:</string>
    <string name='apr2020_que_10'>In the short run, a firm’s average fixed costs of production will:</string>
    <string name='apr2020_que_11'>What will be the impact of an increase in a firm’s fixed costs of production on the firm’s marginal cost?</string>
    <string name='apr2020_que_12'>Which one of the following characteristics does NOT apply to a firm in an industry characterised by perfect competition?</string>
    <string name='apr2020_que_13'>In the long run a firm in a monopolistic competition market structure will produce at:</string>
    <string name='apr2020_que_14'>The socially efficient output for a monopoly is at the point where:</string>
    <string name='apr2020_que_15'>Which of the following will result in an improvement in the domestic country’s terms of trade?</string>
    <string name='apr2020_que_16'>Which of the following types of unemployment would exist even in a well functioning free market economy?</string>
    <string name='apr2020_que_17'>The short run aggregate supply curve show that an increase in the average price level will encourage firms to:</string>
    <string name='apr2020_que_18'>Which of the following statements helps explain why the aggregate demand curve has a negative slope? As the price level falls:</string>
    <string name='apr2020_que_19'>The business cycle is defined as:</string>
    <string name='apr2020_que_20'>Which of the following is a potential source of demand-pull inflation?</string>
    <string name='apr2020_que_21'>Money that is held because of possible unforeseen events is held mainly because of the:</string>
    <string name='apr2020_que_22'>Capital adequacy for banks is a measure of a bank’s:</string>
    <string name='apr2020_que_23'>The Phillips curve shows that the:</string>
    <string name='apr2020_que_24'>The accelerator principle states that:</string>
    <string name='apr2020_que_25'>Which of the following is NOT a problem associated with the active management of fiscal policy?</string>
    <string name='apr2020_que_26'>In the event of a recession in the economy, automatic fiscal stabilisers:</string>



</resources>