<resources>
    <string name='apr2011_que_1'>Which of the following statements below is always TRUE?</string>
    "<string name='apr2011_que_2'>Despite an increase in the minimum price of admission from £15.00 to £18.00, a
football club finds that attendance at home matches increased by 20%. Which of the
following could most effectively explain this situation?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_que_3'>If the demand and supply for a commodity both increase at each price, the market
price will tend to:</string>"
    <string name='apr2011_que_4'>In a free market economy the basic function of the price mechanism is to:</string>
    "<string name='apr2011_que_5'>If the government fixed a minimum price of bread above the equilibrium price and
there was no further government intervention in the market for bread, which of the
following would result?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_que_6'>If a firm increases its output and this results in an equal proportionate increase in its
revenue, which of the following can be deduced about the price elasticity of demand
for the firm’s product?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_que_7'>Which of the following would NOT explain why, when the price of a good rises, the
quantity supplied will also rise?</string>"
    <string name='apr2011_que_8'>Diminishing marginal utility of income implies:</string>
    "<string name='apr2011_que_9'>A firm’s decision to reduce its expenditure on advertising is most likely to have the
following impact on its demand curve:</string>"
    <string name='apr2011_que_10'>In which situation will a firm cease production in the short run?</string>
    <string name='apr2011_que_11'>Which assumption is essential for a market to be contestable?</string>
    "<string name='apr2011_que_12'>Given that a firm’s fixed costs are £1,000, the average total cost of its output is £4 and
its average variable cost is £3.50, which one of the following will represent its total
output per period?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_que_13'>If firms in a perfectly competitive industry are making a loss in the short run then in
the long run firms will:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_que_14'>Which of the following is NOT usually given as a reason why firms form strategic
alliances?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_que_15'>If the average price of exports has risen by 50% since the base year and the average
price of imports has risen by 25% since the base year, what is the current figure for
the terms of trade?</string>"
    <string name='apr2011_que_16'>Firms can benefit through specialisation and international trade due to:</string>
    "<string name='apr2011_que_17'>Which of the following could explain why a country’s aggregate demand curve might
shift inwards to the left?</string>"
    <string name='apr2011_que_18'>If planned injections are less than planned withdrawals:</string>
    <string name='apr2011_que_19'>Which of the following is an example of disequilibrium unemployment?</string>
    "<string name='apr2011_que_20'>Given the following macroeconomic data:
Consumer expenditure £70 million
Investment expenditure £20 million
Government expenditure £40 million
Exports £20 million
Imports £30 million
Net income from abroad £10 million
What is the value of the Gross Domestic Product?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_que_21'>An economy with a floating exchange rate has a deficit on the current account of its
balance of payments. Which policy combination would be most likely to solve this
problem?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_que_22'>Where would interest payments on short term foreign deposits in banks be entered on
the balance of payments account?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_que_23'>The use of debit cards and cash withdrawal machines will have the following effect
on a bank:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_que_24'>Which of the following would cause the demand for money curve to shift inwards to
the left?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_que_25'>The Bank of England’s use of the “Taylor Rule” attempts to take which of the
following two macroeconomic objectives into account?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_que_26'>The overall money multiplier effect might be smaller than the full bank deposits
multiplier because:</string>"

</resources>