<resources>
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_1'>A Structural.
ENDSTOPB Demand-deficient.
ENDSTOPC Regional.
ENDSTOPD Technological.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_2'>A the long run and short run Phillips curves to shift to the right.
ENDSTOPB the long run and short run Phillips curves to shift to the left.
ENDSTOPC the long run Phillips curve to shift to the right and the short run Phillips curves
to shift to the left.
ENDSTOPD the long run Phillips curve to shift to the left and the short run Phillips curves
to shift to the right.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_3'>A A fall in the interest rate of Country A with an even bigger fall in Country B’s
interest rate.
ENDSTOPB A fall in the interest rate of Country A with constant interest rate in Country B.
ENDSTOPC A rise in the interest rate of Country A with an even bigger rise in Country B’s
interest rate.
ENDSTOPD A fall in the interest rate of Country A with a rise in the interest rate of
Country B.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_4'>A An appreciation of a country’s exchange rate will increase its import
expenditure and decrease its export revenues.
ENDSTOPB An appreciation of a country’s exchange rate will increase its import volumes
and decrease its export volumes.
ENDSTOPC A depreciation of a country’s exchange rate will decrease its import volumes
and decrease its export volumes.
ENDSTOPD A depreciation of a country’s exchange rate will decrease its import
expenditure and increase its export revenues.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_5'>A surplus of £125 billion.
ENDSTOPB deficit of £125 billion.
ENDSTOPC surplus of £25 billion.
ENDSTOPD deficit of £25 billion.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_6'>A Gross Domestic Product is greater than Gross National Product.
ENDSTOPB Gross Domestic Product is less than Gross National Product.
ENDSTOPC Gross Domestic Product is the same as Gross National Product.
ENDSTOPD We cannot say whether Gross Domestic Product differs from Gross National
Product from this information.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_7'>A higher the price level.
ENDSTOPB lower the level of real income.
ENDSTOPC higher the rate of interest.
ENDSTOPD higher the speculative (asset) demand for money.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_8'>A rise as Treasury bill prices rise.
ENDSTOPB fall as Treasury bill prices rise.
ENDSTOPC fall as Treasury bill prices fall.
ENDSTOPD rise as Treasury bill prices fall.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_9'>A an increase in aggregate demand and a reduction in real output and
unemployment.
ENDSTOPB an increase in aggregate demand, real output and unemployment.
ENDSTOPC an increase in aggregate demand and real output and a reduction in
unemployment.
ENDSTOPD a reduction in aggregate demand and real output and an increase in
unemployment.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_10'>A raise government expenditure and reduce tax revenue.
ENDSTOPB raise government expenditure and raise tax revenue.
ENDSTOPC reduce government expenditure and raise tax revenue.
ENDSTOPD reduce government expenditure and reduce tax revenue.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_11'>A increase the output of the existing firms and the industry.
ENDSTOPB reduce the output of the existing firms and the industry.
ENDSTOPC reduce the output of the industry and increase the output of the existing firms.
ENDSTOPD reduce the output of the existing firms and increase the output of the industry.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_12'>A £11.50.
ENDSTOPB £11.25.
ENDSTOPC £5.00.
ENDSTOPD £0.25.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_13'>A average total cost equals marginal cost.
ENDSTOPB average revenue is greater than marginal cost.
ENDSTOPC price is greater than average total cost.
ENDSTOPD average total cost is less than marginal cost.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_14'>A a firm’s competitors match both its price increases and price reductions.
ENDSTOPB one firm in the industry sets the price for all other firms.
ENDSTOPC a firm’s competitors match its price reductions but not its price increases.
ENDSTOPD the price charged by a firm can either rise or fall depending on
what happens to its competitors’ prices.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_15'>A surplus of Good X and the price will rise.
ENDSTOPB shortage of Good X and the price will fall.
ENDSTOPC surplus of Good X and the price will fall.
ENDSTOPD shortage of Good X and the price will rise.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_16'>A A decrease in the price of Good X.
ENDSTOPB An increase in the price of a substitute good.
ENDSTOPC An increase in the price of a complementary good.
ENDSTOPD A decrease in consumer income.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_17'>A rise at an increasing rate as consumption of Good X increases.
ENDSTOPB rise at a decreasing rate as consumption of Good X increases.
ENDSTOPC fall at an increasing rate as consumption of Good X increases.
ENDSTOPD fall at a decreasing rate as consumption of Good X increases.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_18'>A having insurance makes an individual less careful.
ENDSTOPB having insurance makes an individual more careful.
ENDSTOPC the people taking out the insurance are those who have the highest risk.
ENDSTOPD the people taking out the insurance are those who have the highest risk
aversion.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_19'>A quantity is 20 and price is 150.
ENDSTOPB quantity is 30 and price is 100.
ENDSTOPC quantity is 35 and price is 75.
ENDSTOPD quantity is 40 and price is 50.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_20'>A quantity demanded of Good X to increase and the demand curve for Good Y
to shift toward the right.
ENDSTOPB quantity demanded of Good X to increase and the demand curve for Good Y
to shift toward the left.
ENDSTOPC demand curve for Good X to shift to the right and the demand curve for Good
Y to shift toward the left.
ENDSTOPD demand curve for Good X to shift to the right and the demand curve for Good
Y to shift toward the right.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_21'>A price rises and demand for the good is price elastic.
ENDSTOPB price rises and demand for the good is price inelastic.
ENDSTOPC consumer income falls and the good is inferior.
ENDSTOPD consumer income falls and the good is a Giffen good.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_22'>A 1 and 0.25.
ENDSTOPB 0 and 0.25.
ENDSTOPC 1 and 0.
ENDSTOPD 0 and 1.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_23'>A different consumer’s tastes but not different quality products.
ENDSTOPB same quality products.
ENDSTOPC different quality products reflecting different production costs.
ENDSTOPD different varieties offered at the same price.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_24'>A A firm charges customers different prices according to how much they
purchase.
ENDSTOPB Consumers are grouped into independent markets and a separate price is
charged in each market.
ENDSTOPC A firm charges each customer the maximum price he/she is prepared to pay.
ENDSTOPD Different firms charge different prices for the same product.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_25'>A positive.
ENDSTOPB above its average physical product.
ENDSTOPC increasing.
ENDSTOPD below its average physical product.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_choices_26'>A Franchise.
ENDSTOPB Joint venture.
ENDSTOPC Merger.
ENDSTOPD Licensing agreement.</string>"

</resources>