<resources>
    "<string name='apr2010_que_1'>The need to employ workers with certain skills may decline even if the industry as a
whole is not in decline. This form of unemployment is called:</string>"
    <string name='apr2010_que_2'>An increase in the natural rate of unemployment will cause:</string>
    "<string name='apr2010_que_3'>All other things being equal which of the following events would cause the
value of Country A’s currency to appreciate against the value of Country B’s
currency?</string>"
    <string name='apr2010_que_4'>All other things being equal, which one of the following statements is always TRUE?</string>
    "<string name='apr2010_que_5'>In Country A government expenditure is £350 billion, tax revenue is £275 billion,
aggregate saving is £300 billion and aggregate investment is £250 billion. The net
exports of Country A are equal to a:</string>"
    <string name='apr2010_que_6'>If a country has a current account deficit then:</string>
    <string name='apr2010_que_7'>The transactions demand for money will be greater the:</string>
    "<string name='apr2010_que_8'>If an excess demand for money exists in the economy, then as the money market
moves towards equilibrium we would expect the short term interest rate to:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_que_9'>According to Keynesian analysis the adoption of an expansionary fiscal policy will
result in:</string>"
    <string name='apr2010_que_10'>In the event of a recession in the economy, automatic fiscal stabilizers:</string>
    "<string name='apr2010_que_11'>If firms in a perfectly competitive industry are making excess profits in the short run
then the long run effect will be to:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_que_12'>A monopolist can sell 25 units of output per day for a price of £11.50 each and 26
units of output per day for a price of £11.25 each. The marginal revenue earned from
the 26th unit sold is:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_que_13'>For a firm in long run equilibrium in an industry characterized by monopolistic
competition:</string>"
    <string name='apr2010_que_14'>The kinked demand curve model of oligopoly is based upon the assumption that:</string>
    "<string name='apr2010_que_15'>The demand equation for Good X is Qd = 15 – 0.5P and the supply equation for
Good X is Qs = 3 + 2P, where P is the price. When the price is £6 there will be a:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_que_16'>Which of the following events would shift the demand curve for Good X, which is a
normal good, to the right?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_que_17'>According to the law of diminishing marginal utility, the total satisfaction that a
consumer gets from consuming Good X will:</string>"
    <string name='apr2010_que_18'>Adverse selection refers to a situation where:</string>
    "<string name='apr2010_que_19'>A consumer’s demand curve for Good X is represented by the equation
Qdx = 50 – 0.2Px
where Qdx is the quantity of Good X demanded and Px is the price of Good X.
A producer’s supply curve for Good X is represented by the equation
Qsx = 10 + 0.6Px
Where Qsx is the quantity of Good X supplied and Px is the price of Good X.
Demand and supply are in equilibrium when:</string>"
    <string name='apr2010_que_20'>If Goods X and Y are substitutes, a fall in the price of Good X causes the:</string>
    <string name='apr2010_que_21'>The total revenue from the sale of a good will fall if:</string>
    "<string name='apr2010_que_22'>A consumer always spends one quarter of his income on travel. What are his price
elasticity of demand for travel and his income elasticity of demand for travel
respectively:</string>"
    <string name='apr2010_que_23'>Vertical product differentiation refers to differences between products which reflect:</string>
    <string name='apr2010_que_24'>Third degree price differentiation refers to the situation where:</string>
    "<string name='apr2010_que_25'>The total output and the average physical product of the variable factor increase as
long as the marginal physical product of the variable factor is:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2010_que_26'>When the owner of a patented product allows another firm to produce it for a fee, the
arrangement is referred to as a:</string>"

</resources>