<resources>
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_1'>A –2 and the two goods are complements.
ENDSTOPB –0.5 and the two goods are complements.
ENDSTOPC –2 and the two goods are substitutes.
ENDSTOPD –0.5 and the two goods are substitutes.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_2'>A quantity of productive inputs.
ENDSTOPB quantity of inputs on one axis and quantity of outputs on the other axis.
ENDSTOPC quantities of finished goods.
ENDSTOPD prices of productive inputs.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_3'>A £30
ENDSTOPB £40
ENDSTOPC £50
ENDSTOPD £60.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_4'>A The curve will shift to the left and become less elastic.
ENDSTOPB The curve will shift to the right and become less elastic.
ENDSTOPC The curve will shift to the left and become more elastic.
ENDSTOPD The curve will shift to the right and become more elastic.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_5'>A the average revenue is equal to marginal cost.
ENDSTOPB the industry demand curve must be perfectly elastic.
ENDSTOPC there may be difficulty for some firms in exiting the industry.
ENDSTOPD there are no supernormal profits in the short run.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_6'>A total utility of water is less than the total utility of diamonds.
ENDSTOPB total utility of water is greater than the total utility of diamonds.
ENDSTOPC marginal utility of water is less than the marginal utility of diamonds.
ENDSTOPD marginal utility of water divided by the marginal utility of diamonds, is greater
than the price of water divided by the price of diamonds.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_7'>A A firm’s fear that if it raises its price then the rise will be matched by
competitors, but if it cuts its price then the cut will not be matched by
competitors
ENDSTOPB Supernormal profits
ENDSTOPC A belief that one firm’s actions has an influence on the actions of other firms
ENDSTOPD Advertising and other non-price competition.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_8'>A raise its price and increase output.
ENDSTOPB lower its price and decrease output.
ENDSTOPC lower its price and increase output.
ENDSTOPD raise its price and decrease output.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_9'>A the joint output of the two firms is greater than the monopoly output, but less
than the perfect competition output.
ENDSTOPB the joint output of the two firms is identical to the monopoly output.
ENDSTOPC the joint output of the two firms is identical to the perfect competition output.
ENDSTOPD the output of the two firms will always be identical.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_10'>A Firm A – High; Firm ENDSTOPB – Low
B Firm A – High; Firm B – High
ENDSTOPC Firm A – Low; Firm B – Low
ENDSTOPD Firm A – Low; Firm B – High</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_11'>A If more labour is added to a given amount of capital, the marginal product of
labour falls.
ENDSTOPB If the ratio of labour to capital increases by 100%, the output of the firm
increases by less than 100%.
ENDSTOPC If the input of both capital and labour increases by 120%, the output of the
firm increases by 100%.
ENDSTOPD If more labour is added to a given amount of capital, the marginal product of
labour rises.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_12'>A The price of Good X will rise by £10.
ENDSTOPB The price of Good X will fall by more than £10.
ENDSTOPC The price of Good X will fall by less than £10.
ENDSTOPD The price of Good X will fall by £20.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_13'>A the market price to fall and the quantity supplied to rise.
ENDSTOPB the market price to fall and the quantity supplied to fall.
ENDSTOPC both market price and quantity supplied to fall.
ENDSTOPD no change to the market price or output.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_14'>A A fall in investment due to the associated rise in interest rates
ENDSTOPB A fall in consumer demand due to fear of higher future taxes
ENDSTOPC A fall in demand for exports due to an exchange rate appreciation caused by
the associated rise in interest rates
ENDSTOPD Reduced import expenditure due to increased government demand for
domestically produced goods.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_15'>A fall as the short-term interest rate falls.
ENDSTOPB fall as the short-term interest rate rises.
ENDSTOPC rise as the short-term interest rate falls.
ENDSTOPD rise as the short-term interest rate rises.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_16'>A a rise.
ENDSTOPB a fall.
ENDSTOPC no change.
ENDSTOPD uncertain.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_17'>A the influence of fiscal policy on the level of inflation and unemployment.
ENDSTOPB the influence of monetary policy on the level of inflation and unemployment.
ENDSTOPC an inverse relationship between inflation and unemployment.
ENDSTOPD a positive relationship between inflation and unemployment.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_18'>A elastic is the demand for money and the more interest elastic is the level of
investment.
ENDSTOPB inelastic is the demand for money and the less interest elastic is the level of
investment.
ENDSTOPC elastic is the demand for money and the less interest elastic is the level of
investment.
ENDSTOPD inelastic is the demand for money and the more interest elastic is the level of
investment.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_19'>A the national income and interest rates will both rise.
ENDSTOPB the national income and interest rates will both fall.
ENDSTOPC the effect on both national income and interest rates is uncertain.
ENDSTOPD the national income will rise but the effect on interest rates is uncertain.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_20'>A government expenditure.
ENDSTOPB taxation.
ENDSTOPC money supply.
ENDSTOPD none of the above.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_21'>A Fixed interest rate borrowers lose
ENDSTOPB Menu costs
ENDSTOPC Shoe-leather costs
ENDSTOPD Fixed interest rate lenders lose.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_22'>A autonomous saving.
ENDSTOPB the marginal propensity to consume.
ENDSTOPC the marginal propensity to import.
ENDSTOPD the marginal rate of taxation.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_23'>A lead to an actual rate of unemployment that is temporarily greater than the
natural rate.
ENDSTOPB lead to an actual rate of unemployment that is temporarily lower than the
natural rate.
ENDSTOPC increase the natural rate of unemployment.
ENDSTOPD decrease the natural rate of unemployment.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_24'>A The real rate of interest is negative.
ENDSTOPB The rate of inflation is less than the real rate of interest.
ENDSTOPC The real rate of interest is 11%.
ENDSTOPD The nominal rate of interest exceeds the real rate of interest.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_25'>A The demand for money is negatively related to the interest rate.
ENDSTOPB The demand for money is positively related to nominal income.
ENDSTOPC The demand for money is negatively related to the general price level.
ENDSTOPD The demand to hold money is positively related to real income.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2021_choices_26'>A fall and the unemployment rate would rise.
ENDSTOPB fall and the unemployment rate would fall.
ENDSTOPC rise and the unemployment rate would fall.
ENDSTOPD rise and the unemployment rate would rise.</string>"




</resources>