<resources>
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_1'>A natural resources, labour and money.
ENDSTOPB labour, money and factories.
ENDSTOPC natural resources, capital and factories.
ENDSTOPD natural resources, labour and capital.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_2'>A all resources will eventually be exhausted.
ENDSTOPB there are unlimited resources, we just have an allocation problem.
ENDSTOPC there are unlimited wants and limited resources.
ENDSTOPD all of the above.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_3'>A a free-market economy.
ENDSTOPB a centrally planned economy.
ENDSTOPC a traditional market economy.
ENDSTOPD a mixed economy.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_4'>A a market system.
ENDSTOPB macroeconomics.
ENDSTOPC competition.
ENDSTOPD opportunity cost.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_5'>A increased expenditure on research and development
ENDSTOPB a reduction in the unemployment rate
ENDSTOPC increased immigration of skilled workers
ENDSTOPD the discovery of new natural resources</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_6'>A Country Y has a comparative advantage in the production of Good A.
ENDSTOPB Country X has an absolute advantage in the production of Good B.
ENDSTOPC Country X has an absolute advantage in the production of Good A.
ENDSTOPD Country Y has a comparative advantage in the production of Good B.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_7'>A decrease the demand for eggs.
ENDSTOPB increase the demand for eggs.
ENDSTOPC increase the quantity of eggs demanded.
ENDSTOPD decrease the quantity of eggs demanded.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_8'>A Cross price elasticity of demand is positive for complementary goods.
ENDSTOPB Elasticity of supply is zero along a horizontal supply curve.
ENDSTOPC Price elasticity of demand varies along a straight-line demand curve.
ENDSTOPD Income elasticity of demand is positive for inferior goods.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_9'>A shifting the demand curve to the left.
ENDSTOPB shifting the supply curve to the left.
ENDSTOPC shifting the supply curve to the right.
ENDSTOPD shifting the demand curve to the right.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_10'>A increase the demand for fruit sorbet and strawberries.
ENDSTOPB decrease the demand for fruit sorbet and increase the demand for strawberries.
ENDSTOPC decrease the demand for fruit sorbet and strawberries.
ENDSTOPD increase the demand for fruit sorbet and decrease the demand for strawberries.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_11'>A rise at an increasing rate as the consumption of Good X increases.
ENDSTOPB rise at a decreasing rate as the consumption of Good X increases.
ENDSTOPC fall at an increasing rate as the consumption of Good X increases.
ENDSTOPD fall at a decreasing rate as the consumption of Good X increases.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_12'>A suggests people who know they are a bad risk are more inclined to take out
insurance.
ENDSTOPB suggests people who know they are a bad risk are less inclined to take out
insurance.
ENDSTOPC suggests a policyholder may act in a way which makes an insured event less
likely to occur.
ENDSTOPD suggests a policyholder may act in a way which makes an insured event more
likely to occur.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_13'>A There are many firms supplying the market.
ENDSTOPB There are no barriers to entry.
ENDSTOPC Supernormal profits can be made in the long run.
ENDSTOPD A firm need not consider the reaction of other firms in the industry.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_14'>A increase output and reduce price.
ENDSTOPB reduce price and output.
ENDSTOPC increase price and output.
ENDSTOPD reduce output and increase price.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_15'>A each firm’s marginal revenue curve is tangential to the average total cost
curve.
ENDSTOPB each firm’s marginal revenue curve is tangential to the marginal cost curve.
ENDSTOPC each firm’s demand curve is tangential to the marginal cost curve.
ENDSTOPD each firm’s demand curve is tangential to the average total cost curve.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_16'>A Gross Domestic Product – depreciation.
ENDSTOPB Net Domestic Product + net property income from abroad.
ENDSTOPC Gross Domestic Product + net property income from abroad.
ENDSTOPD Net National Income + depreciation.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_17'>A I + S + T = G + X + Z
ENDSTOPB Y = ENDSTOPC + S + Td
C I + G + X = S + T + Z
ENDSTOPD Y = C + I + G + X − Z − Te</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_18'>A 0.4
ENDSTOPB 0.6
ENDSTOPC 0.7
ENDSTOPD 0.8</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_19'>A 1.25
ENDSTOPB 0.8
ENDSTOPC 5
ENDSTOPD 0.2</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_20' formatted="false">A 5.9%
ENDSTOPB 5.3%
ENDSTOPC 5.0%
ENDSTOPD 6.3%</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_21'>A The demand for money is negatively related to the interest rate.
ENDSTOPB The demand for money is positively related to national income.
ENDSTOPC The demand for money is negatively related to the price level.
ENDSTOPD The demand for money is positively related to real income.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_22'>A an increase in value added tax
ENDSTOPB an increase in imported commodity prices
ENDSTOPC an increase in consumer expenditure
ENDSTOPD an increase in direct taxes</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_23'>A balance of trade.
ENDSTOPB capital account.
ENDSTOPC balance of payments.
ENDSTOPD current account.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_24'>A The US dollar would appreciate and the Chinese renminbi depreciate.
ENDSTOPB The US dollar would depreciate and the Chinese renminbi depreciate.
ENDSTOPC The US dollar would appreciate and the Chinese renminbi appreciate.
ENDSTOPD The US dollar would depreciate and the Chinese renminbi appreciate.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_25'>A floating exchange rates.
ENDSTOPB terms of trade.
ENDSTOPC purchasing power parity.
ENDSTOPD exchange equalisation.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_choices_26'>A very effective.
ENDSTOPB not effective.
ENDSTOPC equally effective as fiscal policy.
ENDSTOPD less effective than fiscal policy.</string>"

</resources>