<resources>
    "<string name='apr2016_que_1'>Which of the following statements explains how price, demand and supply for a good
respond to an increase in the price of a substitute good?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_que_2'>If the demand for Good X increases (due to a rise in income of consumers) and the
supply of Good X increases (due to increased worker productivity) then the
equilibrium price of Good X:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_que_3'>If an 8% rise in the price of Good X results in a 4% fall in the quantity of Good X
demanded then the approximate price elasticity of demand for Good X is:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_que_4'>In the short run, the range of output over which average total cost falls will be the
same as the range over which:</string>"
    <string name='apr2016_que_5'>Which one of the following statements concerning advertising is FALSE?</string>
    <string name='apr2016_que_6'>A market is defined as perfectly contestable if entry to it:</string>
    "<string name='apr2016_que_7'>Identify the equation below which can be used to find the maximum insurance
premium (P) that a consumer is willing to pay, where U is utility, X is a random loss,
a is the initial level of wealth and E is the expectations operator.</string>"
    <string name='apr2016_que_8'>Which one of the following reveals constant returns to scale?</string>
    "<string name='apr2016_que_9'>The managing director of a monopoly firm is given the following data:
Marginal revenue = £11, Marginal cost = £10
Average cost = £13, Average revenue = £15
To maximise profits the firm should:</string>"
    <string name='apr2016_que_10'>The short run supply curve for a firm in a perfectly competitive industry is its:</string>
    "<string name='apr2016_que_11'>Which one of the following is NOT a feature of an industry characterised by
monopolistic competition?</string>"
    <string name='apr2016_que_12'>Which one of the following statements about market structure is TRUE?</string>
    "<string name='apr2016_que_13'>Go Global Airways, which is a profit maximising firm, has to decide whether or not to
run an extra daily flight between London and Berlin. The total daily fixed costs of the
airline are £6,000, the total variable costs of the extra flight are £3,000 and the expected
revenue from the extra flight is £4,500. In such circumstances Go Global Airways
which is overall a profitable firm will:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_que_14'>Which one of the following will have net exports directly measured in the method
used to calculate Gross Domestic Product (GDP)?</string>"
    <string name='apr2016_que_15'>You are given the following data for an economy: The value of the economy’s Gross National Income at market prices is:</string>
    "<string name='apr2016_que_16'>Assume that the marginal propensity to consume domestically produced goods is 0.7
and there are no taxes. The government decides to increase public spending by £100
million. According to simple Keynesian multiplier analysis, what is likely to be the
total change in national income resulting from this increase in government
expenditure (to the nearest million)?</string>"
    <string name='apr2016_que_17'>Which one of the following will have a negative impact upon money demand?</string>
    "<string name='apr2016_que_18'>In a simple economy, consumption is given by the relationship
C = 0.75Y
where C is consumption expenditure and Y is Gross Domestic Product.
Government expenditure is £150 million, investment is £50 million and there is no
taxation or international trade. What will be the equilibrium value of Gross Domestic
Product of the economy?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_que_19'>To obtain a measure of Net National Income from Gross Domestic Product it is
necessary to:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_que_20'>If the money supply rises as a result of central bank policy, this will normally result
in:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_que_21'>Which of the following would constitute a supply side economic policy for raising
employment?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_que_22'>In Country A, government expenditure is £250 billion, tax revenue is £275 billion,
aggregate saving is £300 billion and aggregate investment is £250 billion. The net
exports of Country A are equal to a:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2016_que_23'>If the Gross Domestic Product (GDP) in an economy rises and the unemployment rate
falls then:</string>"
    <string name='apr2016_que_24'>Which one of the following is likely to lead to cost push inflation?</string>
    <string name='apr2016_que_25'>Firms can benefit through specialisation and international trade due to:</string>
    <string name='apr2016_que_26'>Which one of the following statements about the demand for money is TRUE?</string>



</resources>