<resources>"<string name='apr2006_choices_1'>A equilibrium quantity will increase but the effect on the price is indeterminate
ENDSTOPB equilibrium quantity will decrease but the effect on the price is indeterminate
ENDSTOPC price will fall but the effect on the equilibrium quantity will be indeterminate
ENDSTOPD price will rise but the effect on the equilibrium quantity will be indeterminate</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_2'>A shifting the demand curve to the left
ENDSTOPB shifting the demand curve to the right
ENDSTOPC shifting the supply curve to the right
ENDSTOPD shifting the supply curve to the left</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_3'>A An input in the production process became more expensive.
ENDSTOPB The price of a close substitute for the good increased.
ENDSTOPC An input in the production process became more expensive and the price of a
close substitute increased.
ENDSTOPD An input in the production process became more expensive and the price of a
close substitute decreased.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_4'>A excess supply
ENDSTOPB excess demand
ENDSTOPC a decrease in price and a decrease in the quantity traded
ENDSTOPD an increase in price and an increase in the quantity traded</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_5'>A the demand for X and Y are both price inelastic
ENDSTOPB X and Y are substitutes
ENDSTOPC X and Y are complements
ENDSTOPD the demand for X and Y are both price elastic</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_6'>A income increases and the Good is normal
ENDSTOPB its price rises and demand is price elastic
ENDSTOPC its price rises and demand is price inelastic
ENDSTOPD income falls and the Good is inferior</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_7'>A The price of Good X would fall by exactly £5.
ENDSTOPB The price of Good X would fall by less than £5.
ENDSTOPC The price of Good X would fall by more than £5.
ENDSTOPD The price of Good X would fall by exactly £10.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_8'>A rise at an increasing rate as the consumption of Good X increases
ENDSTOPB rise at a decreasing rate as the consumption of Good X increases
ENDSTOPC fall at an increasing rate as the consumption of Good X increases
ENDSTOPD fall at a decreasing rate as the consumption of Good X increases</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_9'>A suggests people who know they are a bad risk are more inclined to take out
insurance
ENDSTOPB suggests people who know they are a bad risk are less inclined to take out
insurance
ENDSTOPC suggests a policyholder may act in a way which makes an insured event less
likely to occur
ENDSTOPD suggests a policyholder may act in a way which makes an insured event more
likely to occur</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_10'>A total sales are maximised
ENDSTOPB average total costs are minimised
ENDSTOPC marginal cost equals marginal revenue
ENDSTOPD average revenue is maximised</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_11'>A Country Y has an absolute advantage in the production of both goods
ENDSTOPB Country Y has a comparative advantage in the production of bicycles
ENDSTOPC Country X has a comparative advantage in the production of bicycles
ENDSTOPD Country Y has a comparative advantage in the production of cars</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_12'>A There is freedom of entry and exit to the industry.
ENDSTOPB There are many firms supplying the market.
ENDSTOPC Firms can lower their prices without influencing the behaviour of other firms.
ENDSTOPD Each firm faces a horizontal demand curve.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_13'>A increase output and reduce price
ENDSTOPB reduce price and output
ENDSTOPC increase price and output
ENDSTOPD reduce output and increase price</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_14'>A the market price to increase and the quantity traded to decrease
ENDSTOPB the market price to decrease and the quantity traded to decrease
ENDSTOPC the market price to increase and the quantity traded to increase
ENDSTOPD no change to price or the quantity traded</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_15'>A suggests that price will remain constant even with fluctuations in demand
ENDSTOPB assumes that competitors will match price cuts and ignore price increases
ENDSTOPC assumes that marginal revenue sometimes increases with output
ENDSTOPD suggests how the current price is determined</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_16'>A Real GDP per capita falls
ENDSTOPB Real GDP per capita rises
ENDSTOPC Real GDP falls
ENDSTOPD Real GDP rises</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_17'>A deduct transfer payments
ENDSTOPB deduct any indirect taxes paid by firms
ENDSTOPC add net property income from abroad
ENDSTOPD deduct depreciation</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_18'>A the marginal utility of an extra pound of income decreases as more income is
received
ENDSTOPB the marginal utility of an extra pound of income increases as more income is
received
ENDSTOPC there will always be some individuals willing to take risks while others will be
unwilling to take risks regardless of the pay offs
ENDSTOPD investors will only take an increased risk if the marginal utility of risk over the
price of risk rises</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_19'>A A fall in wages.
ENDSTOPB An increase in imported commodity prices.
ENDSTOPC An increase in consumer expenditure.
ENDSTOPD An increase in direct taxes.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_20'>A The marginal propensity to consume.
ENDSTOPB The autonomous expenditure multiplier.
ENDSTOPC The vertical long run aggregate supply curve.
ENDSTOPD The speculative demand for money.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_21'>A 0.4
ENDSTOPB 0.6
ENDSTOPC 0.67
ENDSTOPD 0.7</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_22'>A The demand for air travel is price inelastic.
ENDSTOPB The demand for air travel is price elastic.
ENDSTOPC The demand for air travel is perfectly price elastic.
ENDSTOPD The demand for air travel perfectly price inelastic.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_23'>A fall as the short term interest rate rises
ENDSTOPB fall as the short term interest rate falls
ENDSTOPC rise as the short term interest rate rises
ENDSTOPD rise as the short term interest rate falls</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_24'>A an increase in aggregate demand and a reduction in real output and
unemployment
ENDSTOPB an increase in aggregate demand, real output and unemployment
ENDSTOPC an increase in aggregate demand and real output and a reduction in
unemployment
ENDSTOPD a reduction in aggregate demand and real output and an increase in
unemployment</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_25'>A 4.8%
ENDSTOPB 4.0%
ENDSTOPC 5.0%
ENDSTOPD 5.3%</string>"
    "<string name='apr2006_choices_26'>A increasing its net liabilities and increasing its net assets
ENDSTOPB decreasing its net liabilities and increasing its net assets
ENDSTOPC increasing its net liabilities and decreasing its net assets
ENDSTOPD decreasing its net liabilities and decreasing its net assets</string>"
</resources>