<resources>
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_1'>A Opportunity cost is equal to total revenue minus total variable cost.
ENDSTOPB Opportunity cost is constant.
ENDSTOPC Opportunity cost is the cost in terms of the best foregone alternative.
ENDSTOPD Opportunity cost is the addition to total cost of producing one extra unit of a
good.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_2'>A a decrease in labour productivity in industry X
ENDSTOPB a fall in the price of raw materials used to produce Good X
ENDSTOPC a decrease in wages in industry X
ENDSTOPD a government subsidy on the production of Good X</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_3'>A the demand for Good X to fall and price of Good X to fall
ENDSTOPB the demand for Good X to fall and price of Good X to rise
ENDSTOPC the demand for Good X to rise and price of Good X to fall
ENDSTOPD the demand for Good X to rise and price of Good X to rise</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_4'>A people who know they are a bad risk are more inclined to take out insurance.
ENDSTOPB people who know they are a bad risk are less inclined to take out insurance.
ENDSTOPC a policyholder may act in a way which makes an insured event less likely to
occur.
ENDSTOPD a policyholder may act in a way which makes an insured event more likely to
occur.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_5'>A raise their price in the short run but restore the price back to its original level
in the long run.
ENDSTOPB keep their price constant in both the short run and the long run.
ENDSTOPC raise their price in both the short run and the long run.
ENDSTOPD keep their price constant in the short run but raise their price in the long run.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_6'>A marginal cost curve cuts the demand curve.
ENDSTOPB marginal cost curve cuts the marginal revenue curve.
ENDSTOPC average cost curve cuts the marginal revenue curve.
ENDSTOPD average cost curve cuts the demand curve.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_7'>A significant economies of scale
ENDSTOPB heavy potential advertising costs
ENDSTOPC large capital requirements
ENDSTOPD constant returns to scale</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_8'>A £15,000
ENDSTOPB £12,000
ENDSTOPC £7,000
ENDSTOPD not possible to calculate from the information given</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_9'>A Under perfect competition, in the long run all firms produce where marginal
costs equal average revenue.
ENDSTOPB Under monopolistic competition firms produce differentiated products.
ENDSTOPC Under oligopoly, firms make decisions taking into account the possible
reactions of their competitors.
ENDSTOPD Under monopoly, a profit maximising firm with positive marginal costs always
produces in the region of price inelastic demand.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_10'>A attempts to maximise sales after assuming that the other firm will attempt to
maximise sales.
ENDSTOPB assumes the other firm will produce a given output and then chooses its profit
maximising output.
ENDSTOPC assumes the other firm’s price is given and then chooses its profit maximising
price.
ENDSTOPD will attempt to collude with the other firm so as to set a price and output level
which will maximise industry level profits.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_11'>A The launch phase
ENDSTOPB The growth phase
ENDSTOPC The innovation phase
ENDSTOPD The decline phase</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_12'>A Tier 1 plus Tier 2 capital divided by total assets
ENDSTOPB Tier 1 plus Tier 2 capital divided by risk weighted assets
ENDSTOPC Tier 1 capital divided by total assets
ENDSTOPD Tier 1 capital divided by risk weighted assets</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_13'>A a rise in the average price of exports relative to the average price of imports
ENDSTOPB a rise in the average price of imports relative to the average price of exports
ENDSTOPC an appreciation of the domestic currency
ENDSTOPD a rise in the domestic country’s terms of trade index from 100 to 120</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_14'>A expansionary fiscal policy
ENDSTOPB expansionary monetary policy
ENDSTOPC better education and training
ENDSTOPD a reduction in trade union powers</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_15'>A Gross Domestic Product is greater than Gross National Income.
ENDSTOPB Gross Domestic Product is less than Gross National Income.
ENDSTOPC Gross Domestic Product is the same as Gross National Income.
ENDSTOPD we cannot say whether Gross Domestic Product differs from Gross National
Income from this information.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_16'>A 4.76%
ENDSTOPB 5.0%
ENDSTOPC 6.25%
ENDSTOPD 6.67%</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_17'>A an increase in interest rates
ENDSTOPB a depreciation in its exchange rate
ENDSTOPC a fall in government expenditure
ENDSTOPD a decrease in business confidence</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_18'>A the annual cycle of output.
ENDSTOPB the long run trend path of output after removing short run variations.
ENDSTOPC the periodic fluctuations of output around the long run trend.
ENDSTOPD none of the above.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_19'>A lenders will gain at the expense of borrowers and employers will gain at the
expense of workers.
ENDSTOPB lenders will gain at the expense of borrowers and workers will gain at the
expense of employers.
ENDSTOPC borrowers will gain at the expense of lenders and employers will gain at the
expense of workers.
ENDSTOPD borrowers will gain at the expense of lenders and workers will gain at the
expense of employers.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_20'>A a rise in the value of the fiscal multiplier.
ENDSTOPB a decrease in the transactions demand for money.
ENDSTOPC a rise in the rate of interest.
ENDSTOPD an increase in the speculative demand for money.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_21'>A give an actual rate of unemployment which is temporarily greater than the
natural rate.
ENDSTOPB give an actual rate of unemployment which is temporarily lower than the
natural rate.
ENDSTOPC increase the natural rate of unemployment.
ENDSTOPD decrease the natural rate of unemployment.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_22'>A investment is determined by the rate of change of national income.
ENDSTOPB national income is determined by the rate of change of investment.
ENDSTOPC investment is increased when interest rates fall.
ENDSTOPD national income is increased when interest rates fall.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_23'>A an expansionary fiscal policy.
ENDSTOPB an expansionary monetary policy.
ENDSTOPC a contractionary fiscal policy.
ENDSTOPD a contractionary monetary policy.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_24'>A higher domestic interest rates and an appreciation of the domestic currency.
ENDSTOPB higher domestic interest rates and a depreciation of the domestic currency.
ENDSTOPC lower domestic interest rates and an appreciation of the domestic currency.
ENDSTOPD lower domestic interest rates and a depreciation of the domestic currency.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_25'>A increases in social security benefits designed to increase expenditures of
unemployed workers
ENDSTOPB measures designed to increase trade union powers so that real wage rises can
increase expenditures of employed workers
ENDSTOPC increases in Tariffs designed to increase production of domestic goods
ENDSTOPD reduction in corporate taxation</string>"
    "<string name='apr2018_choices_26'>A Exports become cheaper when measured in the foreign currency.
ENDSTOPB Imports become more expensive when measured in the domestic currency.
ENDSTOPC Export volumes will decrease.
ENDSTOPD Import volumes will decrease.</string>"



</resources>