<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name='apr2019_que_1'>Which one of the following results in a decrease in total consumer expenditure?</string>
    "<string name='apr2019_que_2'>If an economy moves from producing 10 units of Good X and 5 units of Good Y to
producing 8 units of Good X and 6 units of Good Y, the opportunity cost of the 6th
unit of Good Y is:</string>"
    <string name='apr2019_que_3'>Which one of the following will NOT shift the supply curve for Good X to the right?</string>
    "<string name='apr2019_que_4'>Good X has a price elasticity of demand equal to –1.5. In such circumstances, a per
unit sales tax on Good X of £5 will lead to which of the following?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_que_5'>Good Y has a cross elasticity of demand with respect to Good X calculated using the
average method of –1. Initially 100 units of Good Y are demanded when Good X
costs 20 pence. A rise in the price of Good X to 25 pence will result in a new level of
demand for Good Y of:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_que_6'>Making your selection from options A–D below, which of the following statements is
NOT correct in relation to the Austrian school of thought?
Economists following the Austrian school of thought:
(i) place emphasis on individual subjective preferences.
(ii) focus on market forces determining prices.
(iii) believe in a centrally planned economic system.</string>"
    <string name='apr2019_que_7'>Which one of the following is TRUE?</string>
    "<string name='apr2019_que_8'>A profit maximising monopoly facing a linear demand schedule and having positive
marginal costs will set its price in the region of the demand curve where the absolute
price elasticity of demand is:</string>"
    <string name='apr2019_que_9'>Which one of the following statements about market structure is FALSE?</string>
    <string name='apr2019_que_10'>Which one of the following is NOT a feature of perfect competition?</string>
    "<string name='apr2019_que_11'>A managing director of a monopoly firm with constant marginal costs has the
following data:
Average revenue = £15
Marginal revenue = £10
Marginal cost = £11
Average variable cost = £11
Average total cost = £13
To maximise profits/minimise losses in the short run the firm should:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_que_12'>If the price of Good X has risen and the quantity sold has increased, then there must
have been a:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_que_13'>A firm with fixed costs of £400 per week and constant average variable costs of £8 per
unit of output, has the following information about its weekly sales: Which of the following levels of output yields the highest profit?</string>"
    <string name='apr2019_que_14'>To calculate Gross National Income, you need to know all of the following EXCEPT:</string>
    "<string name='apr2019_que_15' tools:ignore="TypographyOther">In a simple closed economy with no government sector the consumption function
relating consumption expenditure (C) to income (Y) is given by the expression:
C = £40 million + 0.7 Y
Planned investment is constant at £50 million.
Which one of the following is TRUE?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_que_16'>If the money supply increases due to an expansionary open market operation by the
central bank, then the price of treasury bills will:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_que_17'>Which of the following are the correct responses for the missing words (i) and (ii) in
the following statement?
Automatic stabilisers act to (i) ________ government expenditures and (ii)________
government revenues during a recessionary period.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_que_18'>The following data is available on an economy:
Consumption Expenditure £70 million
Investment £20 million
Government Expenditure £40 million
Exports £20 million
Imports £30 million
Net Income from abroad £10 million
What is the value of its Gross National Income?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_que_19'>An economy with a floating exchange rate has a large deficit on the current account
of its balance of payments. Which policy combination would be most likely to reduce
this deficit?</string>"
    <string name='apr2019_que_20'>The narrow money supply (monetary base) is increased when:</string>
    "<string name='apr2019_que_21'>Which one of the following is NOT likely to happen following a devaluation of the
domestic currency on the foreign exchange market?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2019_que_22'>Which one of the following would NOT constitute a demand side economic policy for
reducing unemployment?</string>"
    <string name='apr2019_que_23'>Which of the following will increase the size of the multiplier?</string>
    "<string name='apr2019_que_24'>If an increase in the level of the money supply results in no change in either the
nominal or real value of national income, then which of the following is TRUE?</string>"
    <string name='apr2019_que_25'>One way of reducing the natural rate of unemployment would be to increase:</string>
    "<string name='apr2019_que_26'>If the central bank has to intervene in the foreign exchange market to prevent the
home currency from depreciating, then its foreign exchange reserves will:</string>"



</resources>