<resources>"<string name='apr2007_choices_1'>A There is insufficient quantity supplied at the equilibrium price.
ENDSTOPB There is not enough of it to satisfy all those who would want it at zero price.
ENDSTOPC The good’s demand and supply functions don’t meet.
ENDSTOPD It can’t be decided who should consume the good.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_2'>A The interaction of demand and supply solves the allocation problem.
ENDSTOPB The methods of production minimise the costs of production.
ENDSTOPC The goods produced are those for which the amount consumers are willing to
pay exceeds the costs of production.
ENDSTOPD The allocation problem is determined by an agency.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_3'>A a change in demand
ENDSTOPB an increase in demand
ENDSTOPC a decrease in demand
ENDSTOPD a change in quantity demanded</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_4'>A 2
ENDSTOPB ½
ENDSTOPC 50
ENDSTOPD impossible to calculate from the information given</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_5'>A Quantity effects will be large and price effects large.
ENDSTOPB Quantity effects will be small and price effects large.
ENDSTOPC Quantity effects will be large and price effects small.
ENDSTOPD Quantity effects will be small and price effects small.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_6'>A Demand is perfectly elastic where the quantity demanded is zero.
ENDSTOPB Demand is unit elastic at the midpoint of the curve.
ENDSTOPC Elasticity increases as the price falls and the quantity demanded rises.
ENDSTOPD Elasticity decreases as the price falls and the quantity demanded rises.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_7'>A 40
ENDSTOPB 20
ENDSTOPC 30
ENDSTOPD 80</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_8'>A constant returns to scale
ENDSTOPB decreasing returns to scale
ENDSTOPC increasing returns to scale
ENDSTOPD increasing marginal returns</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_9'>A Firm A – High; Firm B – LowENDSTOPB Firm A – High; Firm B – HighENDSTOPC Firm A – Low; Firm B – Low
ENDSTOPD Firm A – Low; Firm B – High</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_10'>A Prices are higher and output lower than the social optimum.
ENDSTOPB Prices are higher and output higher than the social optimum.
ENDSTOPC Prices are lower and output lower than the social optimum.
ENDSTOPD Prices are lower and output higher than the social optimum.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_11'>A exclude imports
ENDSTOPB subtract taxes and subtract subsidies
ENDSTOPC subtract taxes and add subsidies
ENDSTOPD add income from abroad</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_12'>A I + G + B + X + S ≡ Te - Td + ZENDSTOPB I + G + B + X ≡ Te + Td + Z+ SENDSTOPC I + G – B + S ≡ Te + Td + Z+ X
ENDSTOPD G + B + X + S + I ≡ Te + Td + Z</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_13'>A an increase in the country’s population
ENDSTOPB creation of a better transport infrastructure
ENDSTOPC full employment of all available resources
ENDSTOPD technological advances</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_14'>A altering the multiplier
ENDSTOPB reducing private sector investment
ENDSTOPC imposing price controls
ENDSTOPD increasing the money supply</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_15'>A The marginal tax rate is less than the average tax rate.
ENDSTOPB The marginal tax rate is equal to the average tax rate.
ENDSTOPC The marginal tax rate is greater than the average tax rate.
ENDSTOPD The marginal tax rate is zero.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_16'>A £600m
ENDSTOPB –£200m
ENDSTOPC £200m
ENDSTOPD impossible to determine from the information given</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_17'>A Gross National Product
ENDSTOPB National Income
ENDSTOPC Net Domestic Product
ENDSTOPD Net Capital Formation</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_18'>A a rise in the level of national income and fall in the interest rate
ENDSTOPB a fall in the level of national income and fall in the interest rate
ENDSTOPC a rise in the level of national income and rise in the interest rate
ENDSTOPD a fall in the level of national income and rise in the interest rate</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_19'>A Output of the firm is where marginal revenue equals marginal cost.
ENDSTOPB The cost curves of the firm are U-shaped.
ENDSTOPC Marginal revenue equals average revenue.
ENDSTOPD The marginal cost curve cuts the average cost curve at its minimum point.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_20'>A Good X will be exported to the rest of the world and the world price will fall
towards £20.
ENDSTOPB Good X will be imported from the rest of the world and the home price will
rise towards £22.
ENDSTOPC Good X will be imported from the rest of the world and the world price will
fall towards £20.
ENDSTOPD Good X will be exported to the rest of the world and the home price will rise
towards £22.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_21'>A can produce Good A using less labour than Country Y
ENDSTOPB has a higher opportunity cost of producing Good A than Country Y
ENDSTOPC has a lower opportunity cost of producing Good A than Country Y
ENDSTOPD is in a free trade area</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_22'>A £23bn
ENDSTOPB £18.6bn
ENDSTOPC £25.8bn
ENDSTOPD £15.8bn</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_23'>A 1.69
ENDSTOPB 1.47
ENDSTOPC 1.23
ENDSTOPD It is impossible to calculate from the information available.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_24'>A The real money supply will increase, interest rates will fall and employment
will increase
ENDSTOPB The real money supply will decrease, interest rates will fall and employment
will increase
ENDSTOPC The real money supply will decrease, interest rates will rise and
unemployment will increase
ENDSTOPD The real money supply will decrease, interest rates will fall and unemployment
will increase</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_25'>A Fiscal policy is more effective than monetary policy because interest rates are
allowed to fluctuate to prevent crowding out.
ENDSTOPB Monetary policy is more effective than fiscal policy because changes in
interest rates will reduce imports and encourage exports.
ENDSTOPC Fiscal policy is more effective than monetary policy because interest rates
cannot be allowed to rise and so crowding out cannot occur.
ENDSTOPD Monetary policy is more effective than fiscal policy because it permits the
government to lower the interest rate.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_choices_26'>A The long-run curve is vertical and the short-run curve slopes upwards.
ENDSTOPB The long run curve is vertical and the short-run curve slopes downwards.
ENDSTOPC Both the short-run and long-run curves slope downwards, but the short-run
curve is steeper than the long-run curve.
ENDSTOPD The long run curve is horizontal and the short-run curve slopes downwards.</string>"
</resources>