<resources>
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_1'>A Opportunity cost is equal to total revenue minus total variable cost.
ENDSTOPB Opportunity cost is constant.
ENDSTOPC Opportunity cost is the cost in terms of the best foregone alternative.
ENDSTOPD Opportunity cost is equal to a firm’s supernormal profits.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_2'>A Demand to watch football has a high price elasticity.
ENDSTOPB Consumer preference has changed in favour of watching football.
ENDSTOPC Demand to watch football has a very low price elasticity.
ENDSTOPD The prices of alternative attractions have fallen.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_3'>A rise.
ENDSTOPB be indeterminate.
ENDSTOPC fall.
ENDSTOPD remain unchanged.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_4'>A provide a means of allocating resources.
ENDSTOPB ensure that consumer wants are satisfied.
ENDSTOPC enable the government to control prices.
ENDSTOPD ensure the goods that society needs are produced.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_5'>A There would be a surplus on the market and bread producers’ income would
fall.
ENDSTOPB There would be an equilibrium in the market but the change in bread
producers’ income would be uncertain.
ENDSTOPC There would be a shortage on the market and bread producers’ income would
rise.
ENDSTOPD There would be a surplus on the market but the change in bread producers’
income would be uncertain.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_6'>A It is −1.
ENDSTOPB It is infinite elasticity.
ENDSTOPC It is +1.
ENDSTOPD It is zero elasticity.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_7'>A Firms expect future prices to rise.
ENDSTOPB At higher levels of output firms will incur higher costs.
ENDSTOPC The higher the price the more profitable it becomes to produce.
ENDSTOPD The price of a good remains high over a given time period.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_8'>A people are risk lovers.
ENDSTOPB people are risk averse.
ENDSTOPC people are risk diversifiers.
ENDSTOPD people are risk neutral.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_9'>A The curve will shift to the left and become more inelastic.
ENDSTOPB The curve will shift to the right and become less elastic.
ENDSTOPC The curve will shift to the left and become more elastic.
ENDSTOPD The curve will shift to the right and become less inelastic.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_10'>A Total revenue is less than total costs.
ENDSTOPB Total revenue is less than total fixed costs.
ENDSTOPC Average revenue is less than average fixed cost.
ENDSTOPD Average revenue is less than average variable cost.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_11'>A Firms are free to enter and leave the market.
ENDSTOPB Firms produce differentiated products.
ENDSTOPC Firms cannot earn abnormal profits in the short run.
ENDSTOPD There must be a large number of small firms.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_12'>A 2,000 units.
ENDSTOPB 1,750 units.
ENDSTOPC 250 units.
ENDSTOPD None of the above.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_13'>A increase their price and increase output.
ENDSTOPB lower their price and increase output.
ENDSTOPC increase their price and lower output.
ENDSTOPD lower their price and lower output.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_14'>A New markets
ENDSTOPB Risk sharing
ENDSTOPC Capital pooling
ENDSTOPD Economies of scale</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_15'>A 75
ENDSTOPB 120
ENDSTOPC 125
ENDSTOPD 150</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_16'>A comparative advantage.
ENDSTOPB absolute advantage.
ENDSTOPC different factor endowments.
ENDSTOPD all of the above.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_17'>A A decrease in interest rates.
ENDSTOPB A rise in exchange rates.
ENDSTOPC A rise in government expenditure.
ENDSTOPD An increase in business confidence.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_18'>A unemployment will fall.
ENDSTOPB the balance of trade will tend to improve.
ENDSTOPC inflation will tend to rise.
ENDSTOPD national income will rise.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_19'>A Frictional unemployment
ENDSTOPB Cyclical unemployment
ENDSTOPC Seasonal unemployment
ENDSTOPD Structural unemployment</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_20'>A £150 million
ENDSTOPB £130 million
ENDSTOPC £120 million
ENDSTOPD £110 million</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_21'>A Decrease interest rates and increase income tax rates.
ENDSTOPB Increase interest rates and leave income tax rates unchanged.
ENDSTOPC Decrease interest rates and decrease income tax rates.
ENDSTOPD Increase interest rates and increase income tax rates.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_22'>A Visible payments
ENDSTOPB Income flows
ENDSTOPC Portfolio investment
ENDSTOPD Direct investment</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_23'>A Lower the bank’s liquidity ratio and increase the bank deposits multiplier.
ENDSTOPB Increase the bank’s liquidity ratio and lower the bank deposits multiplier.
ENDSTOPC Lower the bank’s liquidity ratio and leave the bank deposits multiplier
unchanged.
ENDSTOPD The effect on the bank’s liquidity ratio and the bank deposits multiplier will be
uncertain.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_24'>A An increase in the frequency of payments to individuals.
ENDSTOPB An increase in real Gross Domestic Product.
ENDSTOPC A decrease in the rate of interest.
ENDSTOPD An increase in prices.</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_25'>A Inflation and the exchange rate
ENDSTOPB Economic growth and unemployment
ENDSTOPC Inflation and economic growth
ENDSTOPD Unemployment and the exchange rate</string>"
    "<string name='apr2011_choices_26'>A governments are pursuing an expansionary monetary policy.
ENDSTOPB high rates of interest are discouraging borrowing.
ENDSTOPC banks are not holding excess cash reserves.
ENDSTOPD all proceeds of loans are re-deposited with banks.</string>"
</resources>