<resources>
    <string name='apr2009_que_1'>The main categories of economic resources are:</string>
    <string name='apr2009_que_2'>In economics the concept of scarcity means:</string>
    <string name='apr2009_que_3'>The UK economy is:</string>
    "<string name='apr2009_que_4'>If the government chooses to use resources to build a nuclear power plant instead of
building new wind farms, this illustrates the concept of:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_que_5'>Which one of the following will have no impact on the position of the production
possibility frontier?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_que_6'>Assume two countries, with the same level of technology and resources, do not
presently trade. In Country X one unit of labour and one unit of capital can produce
20 units of Good A or 15 units of Good B. In Country Y one unit of labour and one
unit of capital can produce 50 units of Good A or 25 units of Good B. Which of the following is TRUE?</string>"
    <string name='apr2009_que_7'>An increase in the price of eggs will:</string>
    <string name='apr2009_que_8'>Which of the following statements is TRUE?</string>
    "<string name='apr2009_que_9'>Wheat is an essential input in the production of pasta. An increase in the price of
wheat would have an impact on the demand and supply of pasta by:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_que_10'>If ice cream is a substitute for fruit sorbet and strawberries are a complement to icecream
but not sorbet then a fall in the price of ice cream will:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_que_11'>According to the law of diminishing marginal utility, the total satisfaction that a
consumer receives from consuming Good X will:</string>"
    <string name='apr2009_que_12'>In relation to insurance, the term moral hazard:</string>
    <string name='apr2009_que_13'>Which of the following is a feature of an oligopolistic market structure?</string>
    "<string name='apr2009_que_14'>A profit maximizing monopolist is currently operating at a level of output where
marginal revenue is greater than marginal cost. The monopolist should:</string>"
    <string name='apr2009_que_15'>In long-run equilibrium under monopolistic competition:</string>
    <string name='apr2009_que_16'>Gross National Income is equal to:</string>
    <string name='apr2009_que_17'>Which one of the following is NOT true?</string>
    "<string name='apr2009_que_18'>If a household’s disposable income increases from £35,000 to £40,000 and its
consumption expenditure increases from £30,000 to £32,000 then the marginal
propensity to consume is:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_que_19'>If the marginal propensity to consume is 0.8 and there are no taxes or trade what is the
simple autonomous expenditure multiplier?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_que_20'>A country with a population of 38 million has 32 million in employment and 2 million
unemployed. What is the unemployment rate?</string>"
    <string name='apr2009_que_21'>Which one of the following statements about the demand for money is FALSE?</string>
    <string name='apr2009_que_22'>Which of the following is a potential source of cost push inflation?</string>
    "<string name='apr2009_que_23'>The record of a country’s transactions in goods and services and assets with the rest of
the world is referred to as its:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_que_24'>The US has been running a large current account deficit, and China has a large current
account surplus. If their exchange rates were both flexible, how would such
imbalances be eliminated?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2009_que_25'>The idea that exchange rates adjust so that standard goods, such as a BIG MAC©, will
cost the same in the USA as in the UK is called:</string>"
    <string name='apr2009_que_26'>With a floating exchange rate system, monetary policy is:</string>

</resources>