<resources><string name='apr2007_que_1'>A resource can be considered scarce if:</string>
    <string name='apr2007_que_2'>Which of the following is NOT true of a free market economy?</string>
    <string name='apr2007_que_3'>A movement along a demand curve is best described as:</string>
    "<string name='apr2007_que_4'>Given that an individual’s income has decreased from £100 to £90 and the quantity of
a Good X demanded has fallen from 25 to 20, the income elasticity of demand for
Good X is:</string>"
    <string name='apr2007_que_5'>When demand for a good is elastic then:</string>
    <string name='apr2007_que_6'>Along a straight-line demand curve which of the following is FALSE?</string>
    <string name='apr2007_que_7'>A firm uses labour as an input to production and finds the following relationship: The marginal product of the second hour’s labour is:</string>
    "<string name='apr2007_que_8'>Which concept does the following table demonstrate, given that all other factors are
held constant other than the amount of labour employed?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_que_9'>Two firms operate in a duopoly, but do not collude. Given the pay-off matrix of
output options to firms A and B below, what is the dominant strategy for the firms?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_que_10'>Monopolies can be considered detrimental to society since they lead to a social cost.
This is because they profit maximise at a level of output and price different from the
socially optimal output and price. The monopolist produces where:</string>"
    <string name='apr2007_que_11'>To transform GDP from market prices to basic prices it is necessary to:</string>
    "<string name='apr2007_que_12'>The circular flow of income model is balanced and has injections equal to leakages
when:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_que_13'>Which of the following would NOT cause a country’s production possibility frontier
to move outwards?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_que_14'>Following an expansionary fiscal policy to boost national income, a government can
avoid Keynesian crowding out by:</string>"
    <string name='apr2007_que_15'>A regressive tax is one where:</string>
    "<string name='apr2007_que_16'>GDP at market prices is £1,400m. Consumption is known to be £800m, government
expenditure £200m and net imports -£200m. What is the level of investment?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_que_17'>By accounting for the depreciation of capital assets used in production the measure
for GDP is transformed to:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_que_18'>Starting at the equilibrium position of a standard IS-LM analysis with a fixed money
supply, a fiscal contraction will lead to:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_que_19'>Which of the following conditions indicates that a firm is operating in a perfectly
competitive industry, rather than a monopolistic industry?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_que_20'>There are no restrictions on world trade. Good X is produced both at home and abroad
without constraints on further supply. In the home country it is priced at £20 while the
world price is £22. Which of the following will occur?</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_que_21'>Country X will have a comparative advantage over Country Y in producing Good A
when Country X:</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_que_22'>Given the information available below, what must be the capital account balance?
Visible plus invisible transactions balance: -£20.8bn
Official financing: £3.6bn
Balancing item: £1.4bn</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_que_23'>What will be the real value of the Euro / £ (sterling) exchange rate if:
Index of UK prices = 118
Index of Euro-area prices = 110
Nominal Euro / £ (sterling) exchange rate = 1.58
UK marginal tax rate = 0.15</string>"
    "<string name='apr2007_que_24'>Wage negotiations are under way and workers and employers anticipate the price
inflation rate to be 8% and the money supply to increase by 8%. As a result wages
are increased by 8% to maintain equilibrium. The government plans to increase the
money supply by 4%, but only they know this. What will be the outcome?</string>"
    <string name='apr2007_que_25'>With a fixed system of exchange rates:</string>
    "<string name='apr2007_que_26'>For a Phillips curve with unemployment on the x-axis and inflation on the y-axis,
which of the following statements is correct?</string>"
</resources>