<resources>
    <string name="question_1">In economics, the problem of scarcity:</string>
    <string name="question_2">What is the combined effect of a fall in the cost of production and a fall in consumer
    income on the equilibrium price and quantity of a normal good?</string>
    <string name="question_3">Economies of scale means:</string>
    <string name="question_4">Which of the following does NOT necessarily apply to a perfectly competitive firm
    that produces in both the short run and the long run?</string>
    <string name="question_5">The prisoner’s dilemma, applied to a situation involving two oligopolistic firms,
    illustrates that:</string>
    <string name="question_6">The welfare consequences of third-degree price discrimination are to the benefit of:</string>
    <string name="question_7">The demand for Good X has a price elasticity of -1. Tax on Good X is £10 per unit. If
    the government decides to reduce the tax on Good X to £5 per unit, this would shift
    the supply curve for Good X down by:</string>
    <string name="question_8">An economy moves from producing 15 units of Good X and six units of Good Y to
    instead producing 16 units of Good X and three units of Good Y. How many units of
    Good Y is the opportunity cost of the 16th unit of Good X?</string>
    <string name="question_9">Which of the following best describes an annual demand curve?</string>
    <string name="question_10">If a maximum price for Good X is fixed above the market equilibrium price, there will
    be:</string>
    <string name="question_11">A firm’s short-run total costs are £250 when ten units are produced and its total
    variable costs are £100. The marginal cost of producing the tenth unit is £27 and the
    marginal cost of producing the eleventh unit is £23. Which of the following is TRUE?</string>
    <string name="question_12">Skipped</string>
    <string name="question_13">Global Airways, which is a profit-maximising firm, has to decide whether or not to
    run an extra daily flight between London and Manchester. The total daily fixed costs
    of the airline are £4,000, the total variable costs of the extra flight are £4,500 and the
    expected average revenue from the extra flight is £50 with 85 passengers. In such
    circumstances, Global Airways will:</string>
    <string name="question_14">Good X is an inferior good (but not a Giffen good). If a budget line is drawn with
    quantity of Good Y on the vertical axis and quantity of Good X on the horizontal axis, a
    fall in price of Good X will cause the budget line of the consumer to:</string>
    <string name="question_15">Which of the following could explain why a country’s aggregate demand curve may
    shift inwards to the left?</string>
    <string name="question_16">Which of the following statements about real variables in the economy is TRUE?</string>
    <string name="question_17">In an economy operating significantly below the full employment level of output, the
    adoption of an expansionary fiscal policy combined with a contractionary monetary
    policy will result in:</string>
    <string name="question_18">Which one of the following would NOT constitute a supply-side economic policy for
    reducing unemployment?</string>
    <string name="question_19">In a simple closed economy with no taxes, consumption is given by the relationship:
    C = £50 million + 0.6 Y
    where C is consumption expenditure and Y is GDP.
    If government expenditure is £100 million and investment is £50 million, what will be
    the equilibrium value of GDP of the economy?</string>
    <string name="question_20">Which one of the following is most likely to lead to cost-push inflation?</string>
    <string name="question_21">Other things remaining the same, in a closed economy, the effect of a cut in
    government expenditure is to:</string>
    <string name="question_22">Assume that the actual rate of unemployment is below the natural rate of
    unemployment because the expected rate of inflation is below the actual rate of
    inflation. If the expected rate of inflation rises to equal the actual rate of inflation,
    then real wage growth will start to:</string>
    <string name="question_23">Which of the following is the correct response for the missing words, (i) and (ii), in
    the statement below?
    Automatic stabilisers act to ___(i) ___ government expenditures and ___(ii)___
    government revenues during a recession.</string>
    <string name="question_24">In a closed economy, planned investment is £20 million, government expenditure is
    £40 million, planned savings are £15 million and taxes are £25 million. Which of the
    following is most likely to occur?</string>
    <string name="question_25">According to the quantity theory of money, an increase in the money supply is least
    likely to lead to inflation if the:</string>
    <string name="question_26">Other things being equal in an economy with zero economic growth, if the expected
    rate of inflation on which wage settlements are based is 3% p.a. and the money supply
    is increasing at 4% p.a., then there will be a short-run:</string>




    </resources>