<resources>
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_1'>A The effect on price is indeterminate but quantity will fall.
ENDSTOPB The effect on price is indeterminate but quantity will rise.
ENDSTOPC The effect on quantity is indeterminate but price will rise.
ENDSTOPD The effect on quantity is indeterminate but price will fall.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_2'>A The cost of producing Good X in money terms.
ENDSTOPB The next best alternative use to which the factors of production used to produce
Good X could be put.
ENDSTOPC The stream of services provided by Good X over its entire lifetime.
ENDSTOPD The production of Good X foregone in the previous year to enable Good X to be
produced this year.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_3'>A attempts to maximise sales after assuming that the other firm will attempt to
maximise sales.
ENDSTOPB assumes the other firm will produce a given output and then chooses its profit
maximising output.
ENDSTOPC assumes the other firm’s price is given and then chooses its profit maximising
price.
ENDSTOPD will attempt to collude with the other firm so as to set a price and output level
which will maximise industry level profits.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_4'>A Significant economies of scale.
ENDSTOPB Heavy potential advertising costs.
ENDSTOPC Large capital requirements.
ENDSTOPD Constant returns to scale.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_5'>A The demand for air travel is price inelastic.
ENDSTOPB The demand for air travel is price elastic.
ENDSTOPC The demand for air travel is infinitely price elastic.
ENDSTOPD The demand for air travel has zero price inelasticity.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_6'>A reduce price and increase output.
ENDSTOPB reduce price and reduce output.
ENDSTOPC increase price and increase output.
ENDSTOPD increase price and reduce output.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_7'>A not run the extra flight as it will expect to lose £2,500 from its profits.
ENDSTOPB not run the extra flight as its expected profit of £500 is insufficient to cover its
fixed costs.
ENDSTOPC run the extra flight as it will add £500 to its profits.
ENDSTOPD not run the extra flight as the expected revenue of £2,500 is less than its fixed
costs.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_8'>A costs of entry and exit are zero and potential entrants can enter the market
quickly.
ENDSTOPB existing companies charge identical prices.
ENDSTOPC the barriers to entry are substantial but the existing firms compete so hard that
industry profits are kept to the normal level over both the short and long run.
ENDSTOPD existing firms compete on price and quality so as to maximise industry abnormal
profits in the long run.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_9'>A has price elasticity equal to minus unity.
ENDSTOPB is price inelastic.
ENDSTOPC is price elastic.
ENDSTOPD has price elasticity equal to zero.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_10'>A shift the supply curve for Good X up by less than £10 and increase the price by
less than £10.
ENDSTOPB shift the supply curve for Good X up by less than £10 and increase the price by
more than £10.
ENDSTOPC shift the supply curve for Good X up by £10 and increase the price by £10.
ENDSTOPD shift the supply curve for Good X up by £10 and increase the price by less than
£10.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_11'>A A bank, by raising its interest rates, will tend to increase the proportion of
borrowers in its loan portfolio who do not intend to repay their loans.
ENDSTOPB An insurance company by inserting extra clauses into an insurance contract will
tend to reduce its customer base.
ENDSTOPC Bank directors will tend to act in their own interests rather than that of their
shareholders.
ENDSTOPD An insurance policy with a 2 year time horizon is more likely to have a claim
made against it than an insurance policy with a 1 year time horizon.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_12'>A economies of scale
ENDSTOPB constant returns to scale
ENDSTOPC diseconomies of scale
ENDSTOPD diminishing marginal productivity</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_13'>A Under perfect competition, in the long run only some firms can make excess
profits.
ENDSTOPB Under oligopoly all firms make decisions without taking into account the
possible reactions of their competitors.
ENDSTOPC For a monopolist facing a linear demand curve, average revenue is always less
than marginal revenue.
ENDSTOPD Firms under monopolistic competition charge a price above their marginal
revenue.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_14'>A Increasing social security benefits.
ENDSTOPB Increasing the money supply.
ENDSTOPC Reducing corporate and personal taxation.
ENDSTOPD Increasing government expenditure aimed at exploiting the multiplier effect.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_15'>A Moral hazard describes the fact that people who know that they are a particularly
bad risk are more inclined to take out insurance.
ENDSTOPB Moral hazard describes the fact that a policyholder may act in a way which
makes the insured event more likely to occur.
ENDSTOPC Moral hazard describes the fact that people who know that they are a particularly
bad risk are less inclined to take out insurance.
ENDSTOPD Moral hazard describes the risk that an insurance company will face false
insurance claims.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_16'>A savings, taxes and investment are withdrawals.
ENDSTOPB savings, imports and taxes are withdrawals.
ENDSTOPC investment, government expenditure and imports are injections.
ENDSTOPD investment, exports and consumption are injections.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_17'>A salaries of school teachers
ENDSTOPB net income from abroad
ENDSTOPC company profits
ENDSTOPD investment expenditure</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_18'>A If nominal Gross Domestic Product (GDP) rises by 5 per cent then the real GDP
may have risen, fallen or remained unchanged.
ENDSTOPB A nominal depreciation of a country’s exchange rate represents a real
depreciation if the domestic inflation rate is less than the foreign inflation rate.
ENDSTOPC An increase in real income will lead to a rise in the demand for real money
balances.
ENDSTOPD Real interest rates are positive if the expected rate of inflation is greater than the
nominal rate of interest.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_19'>A £200 million
ENDSTOPB £312.5 million
ENDSTOPC £1,000 million
ENDSTOPD £800 million</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_20'>A decreases and national income is lower.
ENDSTOPB decreases and national income is higher.
ENDSTOPC increases and national income is lower.
ENDSTOPD increases and national income is higher.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_21'>A add net income from abroad and deduct transfer payments.
ENDSTOPB deduct net income from abroad and add capital depreciation.
ENDSTOPC add net income from abroad.
ENDSTOPD add net income from abroad and deduct capital depreciation.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_22'>A rise as the short term interest rate rises.
ENDSTOPB rise as the short term interest rate falls.
ENDSTOPC fall as the short term interest rate rises.
ENDSTOPD fall as the short term interest rate falls.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_23'>A higher domestic interest rates and an exchange rate appreciation.
ENDSTOPB higher domestic interest rates and an exchange rate depreciation.
ENDSTOPC lower domestic interest rates and an exchange rate appreciation.
ENDSTOPD lower domestic interest rates and an exchange rate depreciation.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_24'>A £250 million
ENDSTOPB £260 million
ENDSTOPC £270 million
ENDSTOPD £280 million</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_25'>A Country A has a comparative advantage and an absolute advantage in producing
Good Y.
ENDSTOPB Country B has a comparative advantage in producing Good X and an absolute
advantage in producing Good Y.
ENDSTOPC Country A has a comparative advantage in producing Good X and an absolute
advantage in producing Good Y.
ENDSTOPD Country B has a comparative advantage in producing Good Y and an absolute
advantage in producing Good X.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_choices_26'>A increasing its net liabilities and/or increasing its net assets.
ENDSTOPB decreasing its net liabilities and/or increasing its net assets.
ENDSTOPC increasing its net liabilities and/or decreasing its net assets.
ENDSTOPD decreasing its net liabilities and/or decreasing its net assets.</string>"

</resources>