<resources>
    <string name='sep2017_que_1'>Which of the following statements defines adverse selection in relation to insurance?</string>
    "<string name='sep2017_que_2'>Which of the following is NOT usually given as a reason why firms form strategic
alliances?</string>"
    <string name='sep2017_que_3'>Third degree price discrimination refers to the situation where:</string>
    "<string name='sep2017_que_4'>Good X has a cross elasticity of demand with respect to Good Y which is equal to
minus unity (i.e. –1). Good X is which of the following with respect to Good Y?</string>"
    <string name='sep2017_que_5'>Which of the following is NOT a characteristic of an inferior good?</string>
    "<string name='sep2017_que_6'>If the government chooses to use resources to build a hospital instead of a school, this
illustrates the concept of:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_que_7'>Which of the following is NOT a motive for advertising by an existing firm in an
industry?</string>"
    <string name='sep2017_que_8'>Which of the following statements about short run costs of production is FALSE?</string>
    <string name='sep2017_que_9'>A firm that produces a main product and a by-product will maximise profits if it:</string>
    <string name='sep2017_que_10'>Which of the following statements is FALSE?</string>
    "<string name='sep2017_que_11'>When a monopolist maximises profits, price exceeds marginal revenue. The
difference between price and marginal revenue occurs because:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_que_12'>Which one of the following characteristics applies to an oligopolistic market
structure?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_que_13'>An implicit or explicit agreement amongst firms in an industry NOT to compete with
each other is known as:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_que_14'>Which of the following will result in an improvement in the domestic country’s terms
of trade?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_que_15'>Which one of the following will occur, assuming spare capacity within the economy,
if both government spending and the money supply are increased:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_que_16'>Which one of the following is NOT a “crowding out” effect resulting from a fiscal
expansion?</string>"
    <string name='sep2017_que_17'>The socially efficient output for a monopoly is at the point where:</string>
    "<string name='sep2017_que_18'>Which of the following would constitute a supply side economic policy for reducing
unemployment?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_que_19'>A government’s attempts to increase the monetary base (narrow money supply)
through open market operations are likely to cause short term interest rates to:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_que_20' formatted="false">The nominal rate of interest is 2% and the expected rate of inflation is positive at 3%.
Which one of the following is TRUE?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_que_21'>All other things being equal, which of the following events would cause the value of
Country A’s currency to appreciate against the value of Country B’s currency?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_que_22'>If the central bank has to intervene in the foreign exchange markets to prevent the
domestic currency from appreciating, then its foreign exchange reserves will:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_que_23'>The unemployment rate, expressed as a percentage, is given by the number of
unemployed divided by:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_que_24'>If unemployment is above the natural level, the long run Phillips curve would suggest
that, other things remaining the same, real wages would:</string>"
    <string name='sep2017_que_25'>The Phillips curve shows that:</string>
    "<string name='sep2017_que_26'>Which of the following does NOT form part of a country’s Gross Domestic Product
(GDP)?</string>"



</resources>