<resources>
    <string name='sep2015_que_1'>Scarcity exists if:</string>
    <string name='sep2015_que_2'>Which of the following statements is always TRUE?</string>
    <string name='sep2015_que_3'>Which of the following will NOT cause a shift in the demand curve for Good X?</string>
    "<string name='sep2015_que_4'>If public transport is an inferior good, which of the following will cause its demand
curve to shift to the left?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_que_5'>Consumer A has a higher income than Consumer B but they have identical
preferences and pay the same prices for the goods which they consume. If they both
maximise utility then the marginal utility from each good consumed will be:</string>"
    <string name='sep2015_que_6'>Adverse selection refers to a situation where:</string>
    <string name='sep2015_que_7'>Vertical product differentiation refers to differences between products which reflect:</string>
    "<string name='sep2015_que_8'>A firm’s fixed costs are £1,000 per period, the average total cost of its output is £4
and its average variable cost is £3.50. Which one of the following will represent its
total output per period?</string>"
    <string name='sep2015_que_9'>Increasing long run average costs are associated with:</string>
    <string name='sep2015_que_10'>The short run supply curve for a firm in a perfectly competitive industry is its:</string>
    "<string name='sep2015_que_11'>In the long run, profit maximising firms operating under conditions of monopolistic
competition will produce at a level of output where price equals:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_que_12'>Which of the following is NOT usually given as a reason why firms form strategic
alliances?</string>"
    <string name='sep2015_que_13'>Third degree price discrimination refers to the situation where:</string>
    <string name='sep2015_que_14'>The short run Phillips curve shows:</string>
    "<string name='sep2015_que_15'>Assume two countries, with the same level of technology and resources, do not
presently trade. In Country X one unit of labour and one unit of capital can produce
20 units of Good A or 15 units of Good B. In Country Y one unit of labour and one
unit of capital can produce 50 units of Good A or 25 units of Good B. Which of the following is TRUE?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_que_16'>The need to employ workers with certain skills may decline even if the industry as a
whole is not in decline. This form of unemployment is called:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_que_17'>A country with a population of 38 million has 32 million in employment and 2 million
unemployed. What is the unemployment rate?</string>"
    <string name='sep2015_que_18'>Which one of the following is NOT a cause of cost push inflation?</string>
    "<string name='sep2015_que_19'>Assuming all other variables remain constant, a decrease in the average price level
will result in a:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_que_20'>Which one of the following will NOT happen following a devaluation of the domestic
currency on the foreign exchange market?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_que_21'>If the central bank has to intervene in the foreign exchange markets to prevent the
home currency from appreciating, then its foreign exchange reserves will:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_que_22'>The direct impact of open market operations, where the central bank purchases
government securities, is to:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_que_23'>Which of the following would cause the demand for money curve to shift inwards to
the left?</string>"
    <string name='sep2015_que_24'>The adoption of an expansionary fiscal policy will result in:</string>
    "<string name='sep2015_que_25'>The introduction of a restrictive monetary policy in an open economy operating with a
flexible exchange rate would most likely lead to:</string>"
    <string name='sep2015_que_26'>“Crowding out” describes the:</string>


</resources>