<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">"<string name='sep2007_que_1'>Good X has a cross elasticity of demand with respect to Good Y which is equal to unity.
Good X is which of the following with respect to Good Y?</string>"
    <string name='sep2007_que_2'>If Good X is an inferior good then a decrease in income will cause:</string>
    "<string name='sep2007_que_3'>Which of the following will result from a 10 per cent rise in the price of whisky, the
demand for which has an absolute price elasticity of demand equal to 2?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_que_4'>Consider the budget line of a consumer that consumes only two Goods X and Y, with
the quantity of Good X represented on the horizontal axis and the quantity of Good Y
represented on the vertical axis. If money income is held constant, a rise in the price
of Good X and a fall in the price of Good Y will:</string>"
    <string name='sep2007_que_5'>If Good X is a Giffen good then an increase in income will cause:</string>
    "<string name='sep2007_que_6'>Which one of the following corresponds to a situation of first order stochastic
dominance?</string>"
    <string name='sep2007_que_7'>Adverse selection means that:</string>
    "<string name='sep2007_que_8'>A monopolist increases sales from 8 units to 9 units by reducing price from £10 to £9.
The marginal revenue from the 9th unit sold is:</string>"
    <string name='sep2007_que_9'>Which one of the following statements is CORRECT?</string>
    <string name='sep2007_que_10'>A movement along a consumer’s indifference curve from right to left means that:</string>
    "<string name='sep2007_que_11'>The government has decided to increase the money supply. Which money measures
are affected?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_que_12'>Consider the following table: The price of labour is £100 per unit and the amount of capital is fixed.
The table illustrates which one of the following?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_que_13'>If a profit maximising firm is to continue operating in the short run, even though it is
making a loss, then its average total revenue must cover its:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_que_14'>A profit maximising oligopolist has marginal costs of £3 at all levels of output and
operates under the belief that the demand curve for its output is kinked at a price of
£10. Provided its marginal costs are between £2 and £4, it sells its commodity at a
price of £10. If new technology reduces its marginal cost to £1.50 at all levels of
output the firm should:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_que_15'>All other things being equal, which of the following will NOT increase the Public
Sector Borrowing Requirement?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_que_16'>In an open economy with a government sector, which one of the following conditions
will ensure a full employment level of output?
You are given that S = Planned savings, I = Planned investment, T = Taxation,
G = Government expenditure, M = Import expenditure and X = Export receipts</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_que_17'>You are given the following data on an economy in 2001 and 2007: The velocity of circulation is the same in both years.
According to the quantity theory of money what would be the value of the price level
in 2007?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_que_18' tools:ignore="TypographyOther">You are given that consumption expenditure (C) is related to current disposable
income (Yd) by the formula:
C = 10 + 0.8 Yd
If disposable income is 100 then the average propensity to consume is:</string>"
    <string name='sep2007_que_19'>Which of the following will decrease the size of the multiplier?</string>
    <string name='sep2007_que_20'>Which one of the following statements about real variables in the economy is FALSE?</string>
    <string name='sep2007_que_21'>Which one of the following is the most accurate description of the National Debt?</string>
    "<string name='sep2007_que_22'>Country A takes 10 man hours to produce one unit of Good X and 20 man hours to
produce one unit of Good Y. Country B takes 5 man hours to produce one unit of
Good X and 10 man hours to produce one unit of Good Y. Which one of the
following statements is TRUE?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_que_23'>Which one of the following would be observed following an expansionary open market
operation by the central bank?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_que_24'>You are given the following data on a country’s balance of payments with the rest of
the world (ROW): What are the values of the current account balance and capital account balance
respectively?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_que_25'>The central bank conducts an open market sale of treasury bills equivalent to £5
million. The commercial banks hold reserves equivalent to 5 per cent of their
deposits, while the public holds a cash to deposit ratio of 20 per cent. What is the
maximum that the broad money supply may fall as a result of the open market
operation?</string>"
    <string name='sep2007_que_26'>Other things being equal, which one of the following statements is ALWAYS TRUE?</string>
</resources>