<resources>"<string name='sep2005_choices_1'>A The cost of producing Good X in money terms.
ENDSTOPB The foregone output from the next best alternative use to which factors of
production used to produce Good X could be put.
ENDSTOPC The stream of services provided by Good X over its entire lifetime.
ENDSTOPD The production of Good X foregone in the previous year to enable Good X to
be produced this year.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_2'>A buyers can but are not willing to purchase at different prices
ENDSTOPB buyers are both willing and able to purchase at one particular price
ENDSTOPC will be supplied at different prices
ENDSTOPD buyers are both willing and able to purchase at different prices</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_3'>A more one consumes of Good X, the less utility one derives from the first unit
of consumption of Good X
ENDSTOPB total utility derived from the consumption of Good X increases by smaller
amounts for each extra unit of Good X consumed
ENDSTOPC marginal utility derived from the consumption of an extra unit of Good X falls
if the price of Good X falls
ENDSTOPD marginal utility derived from the consumption of an extra unit of Good X falls
if the price of Good X rises</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_4'>A supply is zero
ENDSTOPB supply is infinite
ENDSTOPC demand is zero
ENDSTOPD demand is 1</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_5'>A A fall in consumers incomes.
ENDSTOPB A rise in the price of a complementary good.
ENDSTOPC A fall in the price of a substitute good.
ENDSTOPD A rise in the price of the normal good.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_6'>A The demand curve has a positive slope.
ENDSTOPB The income effect on demand of a price change will affect demand in the
opposite direction to the substitution effect.
ENDSTOPC The substitution effect of a fall in price of the good will lead to a fall in
demand.
ENDSTOPD Demand falls if income increases, other things being equal.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_7'>A achieve a greater average revenue than if it charged a single price
ENDSTOPB achieve lower total production costs per unit of output
ENDSTOPC increase its profits and simultaneously lower its profit maximising output
ENDSTOPD increase its profits by reducing its production costs more than its total revenue</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_8'>A remain unchanged
ENDSTOPB shift to the right but not change slope
ENDSTOPC shift to the right and become steeper
ENDSTOPD shit to the right and become less steep</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_9'>A If more labour is added to a given amount of capital, the marginal product of
labour remains unchanged.
ENDSTOPB If the ratio of labour to capital doubles, the output of the firm also doubles.
ENDSTOPC If both the input of capital and labour doubles, output remains constant.
ENDSTOPD If the input of capital and labour doubles, the ratio of output to inputs is
unchanged.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_10'>A Some degree of monopoly power ensures that in the long run firms can make
supernormal profits.
ENDSTOPB There is freedom of entry and exit into the industry.
ENDSTOPC Firms in the industry produce differentiated products.
ENDSTOPD Firms in the industry charge prices above their marginal costs of production.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_11'>A will seek to make only satisfactory rather than maximum profits
ENDSTOPB has a discontinuity in its marginal revenue curve
ENDSTOPC has a discontinuity in its marginal cost curve
ENDSTOPD has a discontinuity in its average revenue curve</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_12'>A most people risk averse
ENDSTOPB most people risk neutral
ENDSTOPC most people risk loving
ENDSTOPD none of the above</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_13'>A average cost curve
ENDSTOPB average variable cost curve
ENDSTOPC marginal cost curve above the lowest point of the average total cost curve
ENDSTOPD marginal cost curve above the lowest point of the average variable cost curve</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_14'>A The purchase of a £1,000 United Kingdom government bond.
ENDSTOPB A museum purchases an 18th century work of art.
ENDSTOPC A firm increases the quantity of cars it holds as stock.
ENDSTOPD A firm places £1 million of its surplus funds with a United Kingdom bank in a
high interest account.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_15'>A £166 million
ENDSTOPB £200 million
ENDSTOPC £500 million
ENDSTOPD £1,000 million</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_16'>A rise and real GDP will fall
ENDSTOPB stay the same and real GDP will rise
ENDSTOPC rise and real GDP will rise
ENDSTOPD fall and real GDP will rise</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_17'>A The multiplier has a value of 4.
ENDSTOPB An increase in the income level will raise the marginal propensity to consume.
ENDSTOPC The economy is in equilibrium if output is £200 million.
ENDSTOPD None of the above.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_18'>A A decrease in government expenditure.
ENDSTOPB A decrease in the income tax rate.
ENDSTOPC An increase autonomous savings.
ENDSTOPD A increase in the rate of interest.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_19'>A £150 million
ENDSTOPB £200 million
ENDSTOPC £450 million
ENDSTOPD none of the above</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_20'>A 0 per cent
ENDSTOPB 10 per cent
ENDSTOPC 10 per cent times the velocity of circulation
ENDSTOPD 10 per cent divided by the velocity of circulation</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_21'>A reduce output and increase employment
ENDSTOPB reduce output and employment
ENDSTOPC increase output and reduce employment
ENDSTOPD increase output and employment</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_22'>A inflation and economic growth
ENDSTOPB inflation and unemployment
ENDSTOPC inflation and balance of payments equilibrium
ENDSTOPD inflation and a stable exchange rate</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_23'>A higher domestic interest rates and an exchange rate appreciation
ENDSTOPB higher domestic interest rates and an exchange rate depreciation
ENDSTOPC lower domestic interest rates and an exchange rate appreciation
ENDSTOPD lower domestic interest rates and an exchange rate depreciation</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_24'>A £50 million in surplus
ENDSTOPB £50 million in deficit
ENDSTOPC £250 million in deficit
ENDSTOPD £350 million in deficit</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_25'>A exports will become less competitive
ENDSTOPB imports will become more expensive
ENDSTOPC inflation will rise
ENDSTOPD export volumes will rise</string>"
    "<string name='sep2005_choices_26'>A Country B has a comparative advantage in the production of both wine and
clothENDSTOPB Country A has a comparative advantage in the production of wine and
Country B has a comparative advantage in the production of clothENDSTOPC Country A has a comparative advantage in the production of cloth and
Country B has a comparative advantage in the production of wine
ENDSTOPD neither country has a comparative advantage in the production of either wine
or cloth</string>"
</resources>