<resources>
    <string name='sep2020_que_1'>Which of the following will NOT shift the supply curve for Good X to the right?</string>
    <string name='sep2020_que_2'>Which of the following best describes the opportunity cost of producing Good X?</string>
    <string name='sep2020_que_3'>Under the Cournot model of duopoly, a firm:</string>
    <string name='sep2020_que_4'>Which of the following is NOT a feature of monopolistic competition?</string>
    "<string name='sep2020_que_5'>Following an increase in the price of fuel, there is a 20% increase in the price of air
travel tickets that results in a 20% decrease in total revenue.
Which of the following statements is TRUE about the demand for air travel?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_que_6'>A consumer uses only two goods, X and Y. Currently the marginal utility of the last
unit of Good X consumed is six times as great as the marginal utility of the last unit of
Good Y consumed. The price of Good X is three times that of Good Y. To maximise
utility, the consumer should:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_que_7'>When a consumer with a given income chooses between two goods with fixed prices,
the slope of the budget line is equal to the:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_que_8'>A perfectly competitive firm is currently producing 2,000 units of Good X per week
that are sold at £3 per unit. The firm’s total cost is currently £12,000 per week of
which £4,000 is the fixed cost per week. The marginal cost of production is £3 per
unit. To maximise profits or minimise losses, the firm should:</string>"
    <string name='sep2020_que_9'>The short run supply curve for a firm in a perfectly competitive industry is its:</string>
    "<string name='sep2020_que_10'>The demand for Good X has a price elasticity of –3 while the supply curve has a
positive slope. If the government decided to impose a tax of £10 per unit on Good X,
this would shift the supply curve for Good X up by:</string>"
    <string name='sep2020_que_11'>Which of the following is an example of economies of scope?</string>
    <string name='sep2020_que_12'>Consider the following table: The table illustrates which one of the following?</string>
    <string name='sep2020_que_13'>An “inferior good” is defined as a good:</string>
    "<string name='sep2020_que_14'>Which of the following would constitute a supply side economic policy for reducing
unemployment?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_que_15'>An increase in the natural rate of unemployment will cause the long run Phillips curve
to:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_que_16'>According to Keynesian analysis, once a closed economy is in macroeconomic
equilibrium such that planned savings equals planned investment, then:</string>"
    <string name='sep2020_que_17'>An increase in the general price level with no change in the money supply will:</string>
    "<string name='sep2020_que_18'>Which one of the following statements about real variables in the economy is
FALSE?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_que_19'>In a simple economy, consumption is given by the relationship:
C = 0.75 Y
where C is consumption expenditure and Y is Gross Domestic Product (GDP).
If government expenditure is £150 million, investment is £50 million and there is no
taxation or international trade, the equilibrium value of GDP of the economy will be:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_que_20'>In Country A, government expenditure is £350 billion, tax revenue is £275 billion,
aggregate saving is £300 billion and aggregate investment is £250 billion. The net
exports of Country A are equal to a:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_que_21'>The proportion of deposits held by the public as cash is 0.5 and the proportion of
deposits held by the banks for reserves is 0.5. If the broad money supply is £300
million, what is the value of the narrow money supply?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_que_22'>If the money supply increases due to an expansionary open market operation by the
central bank, then the price of treasury bills will:</string>"
    <string name='sep2020_que_23'>The Phillips curve shows:</string>
    <string name='sep2020_que_24'>You are given the following data for an economy: The value of the economy’s Gross National Income at market prices is:</string>
    "<string name='sep2020_que_25'>Given the Gross Domestic Product (GDP) at basic prices cost we can calculate the
GDP at market prices by:</string>"
    <string name='sep2020_que_26'>Which of the following statements is NOT correct in relation to Say’s Law?</string>



</resources>