<resources>
    <string name='sep2010_que_1'>According to the accelerator principle investment expenditure will:</string>
    <string name='sep2010_que_2'>A firm that produces a main product and a by-product will maximise profits if it:</string>
    <string name='sep2010_que_3'>If Goods X and Y are substitutes, an increase in the price of Good X causes the:</string>
    <string name='sep2010_que_4'>Which of the following is not a characteristic of an inferior good?</string>
    "<string name='sep2010_que_5'>The price elasticity of demand for beer is –2. If beer increases in price by 15 per cent
the quantity demanded falls by:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_que_6'>If a firm incurs a total cost of £874 when it produces 10 units of output and a total
cost of £950 when it produces 11 units of output, the marginal cost of the 11th unit is:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_que_7'>Suppose that in a firm the amount of capital and plant size are fixed. With 10 workers,
the firm can produce 180 units of output and with 11 workers 190 units of output,
then the:</string>"
    <string name='sep2010_que_8'>Increasing long run average costs are associated with:</string>
    "<string name='sep2010_que_9'>A firm operating in a perfectly competitive industry uses the least cost combination of
the two factors of production capital and labour to produce its output. The price per
unit of capital and labour are £8 and £200 respectively. If the marginal physical
product of labour is 10, then the marginal physical product of capital is:</string>"
    <string name='sep2010_que_10'>Which one of the following defines the economic growth rate?</string>
    "<string name='sep2010_que_11'>In an economy, economic agents have a marginal propensity to save of 0.25, an
income of £200 million and an autonomous expenditure of £15 million. The level of
consumption will be:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_que_12'>In a closed economy with no government sector, the marginal propensity to save is
0.1, investment is £500 million, and autonomous consumption is £200 million.
Which of the following statements is true at the equilibrium level of national income?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_que_13'>In an open economy with a government sector, the marginal propensity to consume is
0.75 and the marginal propensity to import is 0.25. The open economy multiplier will
equal:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_que_14'>Which of the following is not a problem associated with the active management of
fiscal policy?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_que_15'>If a country experiences high domestic inflation compared to its trading partners with
a fixed exchange rate then the effect of the inflation will be to:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_que_16'>Under fixed exchange rates with perfect capital mobility the most effective
macroeconomic policy to increase output is:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_que_17'>If the central bank has to intervene in the foreign exchange markets to prevent the
home currency from appreciating, then its foreign exchange reserves will:</string>"
    <string name='sep2010_que_18'>Which of the following is not included in a country’s current account?</string>
    "<string name='sep2010_que_19'>Suppose that you import DVDs from France and write a £10,000 cheque to cover a
€12,500 billing for your latest purchase of DVDs. The exchange rate is:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_que_20'>In a perfectly competitive market, the typical firm cannot affect the price of its output,
and so it maximises profits or minimises losses when marginal cost is:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_que_21'>A firm is producing 1000 units of output at a price of £20, with a marginal cost of £5
and average cost of £8 at that level of output. What is the supernormal profit that the
monopoly firm is making?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_que_22'>A firm producing carpets has average variable costs of production of £420, marginal
costs of production of £500 and operates in a perfectly competitive market. A
decrease in the demand for carpets which reduces the price from £600 to £400 will
mean that the firm will do which of the following in the short run:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_que_23'>5,000 bottles of a soft drink are demanded when the price for each bottle is £5. When
the price is £6 only 4000 bottles are demanded. The marginal revenue from
increasing the price is:</string>"
    <string name='sep2010_que_24'>Which one of the following is NOT a cause of cost push inflation?</string>
    "<string name='sep2010_que_25'>Which one of the following will NOT happen following a devaluation of the domestic
currency on the foreign exchange market?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_que_26'>An implicit or explicit agreement amongst firms in an industry not to compete with
each other is known as:</string>"

</resources>