<resources>
    <string name='sep2016_que_1'>The solution to the economic problem of deciding which goods to produce requires:</string>
    <string name='sep2016_que_2'>Opportunity cost is always:</string>
    "<string name='sep2016_que_3'>Which of the following statements explains how price, demand and supply respond to
a surplus?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_que_4'>Despite an increase in the price of admission from £15.00 to £18.00, a football club
finds that attendance at matches increased by 20%. Which of the following could
most effectively explain this situation?</string>"
    <string name='sep2016_que_5'>Diminishing marginal utility of income implies that individuals are:</string>
    "<string name='sep2016_que_6'>Consumer A has a higher income than Consumer B but they have identical
preferences and pay the same prices for the goods which they consume. If they both
maximise utility then the marginal utility from each good consumed will be:</string>"
    <string name='sep2016_que_7'>Vertical product differentiation refers to differences between products which reflect:</string>
    <string name='sep2016_que_8'>Which of the following reveals constant returns to scale?</string>
    <string name='sep2016_que_9'>A firm that produces a main product and a by-product will maximise profits if it:</string>
    "<string name='sep2016_que_10'>A perfectly competitive firm has fixed and variable costs of production. It produces
output at the long-run profit maximising level. Which of the following statements is
correct?</string>"
    <string name='sep2016_que_11'>Which of the following statements is FALSE?</string>
    <string name='sep2016_que_12'>Which of the following is NOT a barrier to entry in an oligopolistic industry?</string>
    "<string name='sep2016_que_13'>When the owner of a patented product allows another firm to produce it for a fee, the
arrangement is referred to as a:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_que_14'>If a resident of a country purchases a foreign company’s shares, the value of the
transaction is entered in which of the domestic country’s balance of payments
accounts?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_que_15'>The need to employ workers with certain skills may decline even if the industry as a
whole is not in decline. This form of unemployment is called:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_que_16'>Which one of the following is likely to be the most effective method of reducing the
natural rate of unemployment?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_que_17'>Which of the following could explain why a country’s aggregate demand curve might
shift inwards to the left?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_que_18'>The short run aggregate supply curves show that an increase in the average price level
will encourage firms to:</string>"
    <string name='sep2016_que_19'>The business cycle is defined as:</string>
    <string name='sep2016_que_20'>Which of the following is a potential source of cost push inflation?</string>
    <string name='sep2016_que_21'>Which of the following does NOT form part of a country’s Gross Domestic Product?</string>
    "<string name='sep2016_que_22'>If private savings exceeds private investment by £300 million and government
expenditure on goods and services exceeds government tax revenue by £200 million
then net exports will be:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_que_23'>Consider an economy where the demand for real money balances and the demand for
investment are both highly interest elastic. A change in the money supply will give:</string>"
    <string name='sep2016_que_24'>Which one of the following statements about the demand for money is TRUE?</string>
    "<string name='sep2016_que_25'>The direct impact of open market operations, where the central bank purchases
government securities, is to:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_que_26'>An increase in government expenditure financed by government borrowing from the
non-bank private sector is most likely to:</string>"

</resources>