<resources>
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_1'>A exists only in economies which rely on the market mechanism.
ENDSTOPB could be eliminated if prices are forced to fall.
ENDSTOPC means that there are shortages of some goods.
ENDSTOPD exists because there are insufficient resources to satisfy human wants.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_2'>A £12,000.
ENDSTOPB £20,000.
ENDSTOPC £32,000.
ENDSTOPD £42,000.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_3'>A indeterminate on price but quantity will fall.
ENDSTOPB indeterminate on price but quantity will rise.
ENDSTOPC indeterminate on quantity but price will rise.
ENDSTOPD indeterminate on quantity but price will fall.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_4'>A demand curve to the left.
ENDSTOPB supply curve to the left.
ENDSTOPC supply curve to the right.
ENDSTOPD demand curve to the right.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_5'>A higher for A than for ENDSTOPB and A will have a higher total utility.
B higher for A than for B and A will have a lower total utility.
ENDSTOPC lower for A than for B and A will have a higher total utility.
ENDSTOPD lower for A than for B and A will have a lower total utility.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_6'>A The curve will shift to the left and become less elastic.
ENDSTOPB The curve will shift to the right and become less elastic.
ENDSTOPC The curve will shift to the left and become more elastic.
ENDSTOPD The curve will shift to the right and become more elastic.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_7'>A Spreading of indivisibilities.
ENDSTOPB Spreading of overheads.
ENDSTOPC Dilution of ownership.
ENDSTOPD Specialisation.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_8'>A The marginal physical product of labour reaches a maximum before the total
physical product of labour.
ENDSTOPB The average physical product of labour continues rising as long as the
marginal physical product is greater than the average physical product of
labour.
ENDSTOPC The total physical product of labour is at a maximum when the marginal
physical product of labour is zero.
ENDSTOPD The average physical product of labour is at a maximum when the marginal
physical product of labour is zero.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_9'>A Output of the firm is where marginal revenue equals marginal cost.
ENDSTOPB The cost curves of the firm are U-shaped.
ENDSTOPC Marginal revenue equals average revenue.
ENDSTOPD The marginal cost curve cuts the average cost curve at its minimum point.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_10'>A greater than unity.
ENDSTOPB equal to zero.
ENDSTOPC between zero and unity.
ENDSTOPD unity.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_11'>A marginal revenue curve and the average revenue curve both have a vertical
section (discontinuity).
ENDSTOPB marginal revenue curve has a vertical section (discontinuity).
ENDSTOPC average revenue curve has a vertical section (discontinuity).
ENDSTOPD marginal cost curve has a vertical section (discontinuity).</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_12'>A Cuts in social security benefits designed to encourage more people to work.
ENDSTOPB Measures designed to reduce trade union powers.
ENDSTOPC Deregulation.
ENDSTOPD Tariffs designed to increase production of domestic goods.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_13'>A Gold’s law.
ENDSTOPB Austrian law.
ENDSTOPC Say’s law.
ENDSTOPD Quantity law.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_14'>A A rise in the average price of imports relative to the average price of exports.
ENDSTOPB A fall in the quantity of imports relative to the quantity of exports.
ENDSTOPC A rise in the quantity of exports while imports remain the same.
ENDSTOPD A rise in the average price of exports relative to the average price of imports.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_15'>A Frictional unemployment.
ENDSTOPB Cyclical unemployment.
ENDSTOPC Seasonal unemployment.
ENDSTOPD Structural unemployment.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_16'>A 5.9%
ENDSTOPB 5.3%
ENDSTOPC 5.0%
ENDSTOPD 6.3%</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_17'>A An increase in the money supply.
ENDSTOPB An increase in capital investment expenditure.
ENDSTOPC An increase in education expenditure.
ENDSTOPD An increase in research and development expenditure.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_18'>A A depreciation of the domestic currency.
ENDSTOPB A decrease in imported commodity prices.
ENDSTOPC An increase in consumer expenditure.
ENDSTOPD A decrease in direct taxes.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_19'>A Salaries of school teachers.
ENDSTOPB Net income from abroad.
ENDSTOPC Company profits.
ENDSTOPD Investment expenditure.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_20'>A an increase in the money supply.
ENDSTOPB a decrease in the money demand.
ENDSTOPC a rise in the rate of interest.
ENDSTOPD an increase in the speculative demand for money.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_21'>A 0 per cent.
ENDSTOPB 10 per cent.
ENDSTOPC 10 per cent multiplied by the velocity of circulation.
ENDSTOPD 10 per cent divided by the velocity of circulation.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_22'>A extent to which government expansionary policy is counteracted by lower
private spending resulting from higher interest rates.
ENDSTOPB extent to which government contractionary policy is counteracted by lower
private spending resulting from lower interest rates.
ENDSTOPC increase in interest rates caused by contractionary monetary policy.
ENDSTOPD increase in consumption expenditure caused by lower taxes.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_23'>A raise government expenditure and reduce tax revenue.
ENDSTOPB raise government expenditure and raise tax revenue.
ENDSTOPC reduce government expenditure and raise tax revenue.
ENDSTOPD reduce government expenditure and reduce tax revenue.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_24'>A Increase unemployment benefit.
ENDSTOPB Increase taxes.
ENDSTOPC Increase the money supply.
ENDSTOPD Increase information flows on job availability.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_25'>A A decrease in interest rates.
ENDSTOPB An appreciation of the domestic currency.
ENDSTOPC A rise in government expenditure.
ENDSTOPD An increase in business confidence.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_choices_26'>A increases the opportunity cost of holding money and redistributes wealth from
fixed rate borrowers to lenders.
ENDSTOPB increases the opportunity cost of holding money and redistributes wealth from
fixed rate lenders to borrowers.
ENDSTOPC reduces the opportunity cost of holding money and redistributes wealth from
fixed rate borrowers to lenders.
ENDSTOPD reduces the opportunity cost of holding money and redistributes wealth from
fixed rate lenders to borrowers.</string>"


</resources>