<resources>
    <string name='sep2019_que_1'>The problem of scarcity in economics:</string>
    "<string name='sep2019_que_2'>A student studying a one-year Masters degree in Actuarial Science has course
fees of £12,000. Were she not studying she could have had a job paying an aftertax
income of £20,000. Irrespective of whether she studies or works the cost of
her accommodation is £7,000 and the food bill is £3,000. The opportunity cost of
studying for the Masters degree is:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_que_3'>If the cost of production increases and consumer income rises, the combined effect on
the equilibrium price and quantity of an inferior good is:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_que_4'>Wheat is an essential input in the production of pasta. An increase in the price of
wheat would have an impact on the demand and supply of pasta by shifting the:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_que_5'>Consumer A has a higher income than Consumer B but they have identical
preferences and pay the same prices for the goods which they consume. If both
consumers maximise utility then the marginal utility from each good consumed will
be:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_que_6'>A firm’s decision to reduce its expenditure on advertising is most likely to have the
following impact on its demand curve:</string>"
    <string name='sep2019_que_7'>Which of the following does NOT contribute to economies of scale?</string>
    "<string name='sep2019_que_8'>Assume that a firm has a fixed capital stock and variable units of labour as the only
inputs into its production process. If increasing amounts of the variable labour input
are added to the fixed factor, then according to the law of diminishing returns which of
the following is FALSE?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_que_9'>Which one of the following conditions indicates that a firm is operating in a perfectly
competitive industry rather than a monopolistic industry?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_que_10'>A profit maximising monopoly facing a linear demand schedule and with positive
marginal costs will set its price in the region of the demand curve where the absolute
price elasticity of demand is:</string>"
    <string name='sep2019_que_11'>In the kinked demand curve theory of oligopoly the:</string>
    "<string name='sep2019_que_12'>Which of the following is NOT a supply side economic policy aimed at promoting
economic growth?</string>"
    <string name='sep2019_que_13'>“Supply creates its own demand” is also known as:</string>
    "<string name='sep2019_que_14'>Which of the following will result in an improvement in the domestic country’s terms
of trade?</string>"
    <string name='sep2019_que_15'>Which of the following is an example of disequilibrium unemployment?</string>
    "<string name='sep2019_que_16'>A country with a population of 38 million has 32 million in employment and 2 million
unemployed. What is the unemployment rate?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_que_17'>Which of the following is least likely to lead to an increase in long run economic
growth?</string>"
    <string name='sep2019_que_18'>Which of the following is a potential source of cost push inflation?</string>
    <string name='sep2019_que_19'>Which of the following does NOT form part of a country’s Gross Domestic Product?</string>
    "<string name='sep2019_que_20'>Other things being equal, an increase in the level of real output in an economy will
result in:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_que_21'>According to the quantity theory of money, a 10 per cent increase in the nominal
money supply will lead to an increase in the real output level of the economy of:</string>"
    <string name='sep2019_que_22'>“Crowding out” describes the:</string>
    <string name='sep2019_que_23'>In the event of a recession in the economy, automatic fiscal stabilisers:</string>
    "<string name='sep2019_que_24'>Which one of the following is likely to be the most effective method of reducing the
natural rate of unemployment?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2019_que_25'>Which of the following might explain why a country’s aggregate demand curve might
shift inwards to the left?</string>"
    <string name='sep2019_que_26'>Unanticipated inflation:</string>

</resources>