<resources>"<string name='sep2006_que_1'>The solution to the economic allocation problem of deciding WHICH goods to
produce requires:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_que_2'>The limits on the output of finished goods as imposed by a limited supply of
productive inputs may be shown on a diagram whose axes are:</string>"
    <string name='sep2006_que_3'>Which one of the following will NOT shift the supply curve for Good X to the right?</string>
    "<string name='sep2006_que_4'>Good X has a price elasticity of demand equal to minus one. In such circumstances a
per unit sales tax on Good X of £10 will lead to which of the following?</string>"
    <string name='sep2006_que_5'>If Goods X and Y are substitutes, an increase in the price of X causes:</string>
    "<string name='sep2006_que_6'>A consumer has £1 of income. Good X costs 20 pence, Good Y costs 20 pence.
The relevant marginal utilities for the consumer are: The optimum combination of Good X and Good Y for the consumer to purchase is:</string>"
    <string name='sep2006_que_7'>Which one of the following is TRUE when economies of scale are present?</string>
    "<string name='sep2006_que_8'>For a firm in long run equilibrium in an industry characterised by monopolistic
competition:</string>"
    <string name='sep2006_que_9'>Which one of the following statements about market structure is FALSE?</string>
    "<string name='sep2006_que_10'>When a monopolist maximises profits, price exceeds marginal revenue. The
difference between price and marginal revenue occurs because:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_que_11'>The idea that an oligopolistic firm faces a kinked demand curve is based upon the
assumption that:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_que_12'>If the price of Good X has risen and the quantity sold has increased then there must
have been a:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_que_13'>According to marginal revenue productivity theory the wages paid to workers in a
perfectly competitive firm which produces Good X will be equal to:</string>"
    <string name='sep2006_que_14'>Which of the following does NOT form part of the UK national income:</string>
    <string name='sep2006_que_15'>When taxes on all income are progressive then as income for an individual increases:</string>
    <string name='sep2006_que_16'>The three leakages from the circular flow of income are:</string>
    "<string name='sep2006_que_17'>In a simple closed economy with a marginal propensity to consume of 0.75, what
would be the effect on the level of aggregate expenditure of an increase in
autonomous investment of £20 million?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_que_18'>The data on an economy are:
Consumer Expenditure £70 million
Investment £20 million
Government Expenditure £40 million
Exports £20 million
Imports £30 million
Net Property Income from abroad £10 million
What is the value of its Gross National Income (or Gross National Product)?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_que_19'>Which one of the following situations will lead to the most crowding out of private
sector investment following an increase in government expenditure?</string>"
    <string name='sep2006_que_20'>The narrow money supply is increased when:</string>
    "<string name='sep2006_que_21'>Which one of the following statements about real variables in the economy is
FALSE?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_que_22'>Which one of the following would NOT constitute a demand side economic policy for
reducing unemployment?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_que_23'>Which of the following will increase the size of the government expenditure
multiplier?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_que_24'>A crucial difference between the approaches of the Monetarist and Keynesian
economists to achieving full employment when an economy is in recession is that:</string>"
    <string name='sep2006_que_25'>One way of reducing the natural rate of unemployment would be to increase:</string>
    "<string name='sep2006_que_26'>Country A exports Good X to Country B and imports Good Y from Country B. The
price of Good X rises from £5 to £7 and the price of Good Y falls from £10 to £8.
Which of the following statements is TRUE about Country A's terms of trade?</string>"
</resources>