<resources>"<string name='sep2008_choices_1'>A an increase in the stock of capital (machinery)
ENDSTOPB an increase in the production of consumption goods
ENDSTOPC a decision to fully utilise unemployed resources
ENDSTOPD a decrease in the population</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_2'>A no change in price and a shortage.
ENDSTOPB a rise in price and quantity sold.
ENDSTOPC a rise in price and a shortage.
ENDSTOPD a rise in price and a surplus.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_3'>A 150 units.
ENDSTOPB 125 units.
ENDSTOPC 75 units.
ENDSTOPD 50 units.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_4'>A Inferior goods are goods for which the income elasticity of demand is
negative.
ENDSTOPB Giffen goods are goods for which the own price elasticity of demand is
positive.
ENDSTOPC Complementary goods tend to have positive cross price elasticity of demand.
ENDSTOPD Substitute goods tend to have positive cross price elasticity of demand.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_5'>A fewer bananas and more apples.
ENDSTOPB fewer bananas and fewer apples.
ENDSTOPC more bananas and more apples.
ENDSTOPD more bananas and fewer apples.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_6'>A increasing relative risk aversion.
ENDSTOPB declining absolute risk aversion.
ENDSTOPC increasing absolute risk aversion.
ENDSTOPD none of the above.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_7'>A Marginal cost is equal to average variable cost when average variable cost is at
a minimum.
ENDSTOPB Average fixed cost always falls as output rises.
ENDSTOPC Marginal cost cannot exceed average total cost.
ENDSTOPD Average total cost exceeds average variable cost by an amount that declines
with increasing output.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_8'>A product differentiation.
ENDSTOPB the large number of firms operating in the industry.
ENDSTOPC ease of entry into the industry.
ENDSTOPD cost minimisation.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_9'>A inelastic.
ENDSTOPB elastic.
ENDSTOPC equal to unity.
ENDSTOPD indeterminate.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_10'>A The marginal revenue product of the 8th man is lower than the marginal
revenue product of the 10th man.
ENDSTOPB The marginal revenue product of the 8th man is higher than the marginal
revenue product of the 9th man.
ENDSTOPC The marginal revenue product of the 9th man is lower than that of the 10th
man.
ENDSTOPD The marginal revenue product of the 10th man is negative.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_11'>A average total cost equals average revenue.
ENDSTOPB average total cost is less than average revenue.
ENDSTOPC average total cost is at a minimum.
ENDSTOPD marginal cost is equal to average total cost.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_12'>A if more labour is added to a given amount of capital the marginal product of
labour remains unchanged
ENDSTOPB if the ratio of labour to capital doubles, the output of the firm also doubles
ENDSTOPC if the input of both capital and labour doubles, the output of the firm remains
constant
ENDSTOPD if the input of capital and labour doubles, the output of the firm also doubles</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_13'>A £1,200 billion
ENDSTOPB £750 billion
ENDSTOPC £600 billion
ENDSTOPD £1,000 billion</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_14'>A the marginal propensity to consume is 0.25 and the multiplier is 1.33.
ENDSTOPB the marginal propensity to consume is 0.25 and the multiplier is 4.
ENDSTOPC the marginal propensity to consume is 0.75 and the multiplier is 4.
ENDSTOPD the marginal propensity to consume is 0.75 and the multiplier is 1.33.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_15'>A investment is increased when interest rates fall.
ENDSTOPB an increase in investment will lead to a more than proportionate increase in
output.
ENDSTOPC the level of investment expenditure is determined by the rate of change of
national income.
ENDSTOPD investment is increased when interest rates rise.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_16'>A direct the central bank to pursue contractionary open market operations.
ENDSTOPB direct the central bank to increase the money supply.
ENDSTOPC increase the tax rate on income.
ENDSTOPD raise indirect taxes.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_17'>A Gross Domestic Product is greater than Gross National Income.
ENDSTOPB Gross Domestic Product is less than Gross National Income.
ENDSTOPC Gross Domestic Product is the same as Gross National Income.
ENDSTOPD we cannot say whether Gross Domestic Product differs from Gross National
Income from this information.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_18'>A £24,000.
ENDSTOPB £25,000.
ENDSTOPC £36,000.
ENDSTOPD none of the above.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_19'>A change in consumption divided by the change in disposable income.
ENDSTOPB level of consumption divided by the level of disposable income.
ENDSTOPC level of consumption divided by the change in disposable income.
ENDSTOPD change in consumption divided by the level of disposable income.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_20'>A increases the multiplier at all levels of national income.
ENDSTOPB increases the multiplier at low levels of national income and reduces it at high
levels of national income.
ENDSTOPC decreases the multiplier at all levels of national income.
ENDSTOPD has no effect on the multiplier.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_21'>A an increase in the discount rate
ENDSTOPB a reduction in reserve requirements
ENDSTOPC a purchase of government bonds
ENDSTOPD none of the above</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_22'>A if I only is correct.
ENDSTOPB if II only is correct.
ENDSTOPC if I and II are correct.
ENDSTOPD if all are correct.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_23'>A lowering the rate of interest
ENDSTOPB raising the rate of unemployment benefit
ENDSTOPC higher voluntary redundancy payments for workers in declining industries
ENDSTOPD more government funds for retraining of the unemployed</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_24'>A 0.4
ENDSTOPB 4.8
ENDSTOPC 30
ENDSTOPD 133,333.3</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_25'>A lenders
ENDSTOPB holders of currency
ENDSTOPC pensioners on fixed incomes
ENDSTOPD borrowers</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_choices_26'>A they have improved by 100 per cent
ENDSTOPB they have improved by 60 per cent
ENDSTOPC they have deteriorated by 100 per cent
ENDSTOPD they have deteriorated by 60 per cent</string>"
</resources>