<resources>
    <string name='sep2018_que_1'>Opportunity cost is always:</string>
    "<string name='sep2018_que_2'>If public transport is an inferior good, which of the following will cause its demand
curve to shift to the left?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_que_3'>If ice cream is a substitute for fruit sorbet and strawberries are a complement to
ice-cream but not fruit sorbet then a fall in the price of ice cream will:</string>"
    <string name='sep2018_que_4'>Diminishing marginal utility of income implies that individuals are:</string>
    <string name='sep2018_que_5'>Which of the following statements defines moral hazard in relation to insurance?</string>
    <string name='sep2018_que_6'>Vertical product differentiation refers to differences between products which reflect:</string>
    <string name='sep2018_que_7'>Diseconomies of scale means:</string>
    "<string name='sep2018_que_8'>The range of output over which average variable cost falls will be the same as the
range over which:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_que_9'>A perfectly competitive firm has fixed and variable costs of production. It produces at
the long run profit maximising level. Which of the following statements is correct?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_que_10'>When a monopolist maximises profits, price exceeds marginal revenue. The
difference between price and marginal revenue occurs because:</string>"
    <string name='sep2018_que_11'>Which of the following is NOT an example of the market drivers of globalisation?</string>
    <string name='sep2018_que_12'>Firms can benefit through specialisation and international trade due to:</string>
    <string name='sep2018_que_13'>Structural unemployment is unemployment that:</string>
    "<string name='sep2018_que_14'>A country with a population of 38 million has 32 million in employment and 2 million
unemployed. What is the unemployment rate rounded up to one decimal point?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_que_15'>The aggregate demand curve slopes downwards because at higher price levels the real
money supply:</string>"
    <string name='sep2018_que_16'>Which of the following is NOT a cost of inflation?</string>
    <string name='sep2018_que_17'>In the circular flow of income model which of the following is TRUE?</string>
    "<string name='sep2018_que_18'>Under a fixed exchange rate system the following approaches might be considered by
governments to correct a balance of payments deficit.
I Discouragement of imports.
II Support for exporters.
III Increase the level of aggregate demand.
Which of the following is most likely to achieve this objective?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_que_19'>The US has been running a large current account deficit, and China has a large
current account surplus. If their exchange rates were both flexible, how could such
imbalances be eliminated?</string>"
    <string name='sep2018_que_20'>Money that is held because of possible unforeseen events is held because of the:</string>
    "<string name='sep2018_que_21'>Which of the following policies undertaken by the central bank will have an
expansionary effect on the broad money supply measure other things being equal?</string>"
    <string name='sep2018_que_22'>The short run Phillips curve shows:</string>
    "<string name='sep2018_que_23'>If the government imposes a minimum wage that is above the market equilibrium
wage we would expect:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_que_24'>Which of the following is NOT a problem associated with the active management of
fiscal policy?</string>"
    <string name='sep2018_que_25'>The adoption of an expansionary fiscal policy will result in:</string>
    "<string name='sep2018_que_26'>The “crowding out” effect associated with an increase in government borrowing could
be reduced or eliminated by an accommodating increase in:</string>"


</resources>