<resources>
    "<string name='sep2011_que_1'>What is the combined effect of an increase in the cost of production and a rise in
consumer income on the equilibrium price and quantity of a normal good?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_que_2'>Which one of the following accurately describes the opportunity cost of producing
Good X?</string>"
    <string name='sep2011_que_3'>Under the Cournot model of duopoly a firm:</string>
    <string name='sep2011_que_4'>Which one of the following is NOT a barrier to entry into a monopoly market?</string>
    "<string name='sep2011_que_5' formatted="false">Following an increase in the price of fuel there is a 20% increase in the price of air
travel tickets which results in a 20% decrease in total revenue. Which of following
statements is TRUE about the demand for air travel?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_que_6'>The managing director of a monopoly firm is given the following data:
Marginal revenue = £9, Marginal cost = £10
Average cost = £11, Average revenue = £15
To maximise profits the firm should:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_que_7'>Global Airways, which is a profit maximising firm, has to decide whether or not to run
an extra daily flight between London and Paris. The total daily fixed costs of the airline
are £3,000, the total variable costs of the extra flight are £2,000 and the expected
revenue from the extra flight is £2,500. In such circumstances Global Airways will:</string>"
    <string name='sep2011_que_8'>A perfectly contestable market is a market where the:</string>
    "<string name='sep2011_que_9'>A monopolist facing a downward sloping demand curve for its product will set its price
in the region of the demand curve where the demand:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_que_10'>The demand for Good X has a price elasticity of minus unity while the supply curve has
a positive slope. If the government decided to impose a tax of £10 per unit on Good X
this would:</string>"
    <string name='sep2011_que_11'>Which one of the following illustrates the problem of adverse selection?</string>
    <string name='sep2011_que_12'>Consider the following table: The table illustrates which one of the following:</string>
    <string name='sep2011_que_13'>Which one of the following statements about market structure is TRUE?</string>
    "<string name='sep2011_que_14'>Which of the following would constitute a supply side economic policy for reducing
unemployment?</string>"
    <string name='sep2011_que_15'>Which of the following statements defines moral hazard in relation to insurance?</string>
    <string name='sep2011_que_16'>In the circular flow of income model:</string>
    <string name='sep2011_que_17'>Which of the following does NOT form part of a country’s Gross Domestic Product?</string>
    "<string name='sep2011_que_18'>Which one of the following statements about real variables in the economy is
FALSE?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_que_19'>In a simple economy, consumption is given by the relationship
C = 0.75 Y
Where C is consumption expenditure and Y is Gross Domestic Product.
If government expenditure is £150 million, investment is £50 million and there is no
taxation or international trade, what will be the equilibrium value of Gross Domestic
Product of the economy?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_que_20'>The aggregate demand schedule slopes downwards because at higher price levels the
real money supply:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_que_21'>To obtain a measure of Net National Income from Gross Domestic Product it is
necessary to:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_que_22'>If the money supply increases due to an expansionary open market operation by the
central bank then the price of treasury bills will:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2011_que_23'>A tightening of monetary policy in an open economy operating with a flexible
exchange rate would most likely lead to:</string>"
    <string name='sep2011_que_24'>You are given the following data for an economy: The value of the economy’s Gross National Income at market prices is:</string>
    "<string name='sep2011_que_25'>Given the following labour hours required to produce 1 unit of each of Goods X and
Y, which one of the statements below is TRUE?</string>"
    <string name='sep2011_que_26'>A country is running a current account surplus. In relation to the rest of the world it is:</string>

</resources>