<resources>
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_1'>A (i) only
ENDSTOPB (ii) only
ENDSTOPC (iii) only
ENDSTOPD (i), (ii) and (iii).</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_2'>A a market system.
ENDSTOPB macroeconomics.
ENDSTOPC competition.
ENDSTOPD opportunity cost.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_3'>A the good becomes less expensive relative to all other products.
ENDSTOPB the change in price causes a decline in purchasing power.
ENDSTOPC the good becomes more expensive relative to all other products.
ENDSTOPD the change in price causes an increase in purchasing power.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_4'>A Firms expect future prices to rise.
ENDSTOPB At higher levels of output, firms will incur higher costs.
ENDSTOPC The higher the price, the more profitable a good becomes to produce.
ENDSTOPD Firms expect future prices to fall.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_5'>A 2%.
ENDSTOPB 4%.
ENDSTOPC 6%.
ENDSTOPD 8%.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_6'>A less than the price.
ENDSTOPB greater than the price.
ENDSTOPC equal to the price.
ENDSTOPD below average variable cost.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_7'>A produce at the lowest point of its long run average cost curve.
ENDSTOPB have excess capacity.
ENDSTOPC produce at a socially efficient output level.
ENDSTOPD produce at the lowest point of its marginal cost curve.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_8'>A people who know that they are a particularly high risk are more inclined to
take out insurance.
ENDSTOPB people who know that they are a particularly high risk are less inclined to take
out insurance.
ENDSTOPC an insurance company will face false insurance claims.
ENDSTOPD a policyholder may act in a way that makes the insured event more likely to
occur.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_9'>A The marginal cost of producing the fourth item is greater than the marginal
cost of producing the first item.
ENDSTOPB The marginal cost of producing the fourth item is less than the marginal
revenue from selling the fourth item.
ENDSTOPC The marginal revenue from selling the sixth item is positive.
ENDSTOPD The marginal revenue from selling the third item is greater than the marginal
cost of producing the third item.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_10'>A A firm doubles its inputs of capital and labour and its output more than
doubles.
ENDSTOPB A firm doubles the number of products it produces and also doubles its
research budget.
ENDSTOPC A firm produces a new product and in so doing lowers the average cost of
producing its existing products.
ENDSTOPD A firm produces a new product and in so doing lowers the price it charges on
its existing products.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_11'>A constant returns to scale.
ENDSTOPB decreasing returns to scale.
ENDSTOPC increasing returns to scale.
ENDSTOPD the law of diminishing returns.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_12'>A Marginal physical product is equal to total physical product divided by
average product.
ENDSTOPB Average physical product is always greater than marginal physical product.
ENDSTOPC Marginal physical product can never become negative.
ENDSTOPD Average physical product can never become negative.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_13'>A Average physical product at 2 units of labour and marginal physical product at
1 unit of labour
ENDSTOPB Average physical product at 3 units of labour and marginal physical product at
2 units of labour
ENDSTOPC Average physical product at 4 units of labour and marginal physical product at
3 units of labour
ENDSTOPD Average physical product at 5 units of labour and marginal physical product at
4 units of labour.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_14'>A raise their price in the short run but restore the price back to its original level
in the long run.
ENDSTOPB keep their price constant in both the short run and the long run.
ENDSTOPC raise their price in both the short run and the long run.
ENDSTOPD keep their price constant in the short run but raise their price in the long run.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_15'>A shut down its production.
ENDSTOPB decrease its level of output but continue to produce carpets.
ENDSTOPC reduce its fixed costs of production.
ENDSTOPD increase its level of output.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_16'>A the firm has to charge a price higher than the marginal cost of producing the
last unit.
ENDSTOPB any decision by the monopolist to sell an additional unit of output does not
affect price.
ENDSTOPC the firm has to reduce the price on all units sold in order to sell an additional
unit.
ENDSTOPD of the law of diminishing returns.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_17'>A €20,000
ENDSTOPB €15,000
ENDSTOPC €7,000
ENDSTOPD €12,000.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_18'>A Increasing social security benefits
ENDSTOPB Increasing the money supply
ENDSTOPC Reducing corporate and personal taxation
ENDSTOPD Increasing government expenditure aimed at exploiting the multiplier effect.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_19'>A an increase in aggregate demand and a reduction in real output.
ENDSTOPB an increase in aggregate demand and an increase in real output.
ENDSTOPC a reduction in aggregate demand and a reduction in real output.
ENDSTOPD a reduction in aggregate demand and an increase in real output.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_20'>A 8%
ENDSTOPB 11.1%
ENDSTOPC 12.5%
ENDSTOPD 13%.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_21'>A higher domestic interest rates and an exchange rate appreciation.
ENDSTOPB higher domestic interest rates and an exchange rate depreciation.
ENDSTOPC lower domestic interest rates and an exchange rate appreciation.
ENDSTOPD lower domestic interest rates and an exchange rate depreciation.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_22'>A Increased government expenditure on domestically produced goods
ENDSTOPB Increased money supply
ENDSTOPC Reduced corporate and personal taxation
ENDSTOPD A privatisation programme.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_23'>A an increase in the quantity of labour demanded.
ENDSTOPB the labour supply curve to shift to the left.
ENDSTOPC an increase in the quantity of labour supplied.
ENDSTOPD the demand for labour curve to shift to the left.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_24'>A length of time for the typical job search increased.
ENDSTOPB level of unemployment benefits paid to unemployed workers decreased.
ENDSTOPC level of labour productivity rose.
ENDSTOPD rate of inflation increased.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_25'>A rise and reduce money demand.
ENDSTOPB rise and raise money demand.
ENDSTOPC fall and reduce money demand.
ENDSTOPD fall and raise money demand.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_choices_26'>A fall in the real interest rate.
ENDSTOPB rise in the nominal wage rate.
ENDSTOPC rise in the real wage rate.
ENDSTOPD rise in the nominal interest rate.</string>"

</resources>