<resources>
    "<string name='sep2021_que_1'>Which of the following statements is NOT correct in relation to the Austrian school
of thought?
Economists following the Austrian school of thought:
(i) place emphasis on individual subjective preferences.
(ii) focus on market forces determining prices.
(iii) believe in a centrally planned economic system.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_que_2'>If the government chooses to use resources to build a hospital instead of a school, this
illustrates the concept of:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_que_3'>The substitution effect of a price decrease causes an individual to purchase more units
of a normal good because:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_que_4'>Which of the following would NOT explain why, when the price of a good rises, the
quantity supplied will also rise?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_que_5'>If the income elasticity of demand for Good X is 2, a rise in all consumers’ disposable
incomes from £50 million to £52 million will increase the quantity demanded of Good
X by:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_que_6'>In a perfectly competitive market, a typical firm cannot affect the price of its output,
and so it maximises profits when marginal cost is:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_que_7'>In the long run, a firm operating in an industry characterised by monopolistic
competition will:</string>"
    <string name='sep2021_que_8'>In relation to insurance, moral hazard describes the fact that:</string>
    "<string name='sep2021_que_9'>The following table gives a breakdown of a firm’s average cost and average revenue
at various levels of output. Which of the following is TRUE?</string>"
    <string name='sep2021_que_10'>Which of the following is an example of economies of scope?</string>
    <string name='sep2021_que_11'>Increasing long-run average costs are associated with:</string>
    <string name='sep2021_que_12'>Which of the following statements is TRUE?</string>
    "<string name='sep2021_que_13'>Given the following data, at what levels of employment are the average physical
product and marginal physical products of labour at a maximum?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_que_14'>Assuming that the marginal and average cost curves are unchanged, then following an
increase in demand, firms in a perfectly competitive industry will:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_que_15'>A firm producing carpets has average variable costs of production of £420, marginal
costs of production of £500 and operates in a perfectly competitive market. A
decrease in the demand for carpets that reduces the price from £600 to £400 will mean
that in the short run the firm will:</string>"
    <string name='sep2021_que_16'>For a monopoly, price exceeds marginal revenue because:</string>
    "<string name='sep2021_que_17'>A firm is producing 1,000 units of output at a price of €20, with a marginal cost of €5
and average cost of €8 at that level of output. What is the supernormal profit that the
monopoly firm is making?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_que_18'>Which of the following would constitute a supply side economic policy for reducing
unemployment?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_que_19'>Assuming no crowding out effects, the adoption of a policy to reduce the
government’s budget deficit will involve:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_que_20'>In a country with a population of 25 million, there are 16 million employed and 2
million unemployed. What is the rate of unemployment?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_que_21'>The introduction of a restrictive monetary policy in an open economy operating with a
flexible exchange rate would most likely lead to:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_que_22'>Which one of the following would NOT constitute a demand side economic policy
for reducing unemployment?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_que_23'>If the government imposes a minimum wage that is above the market equilibrium
wage, we would expect:</string>"
    <string name='sep2021_que_24'>Other things being equal, the natural rate of unemployment would increase if the:</string>
    "<string name='sep2021_que_25'>A government’s attempts to increase the narrow money supply through open market
operations are likely to cause short-term interest rates to:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2021_que_26'>Assuming all other variables remain constant, a decrease in the average price level
will result in a:</string>"


</resources>