<resources>
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_1'>A the establishment of freedom of entry and exit.
ENDSTOPB the establishment of a system of market prices.
ENDSTOPC a choice between the production of consumer goods and the sacrifice of
alternatives.
ENDSTOPD a decision to be made on the degree to which capital will be used in the
production process rather than labour.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_2'>A constant.
ENDSTOPB equal to a firm’s supernormal profits.
ENDSTOPC equal to total revenue minus total variable cost.
ENDSTOPD the cost in terms of the best foregone alternative.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_3'>A Price rises, quantity demanded falls and quantity supplied rises.
ENDSTOPB Price rises, quantity demanded falls and quantity supplied falls.
ENDSTOPC Price falls, quantity demanded rises and quantity supplied falls.
ENDSTOPD Price falls, quantity demanded rises and quantity supplied rises.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_4'>A The prices of alternative attractions have fallen.
ENDSTOPB Demand to watch football has a high price elasticity.
ENDSTOPC Demand to watch football has a low price elasticity.
ENDSTOPD Consumer preference has changed in favour of watching football.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_5'>A risk lovers.
ENDSTOPB risk averse.
ENDSTOPC risk neutral.
ENDSTOPD risk diversifiers.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_6'>A higher for A than for ENDSTOPB and A will have a higher total utility.
B higher for A than for B and A will have a lower total utility.
ENDSTOPC lower for A than for B and A will have a higher total utility.
ENDSTOPD lower for A than for B and A will have a lower total utility.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_7'>A same quality products.
ENDSTOPB different quality products with different production costs.
ENDSTOPC different consumers’ tastes but not different quality products.
ENDSTOPD different varieties of the same product offered at the same price.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_8'>A When the input of both capital and labour doubles, output doubles.
ENDSTOPB When the input of both capital and labour doubles, output remains constant.
ENDSTOPC When the ratio of labour to capital doubles, the output of the firm also
doubles.
ENDSTOPD When more labour is added to a given amount of capital, the marginal physical
product of labour remains unchanged.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_9'>A uses cost-based pricing for the main and the by-product.
ENDSTOPB selects the combined output where the combined marginal cost equals the
combined marginal revenue.
ENDSTOPC decides on the viability of producing the by-product after it has made the
decision to produce the main product.
ENDSTOPD selects the level of output of the by-product where the marginal cost of the byproduct
equals its marginal revenue.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_10'>A Marginal cost exceeds average total cost.
ENDSTOPB Marginal cost equals average variable cost.
ENDSTOPC Marginal cost exceeds average variable cost.
ENDSTOPD Marginal cost is less than average variable cost.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_11'>A Collusion may occur between firms in oligopolistic competition.
ENDSTOPB A firm in perfect competition faces a perfectly inelastic demand curve.
ENDSTOPC In monopolistic competition, supernormal profits cannot be made in the long
run.
ENDSTOPD Price discrimination would allow the monopolist to produce the socially
efficient level of output.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_12'>A Product proliferation.
ENDSTOPB Constant returns to scale.
ENDSTOPC Investment in spare capacity.
ENDSTOPD High advertising expenditure.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_13'>A merger.
ENDSTOPB franchise.
ENDSTOPC joint venture.
ENDSTOPD licensing agreement.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_14'>A trade account
ENDSTOPB current account
ENDSTOPC capital account
ENDSTOPD financial account</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_15'>A regional.
ENDSTOPB structural.
ENDSTOPC technological.
ENDSTOPD demand-deficient.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_16'>A increase the money supply
ENDSTOPB increase unemployment benefit
ENDSTOPC increase government expenditure
ENDSTOPD increase information flows on job availability</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_17'>A an appreciation of the domestic currency
ENDSTOPB a decrease in interest rates
ENDSTOPC a rise in government expenditure
ENDSTOPD an increase in business confidence</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_18'>A reduce both output and employment.
ENDSTOPB increase both output and employment.
ENDSTOPC increase output and reduce employment.
ENDSTOPD reduce output and increase employment.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_19'>A the long run trend path of output after removing short run variations.
ENDSTOPB the periodic fluctuations of output around the long run trend.
ENDSTOPC the annual cycle of output.
ENDSTOPD none of the above.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_20'>A a decrease in direct taxes
ENDSTOPB an increase in consumer expenditure
ENDSTOPC a depreciation of the domestic currency
ENDSTOPD a decrease in imported commodity prices</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_21'>A company profits
ENDSTOPB investment expenditure
ENDSTOPC net income from abroad
ENDSTOPD salaries of school teachers</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_22'>A zero.
ENDSTOPB +£100 million.
ENDSTOPC £100 million.
ENDSTOPD +£500 million.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_23'>A a relatively small change in both the rate of interest and the level of
investment.
ENDSTOPB a relatively large change in both the rate of interest and the level of
investment.
ENDSTOPC a relatively large change in the rate of interest and a relatively small change in
the level of investment.
ENDSTOPD a relatively small change in the rate of interest and a relatively large change in
the level of investment.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_24'>A The demand for money is negatively related to the interest rate.
ENDSTOPB The demand for money is negatively related to wealth.
ENDSTOPC The demand for money is negatively related to the general price level.
ENDSTOPD The demand for money is negatively related to real income.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_25'>A reduce the cash reserves of commercial banks and reduce the monetary base.
ENDSTOPB reduce the cash reserves of commercial banks and increase the monetary base.
ENDSTOPC increase the cash reserves of commercial banks and reduce the monetary base.
ENDSTOPD increase the cash reserves of commercial banks and increase the monetary
base.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2016_choices_26'>A reduce the demand for money, reduce interest rates and cause investment to
rise.
ENDSTOPB increase the demand for money, reduce interest rates and cause investment to
rise.
ENDSTOPC reduce the demand for money, increase interest rates and cause investment to
fall.
ENDSTOPD increase the demand for money, increase interest rates and cause investment to
fall.</string>"


</resources>