<resources>
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_1'>A Machinery
ENDSTOPB Casual labour
ENDSTOPC Money in the bank
ENDSTOPD Land.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_2'>A individuals and firms make decisions that determine economic outcomes with
SOME government involvement in priority sectors such as healthcare and
education.
ENDSTOPB individuals and firms make decisions that determine economic outcomes and
there is NO government involvement in any sector of the economy.
ENDSTOPC individuals and government make decisions that determine economic
outcomes in ALL sectors of the economy.
ENDSTOPD firms and the government make decisions that determine economic outcomes
in ALL sectors of the economy.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_3'>A The availability of capital.
ENDSTOPB The skill level of the labour force.
ENDSTOPC The level of demand in the economy.
ENDSTOPD The availability of inputs.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_4'>A Price stays the same and quantity falls.
ENDSTOPB Price falls and quantity rises.
ENDSTOPC Price rises and quantity rises.
ENDSTOPD Price falls and quantity stays the same.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_5'>A quantity is 60 and price is 80.
ENDSTOPB quantity is 70 and price is 90.
ENDSTOPC quantity is 80 and price is 100.
ENDSTOPD quantity is 90 and price is 110.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_6'>A They are complements and are closely related.
ENDSTOPB They are complements and are not closely related.
ENDSTOPC They are substitutes and are closely related.
ENDSTOPD They are substitutes and are not closely related.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_7'>A make supernormal profit in the long run.
ENDSTOPB face barriers when entering the industry.
ENDSTOPC charge a price equal to the marginal cost of the firm.
ENDSTOPD normally face a downward sloping demand curve.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_8'>A increasing returns to scale.
ENDSTOPB decreasing returns to scale.
ENDSTOPC diminishing returns.
ENDSTOPD constant returns to scale.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_9'>A increase the firm’s average fixed costs.
ENDSTOPB decrease the firm’s average total costs.
ENDSTOPC decrease the firm’s average variable costs.
ENDSTOPD increase the firm’s marginal costs.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_10'>A under perfect competition there are only a few firms, whereas in an oligopoly
there are many firms.
ENDSTOPB under perfect competition a firm experiences a downward sloping demand
curve, but in an oligopoly the firm tends to have a perfectly elastic demand
curve.
ENDSTOPC under perfect competition firms can only make normal profit in the long run,
whereas in an oligopoly firms can make abnormal profit in the long run and
short run.
ENDSTOPD under perfect competition firms may be able to dominate the market and
restrict entry, whereas firms operating in an oligopoly tend to facilitate free
entry.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_11'>A $1,625 million
ENDSTOPB $1,500 million
ENDSTOPC $2,575 million
ENDSTOPD $2,450 million.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_12'>A Consumption
ENDSTOPB Net taxes
ENDSTOPC Exports
ENDSTOPD Imports.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_13'>A will generally be reported at a higher value than it would be otherwise.
ENDSTOPB will be growing at a faster rate than official figures report.
ENDSTOPC will generally be reported at a lower value than it would be otherwise.
ENDSTOPD growth is unchanged by the working population undertaking activities
themselves.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_14'>A cyclically unemployed.
ENDSTOPB structurally unemployed.
ENDSTOPC involuntarily unemployed.
ENDSTOPD not part of the labour force.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_15'>A its welfare payment bill will fall.
ENDSTOPB its income tax revenue rises.
ENDSTOPC its production possibility curve shifts outwards.
ENDSTOPD it is operating inside its production possibility curve.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_16'>A risen by approximately 6%.
ENDSTOPB fallen by approximately 6%.
ENDSTOPC risen by approximately 11%.
ENDSTOPD fallen by approximately 11%.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_17'>A an appreciation of the domestic currency.
ENDSTOPB a fall in business confidence.
ENDSTOPC a fall in interest rates.
ENDSTOPD an increase in the rate of income tax.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_18'>A spending is less than income.
ENDSTOPB spending is equal to income.
ENDSTOPC saving is more than expenditure.
ENDSTOPD spending is greater than income.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_19'>A shift the long run and short run aggregate supply curves downwards.
ENDSTOPB shift the long run and short run aggregate supply curves upwards.
ENDSTOPC not shift the short run aggregate supply but will shift the long run aggregate
supply curves downwards.
ENDSTOPD shift the short run aggregate supply curve downwards and leave the long run
aggregate supply curve unchanged.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_20'>A 18
ENDSTOPB 4
ENDSTOPC 12
ENDSTOPD 8.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_21'>A reduce government expenditure.
ENDSTOPB increase the level of protectionism by raising tariffs and implementing quotas.
ENDSTOPC decrease the rate of income tax.
ENDSTOPD increase the level of unemployment benefits.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_22'>A a decrease in loans.
ENDSTOPB a decrease in aggregate demand.
ENDSTOPC an increase in the rate of interest.
ENDSTOPD a decrease in the rate of interest.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_23'>A asset motive for holding money.
ENDSTOPB precautionary motive for holding money.
ENDSTOPC speculative motive for holding money.
ENDSTOPD transactions motive for holding money.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_24'>A Consumers pay a higher price, producers receive a lower price and the
government receives tariff income.
ENDSTOPB Consumers pay a lower price, producers receive a higher price and the
government loses tariff income.
ENDSTOPC Consumers pay a higher price, producers receive a higher price and the
government receives tariff income.
ENDSTOPD Consumers pay a lower price, producers receive a lower price and the
government loses tariff income.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_25'>A Domestic consumers of the good
ENDSTOPB Domestic producers of the good
ENDSTOPC International producers of the good
ENDSTOPD International consumers of the good.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2023_choices_26'>A purchased in Scotland and sold back in Toronto.
ENDSTOPB purchased in Toronto and sold back in Scotland.
ENDSTOPC sold in both Scotland and Toronto.
ENDSTOPD purchased in both Scotland and Toronto.</string>"

</resources>