<resources>
    <string name='sep2022_que_1'>Which one of the following most accurately describes microeconomic topics?</string>
    <string name='sep2022_que_2'>In general, increased investment in capital goods will lead to:</string>
    <string name='sep2022_que_3'>An increase in the price of frozen yoghurt would lead to:</string>
    "<string name='sep2022_que_4'>A significant increase in income is least likely to increase the demand for which of the
following?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2022_que_5'>If the demand for a good increases from 200 units to 400 units when the price falls
from £16 to £12, then the price elasticity of demand using the arc method is equal to:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2022_que_6'>Food outlets in airport terminals are able to charge a higher price than their high street
equivalent because demand for food in airport terminals is:</string>"
    <string name='sep2022_que_7'>The supply curve will shift to the left when:</string>
    "<string name='sep2022_que_8'>If the demand curve is more price inelastic than the supply curve, then a subsidy will
benefit:</string>"
    <string name='sep2022_que_9'>The marginal cost curve:</string>
    <string name='sep2022_que_10'>What type of cost best describes the repayment of a bank loan for a firm?</string>
    <string name='sep2022_que_11'>In the long run, firms will produce as long as the price they charge:</string>
    "<string name='sep2022_que_12'>A firm is operating in a perfectly competitive industry and in long-run equilibrium.
An increase in wages would lead to:</string>"
    <string name='sep2022_que_13'>The marginal revenue curve for a monopoly is:</string>
    <string name='sep2022_que_14'>Which of the following is an example of a government policy conflict?</string>
    <string name='sep2022_que_15'>The circular flow of the income model assumes that injections:</string>
    "<string name='sep2022_que_16'>In an economy, investment spending is £240 billion, savings are £160 billion,
government spending is £80 billion, imports are £120 billion and tax is £80 billion.
What is the value of exports in this economy?</string>"
    <string name='sep2022_que_17'>If the marginal propensity to consume is 0.6, then the multiplier assuming no taxes is:</string>
    "<string name='sep2022_que_18'>In order to determine real national income, the nominal national income is adjusted
for:</string>"
    <string name='sep2022_que_19'>Policies that are designed to support the supply side of the economy do not include:</string>
    <string name='sep2022_que_20'>During an economic boom, the government fiscal position is likely to:</string>
    <string name='sep2022_que_21'>In order to avoid the problem of fiscal drag, the government should:</string>
    <string name='sep2022_que_22'>People hold cash in order to make general purchases. This is known as:</string>
    <string name='sep2022_que_23'>An increase in the money supply will:</string>
    <string name='sep2022_que_24'>Structural unemployment most commonly arises:</string>
    "<string name='sep2022_que_25'>Given a population of 24 million people, with 12 million employed and 2 million
unemployed, what is the size of the labour force?</string>"
    <string name='sep2022_que_26'>Cost-push inflation may be likely to arise following:</string>

</resources>