<resources>"<string name='sep2006_choices_1'>A a choice between the production of consumer goods and the production of
capital goods
ENDSTOPB the establishment of freedom of entry and exit
ENDSTOPC the establishment of a system of market prices
ENDSTOPD a decision to be made on the degree to which capital will be used in the
production process rather than labour</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_2'>A quantity of productive inputs
ENDSTOPB quantity of inputs on one axis and quantity of outputs on the other axis
ENDSTOPC quantities of finished goods
ENDSTOPD prices of productive inputs</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_3'>A An increase in labour productivity in industry X.
ENDSTOPB A fall in price of raw materials used to produce Good X.
ENDSTOPC An increase in real wages in industry X.
ENDSTOPD A government subsidy on the production of Good X.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_4'>A A rise in the price charged to consumers of £10.
ENDSTOPB A rise in the price charged to consumers of less than £10.
ENDSTOPC No change in the price charged to consumers.
ENDSTOPD A fall in the price charged to consumers.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_5'>A the demand curve for Good X to shift to the left, and the demand curve for
Good Y to shift to the left
ENDSTOPB the demand curve for Good X to shift to the left, and the demand curve for
Good Y to shift to the right
ENDSTOPC the quantity demanded of Good X to fall, and the demand curve for Good Y to
shift to the left
ENDSTOPD the quantity demanded of Good X to fall, and the demand curve for Good Y to
shift to the right</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_6'>A 1 Good X and 4 Good Y
ENDSTOPB 2 Good X and 3 Good Y
ENDSTOPC 3 Good X and 2 Good Y
ENDSTOPD 4 Good X and 1 Good Y</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_7'>A The short run average cost declines.
ENDSTOPB If inputs are doubled then output less than doubles.
ENDSTOPC An increase in the variable factor of production holding the fixed factor of
production constant leads to a higher increase in output.
ENDSTOPD The long run average cost curve declines.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_8'>A average total cost equals marginal cost
ENDSTOPB average revenue is greater than marginal cost
ENDSTOPC price is greater than average total cost
ENDSTOPD average total cost is less than marginal cost</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_9'>A Under perfect competition, in the long run all firms make only normal profits.
ENDSTOPB Firms under monopolistic competition produce homogeneous products.
ENDSTOPC Under oligopoly firms make decisions taking into account the possible
reactions of their competitors.
ENDSTOPD Under monopoly, a profit maximising firm with positive marginal costs
always produces in the region of price elastic demand.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_10'>A the firm has to charge a price higher than the marginal cost of producing the
last unit
ENDSTOPB any decision by the monopolist to sell an additional unit of output does not
affect product price
ENDSTOPC the firm has to reduce the price on all previous units sold in order to sell the
additional unit
ENDSTOPD the law of diminishing returns directly affects the price of an imperfectly
competitive firm s price</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_11'>A a firm s competitors match both its price increases and price decreases
ENDSTOPB one firm in the industry sets the price for all other firms
ENDSTOPC a firm s competitors match its price reductions but ignore its price increases
ENDSTOPD prices can either rise or fall; it depends on what happens to a firm s
competitors prices</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_12'>A rightward shift of the supply curve for Good X
ENDSTOPB leftward shift of the supply curve for Good X
ENDSTOPC rightward shift of the demand curve for Good X
ENDSTOPD leftward shift of the demand curve for Good X</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_13'>A the price of Good X times the marginal product of capital
ENDSTOPB the price of Good X times the marginal product of labour
ENDSTOPC the price of Good X divided by the marginal product of labour
ENDSTOPD the marginal product of labour divided by the price of Good X</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_14'>A salaries of firemen
ENDSTOPB dividend payments to shareholders
ENDSTOPC state pension payments
ENDSTOPD company profits</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_15'>A the marginal tax rate will be less than their average tax rate
ENDSTOPB the marginal tax rate will be greater than their average tax rate
ENDSTOPC the marginal tax rate will be equal to their average tax rate
ENDSTOPD the marginal tax rate will initially be less than but eventually greater than their
average tax rate</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_16'>A savings, taxes and import expenditure
ENDSTOPB savings, taxes and government expenditure
ENDSTOPC investment, government expenditure and exports
ENDSTOPD investment, saving and taxes</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_17'>A Aggregate expenditure would rise by £5 million.
ENDSTOPB Aggregate expenditure would rise by £15 million.
ENDSTOPC Aggregate expenditure would rise by £26.6 million.
ENDSTOPD Aggregate expenditure would rise by £80 million.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_18'>A £150 million
ENDSTOPB £130 million
ENDSTOPC £120 million
ENDSTOPD £110 million</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_19'>A The demand for money is interest elastic and private investment is interest
inelastic.
ENDSTOPB The demand for money is interest inelastic and private investment is interest
elastic.
ENDSTOPC The demand for money and private investment are both interest inelastic.
ENDSTOPD The demand for money and private investment are both interest elastic.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_20'>A the government spends more money
ENDSTOPB the government buys Treasury bills from the public
ENDSTOPC a citizen buys a newly issued corporate bond
ENDSTOPD a firm obtains an overdraft from a bank</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_21'>A If nominal Gross Domestic Product (GDP) rises by 8 per cent and the GDP
deflator rises by 5 per cent then real GDP per capita must have risen.
ENDSTOPB A nominal depreciation of a country s exchange rate represents a real
depreciation if the domestic inflation rate is less than the foreign inflation rate.
ENDSTOPC An increase in real income will lead to a rise in the demand for real money
balances.
ENDSTOPD Real interest rates are positive if the expected rate of inflation is less than the
nominal rate of interest.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_22'>A Increased government expenditure on domestically produced goods.
ENDSTOPB Increased money supply.
ENDSTOPC Reduced corporate and personal taxation.
ENDSTOPD A privatisation programme.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_23'>A An increase in the marginal propensity to save.
ENDSTOPB A decrease in the marginal propensity to consume.
ENDSTOPC A decrease in the marginal propensity to import.
ENDSTOPD An increase in income tax rates.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_24'>A Monetarists advocate the use of an expansionary monetary policy while
Keynesians do not
ENDSTOPB Monetarists advocate the use of an expansionary fiscal policy while
Keynesians do not
ENDSTOPC Keynesians advocate the use of an expansionary fiscal policy while
Monetarists do not
ENDSTOPD Keynesians advocate the use of an expansionary monetary policy while
Monetarists do not</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_25'>A unemployment benefit
ENDSTOPB government consumption expenditure
ENDSTOPC information on job availability
ENDSTOPD the money supply</string>"
    "<string name='sep2006_choices_26'>A They have improved by 75 per cent.
ENDSTOPB They have improved by 37.5 per cent.
ENDSTOPC They have deteriorated by 75 per cent.
ENDSTOPD They have deteriorated by 37.5 per cent.</string>"
</resources>