<resources>
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_1'>A natural resources, labour and money.
ENDSTOPB labour, money and factories.
ENDSTOPC natural resources, capital and factories.
ENDSTOPD natural resources, labour and capital.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_2'>A exists only in economies which rely on the market mechanism.
ENDSTOPB could be eliminated if we force prices to fall.
ENDSTOPC means that there are shortages of some goods.
ENDSTOPD exists because there are insufficient resources to satisfy human wants.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_3'>A A change in the price of Good X.
ENDSTOPB A change in the price of other goods.
ENDSTOPC A change in consumer incomes.
ENDSTOPD A change in consumer tastes.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_4'>A The effect on price is indeterminate but quantity will fall.
ENDSTOPB The effect on price is indeterminate but quantity will rise.
ENDSTOPC The effect on quantity is indeterminate but price will rise.
ENDSTOPD The effect on quantity is indeterminate but price will fall.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_5'>A The marginal utility from each good consumed will be higher for X than for Y
and X will have a higher total utility.
ENDSTOPB The marginal utility from each good consumed will be higher for X than for Y
and X will have a lower total utility.
ENDSTOPC The marginal utility from each good consumed will be lower for X than for Y
and X will have a higher total utility.
ENDSTOPD The marginal utility from each good consumed will be lower for X than for Y
and X will have a lower total utility.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_6'>A having insurance makes an individual less careful.
ENDSTOPB having insurance makes an individual more careful.
ENDSTOPC the people taking out the insurance are those who have the highest risk.
ENDSTOPD the people taking out the insurance are those who have the highest risk
aversion.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_7'>A different consumer’s tastes but not different quality products.
ENDSTOPB same quality products.
ENDSTOPC different quality products reflected in different production costs.
ENDSTOPD different varieties offered at the same price.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_8'>A Short run average total cost falls as output rises.
ENDSTOPB Long run average total cost falls as output rises.
ENDSTOPC Long run average total cost rises as output rises.
ENDSTOPD Short run average total cost rises as output rises.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_9'>A The firm will equate its marginal costs to its average revenue.
ENDSTOPB The firm will equate its marginal costs to its marginal revenue.
ENDSTOPC The firm’s average revenue exceeds its average variable costs of production.
ENDSTOPD The firm will make only normal profits.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_10'>A the firm has to charge a price higher than the marginal cost of producing the
last unit.
ENDSTOPB any decision by the monopolist to sell an additional unit of output does not
affect the price.
ENDSTOPC the firm has to reduce the price on all previous units sold in order to sell the
additional unit.
ENDSTOPD the law of diminishing returns directly affects the price of an imperfectly
competitive firm’s product.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_11'>A each firm will not take account of its rival’s reactions when making its
decision.
ENDSTOPB the price set by one firm will not influence the price of the other firm.
ENDSTOPC in avoiding the worst possible outcome the firms will fail to reach the best
possible outcome.
ENDSTOPD in avoiding the worst possible outcome the firms will succeed in reaching the
best possible outcome.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_12'>A franchise.
ENDSTOPB joint venture.
ENDSTOPC merger.
ENDSTOPD licensing agreement.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_13'>A a firm charges customers different prices according to how much they
purchase.
ENDSTOPB consumers are grouped into independent markets and a separate price is
charged in each market.
ENDSTOPC a firm charges each customer the maximum price he/she is prepared to pay.
ENDSTOPD different firms charge different prices for the same product.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_14'>A shift the supply curve for Good X up by less than £3 and increase the price by
less than £3.
ENDSTOPB shift the supply curve for Good X up by less than £3 and increase the price by
more than £3.
ENDSTOPC shift the supply curve for Good X up by £3 and increase the price by £3.
ENDSTOPD shift the supply curve for Good X up by £3 and increase the price by less than
£3.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_15'>A 75
ENDSTOPB 120
ENDSTOPC 125
ENDSTOPD 150</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_16'>A increases in a recession and falls in a boom.
ENDSTOPB arises when the unemployed lack the skills needed by existing and newly
created jobs.
ENDSTOPC arises when those seeking work give up hope of finding a job.
ENDSTOPD occurs as the result of a transition from one job to another.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_17'>A A decrease in interest rates.
ENDSTOPB A rise in exchange rates.
ENDSTOPC A rise in government expenditure.
ENDSTOPD An increase in business confidence.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_18'>A If nominal Gross Domestic Product (GDP) rises by 5 per cent with no inflation
then the real GDP will have risen by 5 per cent.
ENDSTOPB A nominal depreciation of a country’s exchange rate represents a real
depreciation if the domestic inflation rate is less than the foreign inflation rate.
ENDSTOPC An increase in real income will lead to a rise in the demand for real money
balances.
ENDSTOPD Real interest rates are positive if the expected rate of inflation is greater than
the nominal rate of interest.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_19'>A domestic inflation rates are unavoidably linked across national boundaries.
ENDSTOPB domestic inflation in one country can lead to inflation in another.
ENDSTOPC domestic inflation is dictated outside the bounds that would have constrained
prices in a fixed rate regime.
ENDSTOPD none of the above.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_20'>A the government spends more money.
ENDSTOPB the government buys Treasury bills from the public.
ENDSTOPC a citizen buys a newly issued corporate bond.
ENDSTOPD a firm obtains an overdraft from a bank.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_21'>A an increase in aggregate demand and a reduction in real output and
unemployment.
ENDSTOPB an increase in aggregate demand, real output and unemployment.
ENDSTOPC an increase in aggregate demand and real output and a reduction in
unemployment.
ENDSTOPD a reduction in aggregate demand and real output and an increase in
unemployment.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_22'>A Expansionary fiscal policy.
ENDSTOPB Increasing the money supply.
ENDSTOPC A reduction in trade union powers.
ENDSTOPD Better education and training.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_23'>A I only.
ENDSTOPB II only.
ENDSTOPC I and II only.
ENDSTOPD I, II and III.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_24'>A Increase unemployment benefit
ENDSTOPB Increase government expenditure
ENDSTOPC Increase the money supply
ENDSTOPD Increase information flows on job availability</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_25'>A comparative advantage.
ENDSTOPB absolute advantage.
ENDSTOPC different factor endowments.
ENDSTOPD all of the above.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2014_choices_26'>A £1 million
ENDSTOPB £20 million
ENDSTOPC £200 million
ENDSTOPD £400 million</string>"



</resources>