<resources>
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_1'>A equal to total revenue minus total variable cost.
ENDSTOPB constant.
ENDSTOPC the cost in terms of the best foregone alternative.
ENDSTOPD equal to a firm’s supernormal profits.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_2'>A An increase in consumers’ incomes.
ENDSTOPB A rise in the price of cars.
ENDSTOPC An increase in the price of petrol.
ENDSTOPD An increase in the price charged to use public transport.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_3'>A increase the demand for fruit sorbet and strawberries.
ENDSTOPB decrease the demand for fruit sorbet and increase the demand for strawberries.
ENDSTOPC decrease the demand for fruit sorbet and strawberries.
ENDSTOPD increase the demand for fruit sorbet and decrease the demand for strawberries.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_4'>A risk lovers.
ENDSTOPB risk averse.
ENDSTOPC risk seekers.
ENDSTOPD risk neutral.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_5'>A Moral hazard describes the fact that people who know that they are a
particularly bad risk are more inclined to take out insurance.
ENDSTOPB Moral hazard describes the fact that a policyholder may act in a way which
makes the insured event more likely to occur.
ENDSTOPC Moral hazard describes the fact that people who know that they are a
particularly bad risk are less inclined to take out insurance.
ENDSTOPD Moral hazard describes the risk that an insurance company will face false
insurance claims.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_6'>A different consumers’ tastes but not different quality products.
ENDSTOPB same quality products.
ENDSTOPC different quality products with different production costs.
ENDSTOPD different varieties of the same product offered at the same price.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_7'>A short run average total cost falls as output rises.
ENDSTOPB long run average total cost falls as output rises.
ENDSTOPC long run average total cost rises as output rises.
ENDSTOPD short run average total cost rises as output rises.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_8'>A average physical product falls.
ENDSTOPB average physical product rises.
ENDSTOPC marginal physical product falls.
ENDSTOPD marginal physical product rises.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_9'>A Marginal cost exceeds average variable cost.
ENDSTOPB Marginal cost equals average variable cost.
ENDSTOPC Marginal cost is less than average variable cost.
ENDSTOPD Marginal cost exceeds average total cost.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_10'>A the firm has to charge a price higher than the marginal cost of producing the
last unit.
ENDSTOPB any decision by the monopolist to sell an additional unit of output does not
affect price.
ENDSTOPC the firm has to reduce the price on all previous units sold in order to sell the
additional unit.
ENDSTOPD the law of diminishing returns directly affects the price of an imperfectly
competitive firm’s product.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_11'>A Establishment of world brands.
ENDSTOPB Increasing travel, creating global consumers.
ENDSTOPC Per capita income converging among industrialised nations.
ENDSTOPD Reduction of tariff barriers.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_12'>A comparative advantage.
ENDSTOPB absolute advantage.
ENDSTOPC different factor endowments.
ENDSTOPD all of the above.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_13'>A increases in a recession and falls in a boom.
ENDSTOPB arises when the unemployed lack the skills needed by newly created jobs.
ENDSTOPC arises when those seeking work give up hope of finding a job.
ENDSTOPD occurs as the result of a transition from one job to another.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_14' formatted="false">A 5.9%
ENDSTOPB 5.3%
ENDSTOPC 5.0%
ENDSTOPD 6.3%</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_15'>A decreases and national income is lower.
ENDSTOPB decreases and national income is higher.
ENDSTOPC increases and national income is lower.
ENDSTOPD increases and national income is higher.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_16'>A Menu costs.
ENDSTOPB Cost of employing extra resources.
ENDSTOPC Arbitrary redistribution of wealth from lenders to borrowers.
ENDSTOPD Arbitrary redistribution of wealth from borrowers to lenders.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_17'>A Savings, taxes and investment are withdrawals.
ENDSTOPB Exports, imports and government expenditure are withdrawals.
ENDSTOPC Investment, government expenditure and exports are injections.
ENDSTOPD Investment, exports and consumption are injections.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_18'>A I only.
ENDSTOPB II only.
ENDSTOPC I and II only.
ENDSTOPD I, II and III.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_19'>A The US dollar could appreciate and the Chinese renminbi depreciate.
ENDSTOPB The US dollar could depreciate and the Chinese renminbi depreciate.
ENDSTOPC The US dollar could appreciate and the Chinese renminbi appreciate.
ENDSTOPD The US dollar could depreciate and the Chinese renminbi appreciate.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_20'>A speculative motive for holding money.
ENDSTOPB transactions motive for holding money.
ENDSTOPC precautionary motive for holding money.
ENDSTOPD asset motive for holding money.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_21'>A The sale of Treasury Bills in the financial markets.
ENDSTOPB A demand for special deposits from the commercial banks to be placed with
the central bank.
ENDSTOPC A rise in the central bank lending rate.
ENDSTOPD A lowering of the reserve requirements on commercial banks.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_22'>A the influence of fiscal policy on the level of inflation and unemployment.
ENDSTOPB the influence of monetary policy on the level of inflation and unemployment.
ENDSTOPC a negative relationship between inflation and unemployment.
ENDSTOPD a positive relationship between inflation and unemployment.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_23'>A an increase in the quantity of labour demanded.
ENDSTOPB the labour supply curve to shift to the left.
ENDSTOPC an increase in the quantity of labour supplied.
ENDSTOPD the demand for the labour curve to shift to the left.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_24'>A Time lags.
ENDSTOPB Uncertainty.
ENDSTOPC Crowding out.
ENDSTOPD The accelerator.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_25'>A an increase in aggregate demand and a reduction in real output and
unemployment.
ENDSTOPB an increase in aggregate demand, real output and unemployment.
ENDSTOPC an increase in aggregate demand and real output and a reduction in
unemployment.
ENDSTOPD a reduction in aggregate demand and real output and an increase in
unemployment.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2018_choices_26'>A government expenditure.
ENDSTOPB taxation.
ENDSTOPC money supply.
ENDSTOPD transfer payments.</string>"

</resources>