<resources>
    "<string name='sep2009_que_1'>What is the combined effect of an increase in the cost of production and a rise in
consumer income on the equilibrium price and quantity of a normal good?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_que_2'>If the price elasticity of demand for a product is -2, a reduction in its price from 20
pence to 19 pence will result in an increase in demand of:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_que_3'>If rail travel is an inferior good, which one of the following will lead to a shift of its
demand curve to the left?</string>"
    <string name='sep2009_que_4'>Which one of the following is NOT a barrier to entry into a monopoly market?</string>
    <string name='sep2009_que_5'>In the short run, a firm’s average fixed costs of production will:</string>
    "<string name='sep2009_que_6'>Assuming that the marginal and average cost curves are unchanged, following an
increase in demand, firms in a perfectly competitive market may:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_que_7'>Other things being equal, a fall in a monopolist’s fixed costs of production, which
does not lead to new entrants, causes:</string>"
    <string name='sep2009_que_8'>A price ceiling set below the free market price results in:</string>
    <string name='sep2009_que_9'>A profit maximizing monopolist would reduce its price if:</string>
    "<string name='sep2009_que_10'>Which of the following is NOT a prediction of the theory of monopolistic
competition?</string>"
    <string name='sep2009_que_11'>Which of the following is NOT an axiom of the expected utility theorem?</string>
    "<string name='sep2009_que_12'>Under conditions of diminishing marginal product with marginal product being
positive, a firm will find that as it employs more of a variable factor of production in
the short run total product will:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_que_13'>A movement along a consumer’s indifference curve from left to right means that the
consumer’s:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_que_14'>When taxes on all income are progressive then as income increases the marginal tax
rate will:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_que_15'>Given the following data for an economy, what is the value of its Gross National
Income?
Consumption expenditure £140 million
Investment £40 million
Government expenditure £80 million
Exports £20 million
Imports £60 million
Net property income from abroad £20 million</string>"
    <string name='sep2009_que_16'>In the circular flow of income model which of the following is TRUE?</string>
    <string name='sep2009_que_17'>Which one of the following is NOT part of the Gross National Income?</string>
    "<string name='sep2009_que_18'>Which one of the following situations will lead to the most crowding out following an
increase of government expenditure?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_que_19'>Government attempts to increase the money supply through open market operations
are likely to cause short term interest rates to:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_que_20'>An open economy has the following characteristics:
Consumption expenditure = 0.6Y
Investment expenditure = £200 million
Government expenditure = £500 million
Exports = £300 million
Imports = 0.3Y
The rate of taxation is 50% of all income, where Y is national income.
Determine the value of Y.</string>"
    <string name='sep2009_que_21'>Other things being equal, an increase in the fiscal surplus will lead to a:</string>
    "<string name='sep2009_que_22'>The direct impact of open market operations, where the central bank purchases
government securities, is to:</string>"
    <string name='sep2009_que_23'>In IS/LM analysis an increase in government spending may be illustrated as follows:</string>
    <string name='sep2009_que_24'>The accelerator principle implies that:</string>
    "<string name='sep2009_que_25'>Given the following labour hours to produce 1 unit of Goods X and Y, which of the
statements below is TRUE?</string>"
    <string name='sep2009_que_26'>Other things being equal, which one of the following statements is always TRUE?</string>

</resources>