<resources>
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_1'>A An increase in labour productivity in the industry producing Good X
ENDSTOPB A fall in the price of raw materials used to produce Good X
ENDSTOPC An increase in real wages in the industry producing Good X
ENDSTOPD A government subsidy on the production of Good X.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_2'>A The cost of producing Good X in money terms
ENDSTOPB The next best alternative use to which the factors of production used to produce
Good X could be put
ENDSTOPC The stream of services provided by Good X over its entire lifetime
ENDSTOPD The production of Good X foregone in the previous year to enable Good X to
be produced this year.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_3'>A attempts to maximise sales after assuming that the other firm will attempt to
maximise sales.
ENDSTOPB assumes the other firm will produce a given output and then chooses its
profit-maximising output.
ENDSTOPC assumes the other firm’s price is given and then chooses its profit-maximising
price.
ENDSTOPD will attempt to collude with the other firm so as to set a price and output level
that will maximise industry level profits.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_4'>A Equilibrium price will be equal to marginal cost
ENDSTOPB There are no barriers to entry
ENDSTOPC Each firm produces a differentiated product
ENDSTOPD Only normal profits are made in the long run.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_5'>A It is price inelastic
ENDSTOPB It is price elastic
ENDSTOPC It is infinitely price elastic
ENDSTOPD It has zero price elasticity.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_6'>A consume more of Good X and less of Good Y.
ENDSTOPB consume less of Good X and more of Good Y.
ENDSTOPC increase consumption of both Goods X and Y.
ENDSTOPD decrease consumption of both Goods X and Y.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_7'>A ratio of the prices of the two goods.
ENDSTOPB income of the consumer divided by the price of each good.
ENDSTOPC ratio of the total utility of each good divided by the price of each good.
ENDSTOPD ratio of the total utilities of both goods.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_8'>A expand its output in order to increase its total revenue.
ENDSTOPB shutdown and produce no units of Good X in order to minimise its losses.
ENDSTOPC reduce its output to 1,000 units of Good X in order to reduce its total cost of
production by £6,000.
ENDSTOPD continue producing 2,000 units of Good X in the short run but not in the long
run.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_9'>A average cost curve.
ENDSTOPB average variable cost curve.
ENDSTOPC marginal cost curve above the lowest point of the average total cost curve.
ENDSTOPD marginal cost curve above the lowest point of the average variable cost curve.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_10'>A less than £10 and increase the price by less than £10.
ENDSTOPB less than £10 and increase the price by more than £10.
ENDSTOPC £10 and increase the price by £10.
ENDSTOPD £10 and increase the price by less than £10.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_11'>A A firm doubles its inputs of capital and labour and its output more than
doubles
ENDSTOPB A firm doubles the number of products it produces and also doubles its
research budget
ENDSTOPC A firm produces a new product and in so doing lowers the average cost of
producing its existing products
ENDSTOPD A firm produces a new product and lowers the price it charges on its existing
products.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_12'>A Economies of scale
ENDSTOPB Constant returns to scale
ENDSTOPC Diseconomies of scale
ENDSTOPD Diminishing marginal productivity.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_13'>A that will be bought by consumers only at a low price.
ENDSTOPB whose quantity purchased will decline if consumers’ income rises.
ENDSTOPC that is of poor quality compared to more expensive versions of the good.
ENDSTOPD that is bought only by people on low incomes.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_14'>A Increasing social security benefits
ENDSTOPB Increasing the money supply
ENDSTOPC Reducing corporate and personal taxation
ENDSTOPD Increasing government expenditure aimed at exploiting the multiplier effect.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_15'>A shift to the right.
ENDSTOPB shift to the left.
ENDSTOPC remain unchanged.
ENDSTOPD become upward sloping.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_16'>A there will be no unemployment in the economy.
ENDSTOPB the marginal propensity to consume must be greater than the marginal propensity
to save.
ENDSTOPC consumption will be equal to or greater than income.
ENDSTOPD there may or may not be unemployment.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_17'>A increase the demand for money and increase aggregate demand.
ENDSTOPB decrease the demand for money and increase aggregate demand.
ENDSTOPC increase the demand for money and decrease aggregate demand.
ENDSTOPD decrease the demand for money and decrease aggregate demand.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_18'>A If nominal Gross Domestic Product (GDP) rises by 5%, then the real GDP may
have risen, fallen or remained unchanged
ENDSTOPB If the money supply falls by 20% and the price level falls by less than 20%, then
the real money supply falls
ENDSTOPC An increase in real income will lead to a rise in the demand for real money
balances
ENDSTOPD Real interest rates are positive if the expected rate of inflation is greater than the
nominal rate of interest.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_19'>A £200 million.
ENDSTOPB £312.5 million.
ENDSTOPC £1,000 million.
ENDSTOPD £800 million.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_20'>A surplus of £125 billion.
ENDSTOPB deficit of £125 billion.
ENDSTOPC surplus of £25 billion.
ENDSTOPD deficit of £25 billion.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_21'>A £150 million
ENDSTOPB £200 million
ENDSTOPC £450 million
ENDSTOPD None of the above.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_22'>A rise as the short-term interest rate rises.
ENDSTOPB rise as the short-term interest rate falls.
ENDSTOPC fall as the short-term interest rate rises.
ENDSTOPD fall as the short-term interest rate falls.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_23'>A the influence of fiscal policy on the level of inflation and unemployment.
ENDSTOPB the influence of monetary policy on the level of inflation and unemployment.
ENDSTOPC an inverse relationship between inflation and unemployment.
ENDSTOPD a positive relationship between inflation and unemployment.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_24'>A £250 million.
ENDSTOPB £260 million.
ENDSTOPC £270 million.
ENDSTOPD £280 million.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_25'>A adding indirect taxes and adding subsidies.
ENDSTOPB adding indirect taxes and subtracting subsidies.
ENDSTOPC subtracting indirect taxes and subtracting subsidies.
ENDSTOPD subtracting indirect taxes and adding subsidies.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2020_choices_26'>A There will be demand deficient unemployment
ENDSTOPB The production of goods will generate sufficient demand to ensure they are
sold
ENDSTOPC There may be structural unemployment or frictional unemployment if markets
do not work efficiently
ENDSTOPD Aggregate demand and aggregate supply will always be equal.</string>"

</resources>