<resources>"<string name='sep2007_choices_1'>A a perfect substitute
ENDSTOPB an imperfect substitute
ENDSTOPC a perfect complement
ENDSTOPD an imperfect complement</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_2'>A a rightward shift of the demand curve for Good X
ENDSTOPB a leftward shift of the demand curve for Good X
ENDSTOPC a movement along the demand curve for Good X from left to right
ENDSTOPD a movement along the demand curve for Good X from right to left</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_3'>A a rise in the quantity demanded of whisky by 20 per cent
ENDSTOPB a rise in the quantity demanded of whisky by 10 per cent
ENDSTOPC a fall in the quantity demanded of whisky by 20 per cent
ENDSTOPD a fall in the quantity demanded of whisky by 10 per cent</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_4'>A shift the entire budget line to the left
ENDSTOPB shift the entire budget line to the right
ENDSTOPC make the budget line steeper
ENDSTOPD make the budget line less steep</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_5'>A a rightward shift of the demand curve for Good X
ENDSTOPB a leftward shift of the demand curve for Good X
ENDSTOPC a movement along the demand curve for Good X from left to right
ENDSTOPD a movement along the demand curve for Good X from right to left</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_6'>A Investment A dominates Investment ENDSTOPB in over 50% of possible scenarios.
B Investment A has a lower standard deviation of returns than Investment B.
ENDSTOPC Investment A dominates Investment B in 100% of possible scenarios.
ENDSTOPD Investment A has a higher expected rate of return than Investment B.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_7'>A The taking out of an insurance policy makes it more likely that the insured
against event will occur than if no insurance policy is taken out.
ENDSTOPB Insurance companies tend to select only good risk customers.
ENDSTOPC Bad risk customers are able to obtain insurance on the same terms as good risk
customers.
ENDSTOPD People who know they are particularly bad risks are more inclined to take out
insurance than those who know they are good risks.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_8'>A £81
ENDSTOPB £9
ENDSTOPC £1
ENDSTOPD -£1</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_9'>A Average product can never be above marginal product.
ENDSTOPB Average product can never be less than marginal product.
ENDSTOPC Marginal product can never become negative.
ENDSTOPD Average product can never become negative.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_10'>A a consumer’s utility will rise
ENDSTOPB a consumer’s utility will be unchanged
ENDSTOPC a consumer’s utility will fall
ENDSTOPD a consumer’s money income is unchanged</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_11'>A M0, M1, M4 but not M3
ENDSTOPB M0 and M4, but not M1 and M3
ENDSTOPC M0, but not M1, M3 and M4
ENDSTOPD M0, M1, M3 and M4</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_12'>A Increasing returns to scale.
ENDSTOPB Constant returns to scale.
ENDSTOPC Decreasing returns to scale.
ENDSTOPD The law of diminishing marginal returns.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_13'>A average fixed costs
ENDSTOPB average variable costs
ENDSTOPC average total costs
ENDSTOPD average normal profit level</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_14'>A lower the price and raise output
ENDSTOPB maintain the existing price and output
ENDSTOPC lower the price but maintain existing output
ENDSTOPD maintain the existing price and raise output</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_15'>A An increase in local government expenditure.
ENDSTOPB An increase in grants from central government to nationalised industries.
ENDSTOPC An increase in transfer payments to recipients of state welfare benefits.
ENDSTOPD An increase in the interest rate paid on the national debt.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_16'>A S = I
ENDSTOPB S + T + M = I + G + X
ENDSTOPC S + T + X = M + T + G
ENDSTOPD None of the above</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_17'>A 20
ENDSTOPB 15
ENDSTOPC 10
ENDSTOPD none of the above</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_18'>A 0.1
ENDSTOPB 0.9
ENDSTOPC 0.8
ENDSTOPD 0.7</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_19'>A A decrease in the marginal propensity to save.
ENDSTOPB A decrease in the marginal propensity to consume.
ENDSTOPC A decrease in the marginal rate of taxation.
ENDSTOPD A decrease in the marginal propensity to import.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_20'>A Real interest rates are negative if the expected rate of inflation exceeds the
nominal rate of interest.
ENDSTOPB Assuming a constant price level, a rise in nominal wages is also a rise in real
wages.
ENDSTOPC An increase in real income will lead to a reduced demand for real money
balances.
ENDSTOPD If nominal Gross Domestic Product (GDP) rises by 10 per cent and the GDP
deflator rises by 5 per cent then real GDP has risen.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_21'>A The annual gap between total government tax receipts and total government
expenditure.
ENDSTOPB The total amount owed by a country to the rest of the world.
ENDSTOPC The net accumulation of a country’s budget deficits.
ENDSTOPD The net accumulation of a country’s current account deficits in the balance of
payments.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_22'>A Country ENDSTOPB has a comparative advantage in the production of Good X.
B Country B has a comparative advantage in the production of both Good X and
Good Y.
ENDSTOPC Country B has a comparative advantage in the production of Good Y.
ENDSTOPD Country B has no comparative advantage in the production of either good.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_23'>A A rise in the money supply, a fall in the short term rate of interest and a fall in
the price of treasury bills.
ENDSTOPB A rise in the money supply, a fall in the short term rate of interest and a rise in
the price of treasury bills.
ENDSTOPC A rise in the money supply, a rise in the short term rate of interest and a fall in
the price of treasury bills.
ENDSTOPD A rise in the money supply, a rise in the short term rate of interest and a rise in
the price of treasury bills.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_24'>A £300 million, £200 million.
ENDSTOPB £300 million, -£200 million.
ENDSTOPC £200 million, £300 million.
ENDSTOPD £200 million, -£300 million.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_25'>A £25 million
ENDSTOPB £24 million
ENDSTOPC £20 million
ENDSTOPD £6.25 million</string>"
    "<string name='sep2007_choices_26'>A An appreciation of a country’s exchange rate will increase its import volumes
and decrease its export volumes.
ENDSTOPB An appreciation of a country’s exchange rate will increase its import
expenditure and decrease its export revenues.
ENDSTOPC A depreciation of country’s exchange rate will decrease its import volumes
and decrease its export volumes.
ENDSTOPD A depreciation of a country’s exchange rate will decrease its import
expenditure and increase its export revenues.</string>"
</resources>