<resources>
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_1'>A prices are too high.
ENDSTOPB human wants cannot be satisfied.
ENDSTOPC there are shortages of some goods.
ENDSTOPD markets are not perfectly competitive.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_2'>A Opportunity cost is constant.
ENDSTOPB Opportunity cost is equal to total revenue minus total variable cost.
ENDSTOPC Opportunity cost is equal to a firm’s supernormal profits.
ENDSTOPD Opportunity cost is the cost in terms of the best foregone alternative.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_3'>A a change in consumer tastes
ENDSTOPB a change in consumer incomes
ENDSTOPC a change in the price of Good X
ENDSTOPD a change in the price of other goods</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_4'>A a rise in the price of cars
ENDSTOPB an increase in the price of petrol
ENDSTOPC an increase in consumers’ incomes
ENDSTOPD an increase in the price charged to use public transport</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_5'>A higher for A than for ENDSTOPB and A will have a higher total utility.
B higher for A than for B and A will have a lower total utility.
ENDSTOPC lower for A than for B and A will have a higher total utility.
ENDSTOPD lower for A than for B and A will have a lower total utility.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_6'>A having insurance makes an individual less careful.
ENDSTOPB having insurance makes an individual more careful.
ENDSTOPC the individuals who take out insurance are those who pose the highest risk.
ENDSTOPD the individuals who take out insurance are those who have the highest risk
aversion.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_7'>A same quality products.
ENDSTOPB different varieties of the same product offered at the same price.
ENDSTOPC different consumers’ tastes but not different quality products.
ENDSTOPD different quality products with different production costs.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_8'>A 250 units
ENDSTOPB 1,750 units
ENDSTOPC 2,000 units
ENDSTOPD None of the above</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_9'>A constant returns to scale.
ENDSTOPB increasing returns to scale.
ENDSTOPC decreasing returns to scale.
ENDSTOPD the law of diminishing returns.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_10'>A average total cost curve.
ENDSTOPB average variable cost curve.
ENDSTOPC marginal cost curve above the lowest point of the average variable cost curve.
ENDSTOPD marginal cost curve above the lowest point of the average total cost curve.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_11'>A marginal cost.
ENDSTOPB average total cost.
ENDSTOPC average fixed cost.
ENDSTOPD average variable cost.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_12'>A risk sharing
ENDSTOPB entry into new markets
ENDSTOPC capital pooling
ENDSTOPD economies of scale</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_13'>A different firms charge different prices for the same product.
ENDSTOPB a firm charges each customer the maximum price he/she is prepared to pay.
ENDSTOPC a firm charges customers different prices according to how much they
purchase.
ENDSTOPD consumers are grouped into independent markets and a separate price is
charged in each market.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_14'>A the influence of fiscal policy on the level of inflation and unemployment.
ENDSTOPB the influence of monetary policy on the level of inflation and unemployment.
ENDSTOPC a negative relationship between inflation and unemployment.
ENDSTOPD a positive relationship between inflation and unemployment.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_15'>A Country X has an absolute advantage in the production of Good A.
ENDSTOPB Country X has an absolute advantage in the production of Good B.
ENDSTOPC Country Y has a comparative advantage in the production of Good A.
ENDSTOPD Country Y has a comparative advantage in the production of Good B.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_16'>A regional.
ENDSTOPB structural.
ENDSTOPC technological.
ENDSTOPD demand-deficient.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_17'>A 5.0%
ENDSTOPB 5.3%
ENDSTOPC 5.9%
ENDSTOPD 6.3%</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_18'>A an appreciation of the exchange rate
ENDSTOPB an increase in the price of raw materials
ENDSTOPC an increase in profit margins applied by firms
ENDSTOPD an increase in wages above increases in labour productivity</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_19'>A rise in the real wage rate.
ENDSTOPB fall in the real interest rate.
ENDSTOPC rise in the nominal wage rate.
ENDSTOPD rise in the nominal interest rate.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_20'>A Import volumes will increase.
ENDSTOPB Export volumes will increase.
ENDSTOPC Exports become less expensive when measured in the foreign currency.
ENDSTOPD Imports become more expensive when measured in the domestic currency.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_21'>A increase and the domestic money supply fall.
ENDSTOPB increase and the domestic money supply rise.
ENDSTOPC decrease and the domestic money supply fall.
ENDSTOPD decrease and the domestic money supply rise.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_22'>A reduce the cash reserves of commercial banks and reduce the monetary base.
ENDSTOPB reduce the cash reserves of commercial banks and increase the monetary base.
ENDSTOPC increase the cash reserves of commercial banks and reduce the monetary base.
ENDSTOPD increase the cash reserves of commercial banks and increase the monetary
base.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_23'>A an increase in prices
ENDSTOPB a decrease in the rate of interest
ENDSTOPC an increase in real Gross Domestic Product
ENDSTOPD an increase in the frequency of payments to individuals</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_24'>A an increase in aggregate demand, real output and unemployment.
ENDSTOPB an increase in aggregate demand and a reduction in real output and
unemployment.
ENDSTOPC an increase in aggregate demand and real output and a reduction in
unemployment.
ENDSTOPD a reduction in aggregate demand and real output and an increase in
unemployment.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_25'>A lower domestic interest rates and an exchange rate appreciation.
ENDSTOPB lower domestic interest rates and an exchange rate depreciation.
ENDSTOPC higher domestic interest rates and an exchange rate appreciation.
ENDSTOPD higher domestic interest rates and an exchange rate depreciation.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2015_choices_26'>A increase in consumption expenditure caused by lower taxes.
ENDSTOPB increase in interest rates caused by contractionary monetary policy.
ENDSTOPC extent to which government expansionary policy is counteracted by lower
private spending resulting from higher interest rates.
ENDSTOPD extent to which government contractionary policy is counteracted by lower
private spending resulting from lower interest rates.</string>"


</resources>