<resources>
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_1'>A A rise in the price of fuel by 10.5 per cent.
ENDSTOPB A rise in the price of fuel by 9 per cent.
ENDSTOPC A rise in the price of fuel by 12 per cent.
ENDSTOPD A rise in the price of fuel by less than 9 per cent.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_2'>A no change in price and a shortage.
ENDSTOPB a rise in price and quantity sold.
ENDSTOPC a rise in price and a shortage.
ENDSTOPD a rise in price and a surplus.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_3'>A Marginal cost is equal to average variable cost when average variable cost is at
a minimum.
ENDSTOPB Average fixed cost always falls as output rises.
ENDSTOPC Marginal cost cannot exceed average total cost.
ENDSTOPD Average total cost exceeds average variable cost by an amount that declines
with increasing output.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_4'>A There are many firms.
ENDSTOPB Firms sell differentiated products.
ENDSTOPC In the long run monopolistic powers enable firms to make excess profits.
ENDSTOPD A firm can raise its price without losing all its customers.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_5'>A price inelastic.
ENDSTOPB price elastic.
ENDSTOPC of unit price elasticity.
ENDSTOPD of infinite price elasticity.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_6'>A The marginal physical product of the 8th man is lower than the marginal
physical product of the 10th man.
ENDSTOPB The marginal physical product of the 8th man is higher than the marginal
physical product of the 9th man.
ENDSTOPC The marginal physical product of the 9th man is lower than that of the 10th
man.
ENDSTOPD The marginal physical product of the 10th man is negative.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_7'>A average total cost equals average revenue.
ENDSTOPB average total cost is less than average revenue.
ENDSTOPC average total cost is at a minimum.
ENDSTOPD marginal cost is equal to average total cost.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_8'>A The long run average total cost curve is derived by joining all the minimum
points of the short run average total cost curves.
ENDSTOPB The minimum efficient scale is the point at which long run average costs must
begin to fall.
ENDSTOPC In the long run a firm cannot alter its fixed costs of production.
ENDSTOPD If a firm trebles all its inputs and its output doubles then this is indicative of
diseconomies of scale.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_9'>A The marginal cost of production is less than the average fixed cost of
production.
ENDSTOPB The average cost of production is rising.
ENDSTOPC The average fixed cost of production is rising.
ENDSTOPD The average cost of production exceeds the marginal cost of production.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_10'>A a firm’s competitors match both its price increases and price decreases.
ENDSTOPB one firm in the industry sets the price for all other firms.
ENDSTOPC a firm’s competitors match its price decreases but ignore its price increases.
ENDSTOPD prices can either rise or fall; it depends on what happens to a firm’s
competitors’ prices.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_11'>A a firm charges customers different prices according to how much they
purchase.
ENDSTOPB consumers are grouped into independent markets and a separate price is
charged in each market.
ENDSTOPC a firm charges each customer the maximum price he/she is prepared to pay.
ENDSTOPD different firms charge different prices for the same product.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_12'>A Strategy 1
ENDSTOPB Strategy 2
ENDSTOPC Strategy 3
ENDSTOPD Strategy 4</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_13'>A Country A has a comparative advantage and an absolute advantage in
producing Good Y.
ENDSTOPB Country B has a comparative advantage in producing Good X and an absolute
advantage in producing Good Y.
ENDSTOPC Country A has a comparative advantage in producing Good Y and an absolute
advantage in producing Good X.
ENDSTOPD Country B has a comparative advantage in producing Good Y and an absolute
advantage in producing Good X.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_14'>A €700 million
ENDSTOPB €800 million
ENDSTOPC €900 million
ENDSTOPD €1000 million</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_15'>A investment is increased when interest rates fall.
ENDSTOPB an increase in consumer demand leads to a more than proportionate increase in
the level of investment.
ENDSTOPC an increase in investment will lead to a more than proportionate increase in
output.
ENDSTOPD the rate of change of investment affects the rate of change of output.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_16'>A Gross Domestic Product is greater than Gross National Income.
ENDSTOPB Gross Domestic Product is less than Gross National Income.
ENDSTOPC Gross Domestic Product is the same as Gross National Income.
ENDSTOPD We cannot say whether Gross Domestic Product differs from Gross National
Income from this information.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_17'>A fall as the short term interest rate rises.
ENDSTOPB fall as the short term interest rate falls.
ENDSTOPC rise as the short term interest rate rises.
ENDSTOPD rise as the short term interest rate falls.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_18'>A An increase in Government expenditure.
ENDSTOPB A decrease in the marginal propensity to save.
ENDSTOPC An increase in the marginal propensity to save.
ENDSTOPD An increase in autonomous investment.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_19'>A a rise in national income.
ENDSTOPB an unplanned rise in stocks.
ENDSTOPC inflationary pressures.
ENDSTOPD a rise in the amount people plan to invest.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_20'>A an increase in aggregate demand and a reduction in real output and
unemployment.
ENDSTOPB an increase in aggregate demand, real output and unemployment.
ENDSTOPC an increase in aggregate demand and real output and a reduction in
unemployment.
ENDSTOPD a reduction in aggregate demand and real output and an increase in
unemployment.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_21'>A Lowering the rate of interest.
ENDSTOPB Raising the rate of unemployment benefit.
ENDSTOPC Higher voluntary redundancy payments for workers in declining industries.
ENDSTOPD More government funds for retraining of the unemployed.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_22'>A an increase in aggregate demand and a reduction in real output.
ENDSTOPB an increase in aggregate demand and an increase in real output.
ENDSTOPC a reduction in aggregate demand and a reduction in real output.
ENDSTOPD a reduction in aggregate demand and an increase in real output.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_23'>A velocity of circulation and nominal output are both fixed.
ENDSTOPB ratio of the velocity of circulation to the price level is fixed.
ENDSTOPC ratio of the money supply to the velocity of circulation is fixed.
ENDSTOPD velocity of circulation and real output are both fixed.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_24'>A It has improved by 100 per cent.
ENDSTOPB It has improved by 60 per cent.
ENDSTOPC It has deteriorated by 100 per cent.
ENDSTOPD It has deteriorated by 60 per cent.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_25'>A Migrant remittances
ENDSTOPB Interest, profits and dividends paid to the rest of the world.
ENDSTOPC Exports of services
ENDSTOPD The purchase of foreign shares by a domestic pension fund.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_choices_26'>A marginal cost than other countries.
ENDSTOPB labour cost than other countries.
ENDSTOPC absolute cost than other countries.
ENDSTOPD opportunity cost than other countries.</string>"

</resources>