<resources>
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_1'>A Adverse selection describes the fact that people who know that they are a
particularly bad risk are more inclined to take out insurance.
ENDSTOPB Adverse selection describes the fact that a policyholder may act in a way
which makes the insured event more likely to occur.
ENDSTOPC Adverse selection describes the fact that people who know that they are a
particularly bad risk are less inclined to take out insurance.
ENDSTOPD Adverse selection describes the risk that an insurance company will face false
insurance claims.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_2'>A entry into new markets
ENDSTOPB risk sharing
ENDSTOPC capital pooling
ENDSTOPD to reduce overall managerial remuneration</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_3'>A a firm charges customers different prices according to how much they
purchase.
ENDSTOPB consumers are grouped into independent markets and a separate price is
charged in each market.
ENDSTOPC a firm charges each customer the maximum price that he/she is prepared to
pay.
ENDSTOPD different firms charge different prices for the same product.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_4'>A a perfect substitute
ENDSTOPB an imperfect substitute
ENDSTOPC a perfect complement
ENDSTOPD an imperfect complement</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_5'>A The income elasticity of demand is negative.
ENDSTOPB The income elasticity of demand is between zero and one.
ENDSTOPC The demand for the good increases as income falls.
ENDSTOPD The demand will rise if its price falls.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_6'>A a market system.
ENDSTOPB macroeconomics.
ENDSTOPC competition.
ENDSTOPD opportunity cost.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_7'>A to make the demand for the product more price elastic
ENDSTOPB to shift the demand for the firm’s product to the right
ENDSTOPC to increase barriers to entry
ENDSTOPD to increase sales and so help the firm exploit economies of scale</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_8'>A Marginal cost cannot exceed average total cost.
ENDSTOPB Marginal cost is equal to average variable cost when average variable cost is at
a minimum.
ENDSTOPC Average fixed cost always falls as output rises.
ENDSTOPD Average total cost exceeds average variable cost by an amount that declines
with increasing output.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_9'>A decides on the viability of producing the by-product after it has made the
decision to produce the main product.
ENDSTOPB selects the level of output of the by-product where marginal cost of the byproduct
equals its marginal revenue.
ENDSTOPC selects the combined output where the combined marginal cost equals the
combined marginal revenue.
ENDSTOPD uses cost-based pricing for the main product and the by-product.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_10'>A In monopolistic competition, supernormal profits cannot be made in the long
run.
ENDSTOPB Price discrimination is impossible under perfect competition.
ENDSTOPC Collusion may occur between firms in oligopolistic competition.
ENDSTOPD A firm in perfect competition faces a perfectly inelastic demand curve.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_11'>A the firm has to charge a price higher than the marginal cost of producing the
last unit.
ENDSTOPB any decision by the monopolist to sell an additional unit of output does not
affect price.
ENDSTOPC the firm has to reduce the price on all units sold in order to sell the additional
unit.
ENDSTOPD the law of diminishing returns directly affects the price of an imperfectly
competitive firm’s product.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_12'>A There is a large number of firms.
ENDSTOPB There is an absence of barriers to entry into the market.
ENDSTOPC Demand for each firm is infinitely price elastic.
ENDSTOPD The output decisions of one firm may exert a significant influence on other
firms in the industry.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_13'>A the dominant firm hypothesis.
ENDSTOPB collusion.
ENDSTOPC non-cooperative oligopoly.
ENDSTOPD product differentiation.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_14'>A a rise in the average price of imports relative to the average price of exports
ENDSTOPB a fall in the quantity of imports relative to the quantity of exports
ENDSTOPC a rise in the quantity of exports while imports remain the same
ENDSTOPD a rise in the average price of exports relative to the average price of imports</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_15'>A national income and interest rates will both rise
ENDSTOPB national income and interest rates will both fall
ENDSTOPC the effect on both national income and interest rates is uncertain
ENDSTOPD national income will rise but the effect on interest rates is uncertain</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_16'>A a fall in investment due to the associated rise in the interest rate
ENDSTOPB a fall in consumer demand due to the fear of higher future taxes
ENDSTOPC reduced import expenditure due to increased government demand for
domestically produced goods
ENDSTOPD a fall in demand for exports due to an exchange rate appreciation as a result of
the associated rise in the interest rate</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_17'>A the marginal cost curve cuts the marginal revenue curve.
ENDSTOPB the marginal cost curve cuts the demand curve.
ENDSTOPC the average cost curve cuts the marginal revenue curve.
ENDSTOPD the average cost curve cuts the demand curve.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_18'>A increasing social security benefits
ENDSTOPB increasing the money supply
ENDSTOPC reducing corporate and personal taxation
ENDSTOPD increasing government expenditure aimed at exploiting the multiplier effect</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_19'>A rise and reduce money demand.
ENDSTOPB rise and raise money demand.
ENDSTOPC fall and reduce money demand.
ENDSTOPD fall and raise money demand.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_20'>A The real rate of interest is positive.
ENDSTOPB The expected rate of inflation is less than the real rate of interest.
ENDSTOPC The real rate of interest is greater than the nominal rate of interest.
ENDSTOPD The real rate of interest is –1%.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_21'>A a fall in the interest rate of Country A with an even bigger fall in Country B’s
interest rate
ENDSTOPB a fall in the interest rate of Country A with constant interest rate in Country B
ENDSTOPC a rise in the interest rate of Country A with an even bigger rise in Country B’s
interest rate
ENDSTOPD a fall in the interest rate of Country A with a rise in the interest rate of Country
B</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_22'>A decrease and the domestic money supply will rise.
ENDSTOPB decrease and the domestic money supply will fall.
ENDSTOPC increase and the domestic money supply will rise.
ENDSTOPD increase and the domestic money supply will fall.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_23'>A the total population.
ENDSTOPB the total labour force.
ENDSTOPC the number of employed.
ENDSTOPD the number in the population who are of working age.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_24'>A fall and unemployment would rise.
ENDSTOPB fall and unemployment would fall.
ENDSTOPC rise and unemployment would fall.
ENDSTOPD rise and unemployment would rise.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_25'>A the higher the level of prices, the lower will be the rate of unemployment.
ENDSTOPB the higher the rate of inflation, the lower will be the rate of unemployment.
ENDSTOPC the lower the level of prices, the lower will be the rate of unemployment.
ENDSTOPD the higher the rate of inflation, the higher will be the rate of unemployment.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2017_choices_26'>A salaries of school teachers
ENDSTOPB net income from abroad
ENDSTOPC company profits
ENDSTOPD investment expenditure</string>"

</resources>