<resources>
    <string name='sep2008_que_1'>Which of the following will cause a production possibility frontier to shift outward?</string>
    "<string name='sep2008_que_2'>A maximum price is set for Good X at £25 which happens to be equal to the free
market price. An increase in the demand for Good X keeping the maximum price
fixed at £25 will lead to:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_que_3'>Good Y has a cross price elasticity of demand with respect to Good X of 0.5 and 100
units of Good Y are demanded when Good X costs 50 pence. A rise in the price of
Good X to 75 pence will lead to a change in the demand for Good Y to:</string>"
    <string name='sep2008_que_4'>Which of the following statements is FALSE?</string>
    "<string name='sep2008_que_5'>An individual can consume either bananas or apples. The price of bananas and apples
is the same. The individual calculates that the marginal utility of bananas is higher
than the marginal utility of apples. The individual could be better off by consuming:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_que_6'>In terms of utility theory, if the absolute value of the certainty equivalent decreases as
a proportion of total wealth as wealth increases, an investor is said to exhibit:</string>"
    <string name='sep2008_que_7'>Which one of the following statements about short run costs of production is FALSE?</string>
    "<string name='sep2008_que_8'>In a monopolistically competitive market profits will be driven to their normal level
because of:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_que_9'>A profit maximising monopolist with positive marginal costs and a downward sloping
demand curve will set its price in the region of the demand curve where the price
elasticity of demand is:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_que_10'>The following data relate to a perfectly competitive firm producing Good X in the
short run. The market price of Good X is £5. Which one of the following statements is TRUE?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_que_11'>In the long run, a firm operating under conditions of monopolistic competition will
produce at an output at which:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_que_12'>Which of the following describes a situation in which there are constant returns to
scale?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_que_13'>Given the following data for Country A, what is the value of injections into the
circular flow of income?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_que_14'>If consumption expenditure increases from £18,000 to £19,500 when disposable
income increases from £20,000 to £26,000 then:</string>"
    <string name='sep2008_que_15'>The accelerator principle states that:</string>
    "<string name='sep2008_que_16'>To reduce the crowding out of private expenditure when government expenditure is
increased the authorities could:</string>"
    <string name='sep2008_que_17'>If a country has a negative Net Property Income from abroad then:</string>
    "<string name='sep2008_que_18'>In 2000 the nominal Gross Domestic Product (GDP) per capita is £20,000 and the
GDP deflator is 100. In 2007 the nominal GDP per capita is £30,000 and the GDP
deflator is 120. Real GDP per capita for 2007 at 2000 prices is:</string>"
    <string name='sep2008_que_19'>The average propensity to consume is defined as the:</string>
    <string name='sep2008_que_20'>An increase in the marginal propensity to import:</string>
    <string name='sep2008_que_21'>Which of the following would a central bank use to decrease the money supply?</string>
    "<string name='sep2008_que_22'>If two countries start to trade with each other on the basis of comparative advantage,
then each country:
I can consume more of the goods which it now imports than before trade.
II can consume more of the goods which it now exports than before trade.
III can consume beyond its production possibility frontier.
Answer:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_que_23'>Which of the following is best suited to reducing the level of structural
unemployment?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2008_que_24'>If the nominal money supply is 800, output (the real level of economic activity) is
2,000 and the average price level is 12, then the velocity of circulation is:</string>"
    <string name='sep2008_que_25'>Which of the following groups is most likely to gain from unanticipated inflation?</string>
    "<string name='sep2008_que_26'>Country A exports Good X and imports Good Y from Country B. The price of Good X
rises by 20 per cent and the price of Good Y falls by 40 per cent. Which of the
following statements is correct about Country A’s terms of trade?</string>"

</resources>