<resources>
    "<string name='sep2012_que_1'>Which of the following will result from the imposition of a 9 per cent sales tax on
household fuel, the demand for which has an absolute price elasticity of demand equal
to 1.5?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_que_2'>A minimum price is set for Good X at £10 which happens to coincide with the free
market price. An increase in the demand for Good X keeping the minimum price
fixed at £10 will lead to:</string>"
    <string name='sep2012_que_3'>Which of the following statements about short run costs of production is incorrect?</string>
    "<string name='sep2012_que_4'>Which of the following is NOT a feature of an industry characterised by monopolistic
competition?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_que_5'>A profit maximising monopolist with positive marginal costs and a downward sloping
demand curve will be able to make most profit if the demand curve is:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_que_6'>The following data is for a perfectly competitive firm producing Good X in the short
run: Which one of the following statements is correct?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_que_7'>In the long run, a firm operating under conditions of monopolistic competition will
produce at an output at which:</string>"
    <string name='sep2012_que_8'>Which one of the following is TRUE?</string>
    "<string name='sep2012_que_9'>Total costs of production for a firm producing 100 units of output are $5,000 and
fixed costs are $2,000. If output is increased by 1 unit in the short run, the total costs
of production are $5,030. Which one of the following statements is TRUE with
respect to the extra unit of output?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_que_10'>The idea that an oligopolistic firm faces a kinked demand curve is based upon the
assumption that:</string>"
    <string name='sep2012_que_11'>First degree price discrimination refers to the situation where:</string>
    "<string name='sep2012_que_12'>The profit payoffs to Firm X from various strategies 1 to 4 and the presumed
responses of the other firm in a duopoly industry is given below: Which one of the following represents the maximin strategy of Firm X?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_que_13'>Given the following labour hours to produce 1 unit of Goods X and Y, which of the
statements below is TRUE?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_que_14'>In an open economy with no taxation, the marginal propensity to save is 0.25 and the
level of income is €800m. What is the likely level of consumption expenditure
resulting from a rise in government expenditure of €100 million?</string>"
    <string name='sep2012_que_15'>The accelerator principle states that:</string>
    <string name='sep2012_que_16'>If a country has a negative net income from abroad then:</string>
    "<string name='sep2012_que_17'>If the money supply decreases due to a contractionary open market operation by the
central bank then the price of treasury bills will:</string>"
    <string name='sep2012_que_18'>Which of the following will increase the size of the multiplier?</string>
    "<string name='sep2012_que_19'>In a closed economy with no government sector if the amount people plan to save
exceeds the amount they plan to invest then there will be:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_que_20'>According to Keynesian analysis, the adoption of an expansionary fiscal policy will
result in:</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_que_21'>Which of the following is best suited to reducing the level of structural
unemployment?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_que_22'>According to Keynesian analysis, the adoption of a policy to reduce the government’s
budget deficit will involve:</string>"
    <string name='sep2012_que_23'>The quantity theory of money in its simplest form assumes that the:</string>
    "<string name='sep2012_que_24'>Country A exports Good X and imports Good Y from Country B. The price of Good
X rises by 20 per cent and the price of Good Y falls by 40 per cent. Which of the
following statements is correct about Country A’s terms of trade?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_que_25'>Which of the following would NOT be included in the current account of a country’s
balance of payments?</string>"
    "<string name='sep2012_que_26'>The law of comparative advantage states that countries should specialise in producing
and exporting the goods that they produce at a lower:</string>"
</resources>