<resources>
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_1'>A fluctuate more than consumer expenditure.
ENDSTOPB rise when the long term rate of interest falls.
ENDSTOPC accelerate if business confidence picks up.
ENDSTOPD accelerate if the government increases its capital expenditure.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_2'>A decides on the viability of producing the by-product after it has made the
decision to produce the main product.
ENDSTOPB selects the level of output of the by-product where marginal cost of the byproduct
equals its marginal revenue.
ENDSTOPC selects the combined output where the combined marginal cost equals the
combined marginal revenue.
ENDSTOPD uses cost-based pricing for the main and the by-product.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_3'>A quantity demanded of Good X to fall and the demand curve for Good Y to
shift to the left.
ENDSTOPB quantity demanded of Good X to fall and the demand curve for Good Y to
shift to the right.
ENDSTOPC quantity demand of Good X to remain constant, but the demand for Good Y to
fall.
ENDSTOPD demand curves for both Good X and Good Y to shift to the right.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_4'>A The income elasticity of demand is negative.
ENDSTOPB The income elasticity of demand is between zero and one.
ENDSTOPC The demand for the good increases as income falls.
ENDSTOPD The demand will rise if its price falls.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_5'>A 7.5 per cent.
ENDSTOPB 15 per cent.
ENDSTOPC 17 per cent.
ENDSTOPD 30 per cent.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_6'>A 1,824.
ENDSTOPB 950.
ENDSTOPC 54.
ENDSTOPD 76.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_7'>A average product of labour when 10 workers are hired is lower than when 11
workers are hired.
ENDSTOPB 11th worker has a higher average product of labour than marginal product of
labour.
ENDSTOPC firm has not yet passed the point of diminishing returns to labour.
ENDSTOPD marginal product of the 11th worker is negative.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_8'>A constant returns to scale.
ENDSTOPB decreasing returns to scale.
ENDSTOPC increasing returns to scale.
ENDSTOPD the law of diminishing returns.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_9'>A 20.
ENDSTOPB 250.
ENDSTOPC 160.
ENDSTOPD 25.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_10'>A An increase in real investment.
ENDSTOPB An increase in Gross Domestic Product.
ENDSTOPC An increase in real Gross Domestic Product.
ENDSTOPD An increase in the Gross Domestic Product price deflator.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_11'>A £215 million.
ENDSTOPB £165 million.
ENDSTOPC £65 million.
ENDSTOPD £100 million.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_12'>A Planned savings are £300 million.
ENDSTOPB The marginal propensity to consume is higher than the average propensity to
consume.
ENDSTOPC Consumption expenditure is equal to £6,500 million.
ENDSTOPD The Gross Domestic Product is £6,800 million.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_13'>A 4
ENDSTOPB 2
ENDSTOPC 1
ENDSTOPD 1.33</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_14'>A time lags
ENDSTOPB uncertainty
ENDSTOPC crowding out
ENDSTOPD the accelerator</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_15'>A decrease the country’s imports.
ENDSTOPB increase the country’s exports.
ENDSTOPC shift the country’s currency supply curve in the foreign exchange market to the
right requiring central bank purchases of the domestic currency to maintain the
fixed exchange rate.
ENDSTOPD shift the demand curve for the country’s foreign exchange to the right
requiring central bank purchases of the domestic currency to maintain the
fixed exchange rate.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_16'>A an expansionary monetary policy.
ENDSTOPB a revaluation of the domestic currency.
ENDSTOPC an expansionary fiscal policy.
ENDSTOPD an increase in taxes.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_17'>A decrease and the domestic money supply rise.
ENDSTOPB decrease and the domestic money supply fall.
ENDSTOPC increase and the domestic money supply rise.
ENDSTOPD increase and the domestic money supply fall.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_18'>A exports of goods
ENDSTOPB foreign direct investment flows
ENDSTOPC unilateral transfers to other nations
ENDSTOPD imports of services</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_19'>A £0.8 / €1.00
ENDSTOPB €0.8 / £1.00
ENDSTOPC £1.25 / €1.00
ENDSTOPD none of the above</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_20'>A less than the price.
ENDSTOPB greater than the price.
ENDSTOPC equal to the price.
ENDSTOPD below average variable cost.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_21'>A £20,000
ENDSTOPB £15,000
ENDSTOPC £7,000
ENDSTOPD £12,000</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_22'>A shut down its production.
ENDSTOPB decreases its level of output but continue to produce carpets.
ENDSTOPC reduce its fixed costs of production.
ENDSTOPD increases its level of output.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_23'>A +£1,000.
ENDSTOPB −£1,000.
ENDSTOPC +£1.
ENDSTOPD −£1.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_24'>A An increase in the price of raw materials.
ENDSTOPB A percentage increase in wages which is less than the percentage increase in
labour productivity.
ENDSTOPC An increase in the profit margins applied by firms.
ENDSTOPD A depreciation of the exchange rate.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_25'>A Exports become less expensive when measured in the foreign currency.
ENDSTOPB Imports become more expensive when measured in the domestic currency.
ENDSTOPC Export values measured in the domestic currency will increase.
ENDSTOPD Import volumes will increase.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2010_choices_26'>A the dominant firm hypothesis.
ENDSTOPB collusion.
ENDSTOPC non-cooperative oligopoly.
ENDSTOPD product differentiation.</string>"

</resources>