<resources>
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_1'>A The effect on price is indeterminate but quantity will fall.
ENDSTOPB The effect on price is indeterminate but quantity will rise.
ENDSTOPC The effect on quantity is indeterminate but price will rise.
ENDSTOPD The effect on quantity is indeterminate but price will fall.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_2'>A 2.0 per cent.
ENDSTOPB 2.5 per cent.
ENDSTOPC 10 per cent.
ENDSTOPD 38 per cent.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_3'>A an increase in incomes
ENDSTOPB a rise in car prices
ENDSTOPC an increase in petrol prices
ENDSTOPD a rise in the price of rail travel</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_4'>A significant economies of scale
ENDSTOPB heavy potential advertising costs
ENDSTOPC large capital requirements
ENDSTOPD constant returns to scale</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_5'>A increase as its output increases.
ENDSTOPB decrease as its output increases.
ENDSTOPC remain constant as its output increases.
ENDSTOPD always be greater than its average variable costs of production.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_6'>A raise their price in the short run but the price will fall back to its original level
in the long run.
ENDSTOPB keep their price constant both in the short and in the long run.
ENDSTOPC raise price in both the short run and the long run.
ENDSTOPD keep price constant in the short run but raise their price in the long run.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_7'>A the market price to fall but quantity supplied to increase.
ENDSTOPB the market price to rise but quantity supplied to fall.
ENDSTOPC both market price and quantity supplied to rise.
ENDSTOPD no change to the market price or quantity supplied.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_8'>A excess demand and shortages.
ENDSTOPB excess supply and surpluses.
ENDSTOPC excess demand and surpluses.
ENDSTOPD excess supply and shortages.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_9'>A its marginal costs of production decrease.
ENDSTOPB it is making excess profits.
ENDSTOPC its fixed costs of production decrease.
ENDSTOPD it is making a loss.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_10'>A When the monopolistically competitive industry achieves a long-run equilibrium,
price is greater than marginal cost.
ENDSTOPB Monopolistically competitive firms offer differentiated products and face a
downward sloping demand curve.
ENDSTOPC Under monopolistic competition, the price charged to the consumer is equal to the
average revenue of the firm.
ENDSTOPD Monopolistically competitive firms can earn supernormal profits in the long run.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_11'>A comparability
ENDSTOPB indifference
ENDSTOPC independence
ENDSTOPD transitivity</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_12'>A fall at an increasing rate.
ENDSTOPB fall at a decreasing rate.
ENDSTOPC rise at an increasing rate.
ENDSTOPD rise at a decreasing rate.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_13'>A marginal utility will rise.
ENDSTOPB total utility will be unchanged.
ENDSTOPC marginal utility will fall.
ENDSTOPD money income is unchanged.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_14'>A be less than the average tax rate.
ENDSTOPB be greater than the average tax rate.
ENDSTOPC be equal to the average tax rate.
ENDSTOPD initially be less than, but eventually greater than, the average tax rate.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_15'>A £180 million
ENDSTOPB £200 million
ENDSTOPC £220 million
ENDSTOPD £240 million</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_16'>A Savings, taxes and investment are withdrawals.
ENDSTOPB Exports, imports and government expenditure are withdrawals.
ENDSTOPC Investment, government expenditure and exports are injections.
ENDSTOPD Investment, exports and consumption are injections..</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_17'>A wages from self employment
ENDSTOPB property rental income
ENDSTOPC transfer payments
ENDSTOPD net property income from abroad</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_18'>A The demand for money is interest elastic and private investment is interest
inelastic.
ENDSTOPB The demand for money is interest inelastic and private investment is interest
elastic.
ENDSTOPC The demand for money and private investment are both interest inelastic.
ENDSTOPD The demand for money and private investment are both interest elastic.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_19'>A rise and reduce money demand.
ENDSTOPB rise and raise money demand.
ENDSTOPC fall and reduce money demand.
ENDSTOPD fall and raise money demand.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_20'>A £500 million
ENDSTOPB £700 million
ENDSTOPC £1,000 million
ENDSTOPD £1,300 million</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_21'>A rise in long term interest rates.
ENDSTOPB increase in the money supply.
ENDSTOPC a fall in bond prices.
ENDSTOPD none of the above.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_22'>A increase the cash reserves of commercial banks and increase the monetary
base.
ENDSTOPB increase the cash reserves of commercial banks and reduce the monetary base.
ENDSTOPC reduce the cash reserves of commercial banks and increase the monetary base.
ENDSTOPD reduce the cash reserves of commercial banks and reduce the monetary base.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_23'>A The IS curve shifts left and the LM curve remains in the same place.
ENDSTOPB The IS curve shifts right and the LM curve remains in the same place.
ENDSTOPC The LM curve shifts left and the IS curve remains in the same place.
ENDSTOPD The LM curve shifts right and the IS curve remains in the same place.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_24'>A investment is increased when interest rates fall.
ENDSTOPB an increase in investment will lead to a proportionate increase in output.
ENDSTOPC the rate of change of investment is directly proportional to the rate of change of
output.
ENDSTOPD small fluctuations in national income can lead to large fluctuations in investment
demand.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_25'>A Country A has a comparative advantage and an absolute advantage in
producing Good Y.
ENDSTOPB Country B has a comparative advantage in producing Good X and an absolute
advantage in producing Good Y.
ENDSTOPC Country A has a comparative advantage in producing Good Y and an absolute
advantage in producing Good X.
ENDSTOPD Country B has a comparative advantage in producing Good Y and an absolute
advantage in producing Good X.</string>"
    "<string name='sep2009_choices_26'>A An appreciation of a country’s exchange rate will increase its import volumes
and decrease its export volumes.
ENDSTOPB An appreciation of a country’s exchange rate will increase its import
expenditure and decrease its export revenues.
ENDSTOPC A depreciation of a country’s exchange rate will decrease its import volumes
and decrease its export volumes.
ENDSTOPD A depreciation of a country’s exchange rate will decrease its import
expenditure and increase its export revenues.</string>"

</resources>